<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<modules xmlns="http://www.example.org/Phresco">
    <module id="mod_block__7.0" name="block" version="7.0" core="true" required="true">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Blocks are the boxes of content (such as &quot;User Login&quot; or &quot;Who's online&quot;) that can be displayed in regions (such as footer or sidebar) on your page.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Blocks are the boxes of content (such as &quot;User Login&quot; or &quot;Who's online&quot;) that can be displayed in regions (such as footer or sidebar) on your page.Blocks are made available to your site most commonly by enabling modules. Once created, a Block can be modified to adjust its appearance, shape, size and position - or which Website pages it appears on. For example, enabling the core Poll module makes the &quot;Most Recent Polls&quot; block available for you to place in a region. The block management screen also provides checkboxes (depending on your version of Drupal and what modules you have enabled), as well as a configure link, which takes you to the configuration screen. The checkboxes and configuration page let you customize the visibility of the block. A block's visibility depends on:

• Whether it is Enabled and assigned to a region. Disabled blocks (blocks not assigned to any region in your theme) are never shown.

• The Throttle checkbox (if you have the Throttle module enabled). Throttled blocks are hidden during high server loads.

• Page-specific visibility settings. Individual blocks can be configured to only show/hide on certain pages. You can also show/hide blocks based on the result of a PHP snippet.

• Custom visibility settings. Individual blocks can be configured so that users decide whether to show/hide certain blocks.

• Its function. Dynamic blocks (such as those defined by modules) may be empty on certain pages and will not be shown.

The block management screen also has an &quot;Add block&quot; link. This allows you to define a block containing content of your choice. Each administrator-defined block consists of a title, a description, and a body which can be as long as you wish; the Drupal engine will render the content of the block.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_field__7.0" name="field" version="7.0" core="true" required="true">
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>The Field API allows custom data fields to be attached to Drupal entities and takes care of storing, loading, editing, and rendering field data

</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>The Field API allows custom data fields to be attached to Drupal entities and takes care of storing, loading, editing, and rendering field data. Any entity type (node, user, etc.) can use the Field API to make itself &quot;fieldable&quot; and thus allow fields to be attached to it. Other modules can provide a user interface for managing custom fields via a web browser as well as a wide and flexible variety of data type, form element, and display format capabilities.

The Field API defines two primary data structures, Field and Instance, and the concept of a Bundle. A Field defines a particular type of data that can be attached to entities. A Field Instance is a Field attached to a single Bundle. A Bundle is a set of fields that are treated as a group by the Field Attach API and is related to a single fieldable entity type.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_field_sql_storage__7.0" name="field_sql_storage" version="7.0" core="true" required="true">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>The Field SQL Storage module provides data management for the Field module. This module uses the Field API to generate dynamic data tables for entities and fields. While this is a required core module, it may be replaced by other contributed modules that implement The Field Storage
</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>The Field SQL Storage module provides data management for the Field module. This module uses the Field API to generate dynamic data tables for entities and fields. While this is a required core module, it may be replaced by other contributed modules that implement The Field Storage API. The Field SQL Storage module provides data management for the Field module. This module uses the Field API to generate dynamic data tables for entities and fields. While this is a required core module, it may be replaced by other contributed modules that implement The Field Storage API.
Field Module :-The Field module allows custom data fields to be attached to Drupal entities (content nodes, users, taxonomy vocabularies, etc.) and takes care of storing, loading, editing, and rendering field data. Most users will not interact with the Field module directly, but will instead use the Field UI module user interface. Module developers can use the Field API to make new entities &quot;fieldable&quot; and allow fields to be attached to their entities.
Field API:-The Field API allows custom data fields to be attached to Drupal entities and takes care of storing, loading, editing, and rendering field data. Any entity type (node, user, etc.) can use the Field API to make itself &quot;fieldable&quot; and thus allow fields to be attached to it. Other modules can provide a user interface for managing custom fields via a web browser as well as a wide and flexible variety of data type, form element, and display format capabilities.
The Field API defines two primary data structures, Field and Instance, and the concept of a Bundle. A Field defines a particular type of data that can be attached to entities. A Field Instance is a Field attached to a single Bundle. A Bundle is a set of fields that are treated as a group by the Field Attach API and is related to a single fieldable entity type.
Field Module :-The Field module allows custom data fields to be attached to Drupal entities (content nodes, users, taxonomy vocabularies, etc.) and takes care of storing, loading, editing, and rendering field data. Most users will not interact with the Field module directly, but will instead use the Field UI module user interface. Module developers can use the Field API to make new entities &quot;fieldable&quot; and allow fields to be attached to their entities.
Field API:-The Field API allows custom data fields to be attached to Drupal entities and takes care of storing, loading, editing, and rendering field data. Any entity type (node, user, etc.) can use the Field API to make itself &quot;fieldable&quot; and thus allow fields to be attached to it. Other modules can provide a user interface for managing custom fields via a web browser as well as a wide and flexible variety of data type, form element, and display format capabilities.
The Field API defines two primary data structures, Field and Instance, and the concept of a Bundle. A Field defines a particular type of data that can be attached to entities. A Field Instance is a Field attached to a single Bundle. A Bundle is a set of fields that are treated as a group by the Field Attach API and is related to a single fieldable entity type.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_file__7.0" name="file" version="7.0" core="true" required="true">
        <dependentModules>mod_field__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>The File module enables you to upload and attach files to content and to manage these uploads if you have the appropriate permissions. This module is responsible for validating file content and managing uploaded files. It also provides options for displaying file content. As a site administrator you will be able to control what type of files can be uploaded and their maximum size.File module provides its functionality by defining a File field type for the Field module</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>The File module enables you to upload and attach files to content and to manage these uploads if you have the appropriate permissions.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_filter__7.0" name="filter" version="7.0" core="true" required="true">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>This module allows you to create content filter using regular expressions. Instead of creating a new module for each filter you need, now you can easily create and organize your own filters. Your filter will appear in the input format configuration page.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module allows you to create content filter using regular expressions. Instead of creating a new module for each filter you need, now you can easily create and organize your own filters. Your filter will appear in the input format configuration page.

For a description of the regular expression syntax, see PCRE regex syntax; for a description of the modifiers, see Possible modifiers in regex patterns. If you know the syntax used by Perl regular expressions, see Differences From Perl.
Features

Instead of creating a new filter module for every filter you need, you can use this module for tasks like creating your own tags, replacing token values and all changes you need in the text.
You can use simple replacements or use php code to write more powerfull things(like use it to highligth code with geshi).

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_node__7.0" name="node" version="7.0" core="true" required="true">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>content on a Drupal website is stored and treated as &quot;nodes.&quot; A node is any posting, such as a page, poll, article, forum topic, or blog entry. Comments are not stored as nodes but are always tied to one. Treating all content as nodes allows the flexibility of creating new types of content. It also allows you to painlessly apply new features or changes to all content.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>All content on a Drupal website is stored and treated as &quot;nodes.&quot; A node is any posting, such as a page, poll, article, forum topic, or blog entry. Comments are not stored as nodes but are always tied to one. Treating all content as nodes allows the flexibility of creating new types of content. It also allows you to painlessly apply new features or changes to all content.
Behind the scenes, the nodes module manages these nodes. This module is what lets you:
• List, sort through, and manage all the content on your site.
• Set defaults for how all posts are displayed.
• List and configure the &quot;content types&quot; for your site, and create new ones.
Offering &quot;content types&quot; is a way Drupal allows you to have different kinds of nodes for different purposes. For example, an &quot;article&quot; is one kind of node, a &quot;book page&quot; another, and a &quot;blog entry&quot; yet another. You can also create new content types of your own.
The Node module manages the creation, editing, deletion, settings, and display of the main site content. Content items managed by the Node module are typically displayed as pages on your site, and include a title, some meta-data (author, creation time, content type, etc.), and optional fields containing text or other data. (Fields are managed by the Field module in Drupal 7.)
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_options__7.0" name="options" version="7.0" core="true" required="true">
        <dependentModules>mod_field__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Defines selection, check box and radio button widgets for text and numeric fields.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module defines selection, check box and radio button widgets for text and numeric fields.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_system__7.0" name="system" version="7.0" core="true" required="true">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Handles general site configuration for administrators.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Administer system configuration' and 'administer users.' It add the following permissions: ... that is, the permission provided by that module are ignore when the permission is granted. System ... not exceptions to them. This approach is what makes System Permissions useful without any special configuration. ...</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_text__7.0" name="text" version="7.0" core="true" required="true">
        <dependentModules>mod_field__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Defines simple text field types.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module defines simple text field types.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_user__7.0" name="user" version="7.0" core="true" required="true">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content> The &quot;User Details&quot; module come with two block: user details: logged-in user and user details: authored user. Both of these block work the same with a different purpose. The &quot;User Details: logged-in user&quot; block supports the logged-in user variables displaying: name, avatar, ...</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content> The &quot;User Details&quot; module come with two block: user details: logged-in user and user details: authored user. Both of these block work the same with a different purpose. The &quot;User Details: logged-in user&quot; block supports the logged-in user variables displaying: name, avatar, ...</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_aggregator__7.0" name="aggregator" version="7.0" core="true" required="false">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Aggregates syndicated content (RSS, RDF, and Atom feeds).

One of our clients came to us with a performance issue on their Drupal 6 multi-site installation. Views were taking ages to save, the admin pages seemed unnecessarily sluggish, and clearing the cache put the site in danger of going down. They reported that the issue was most noticeable in their state-of-the-art hosting environment, yet was not reproducible on a local copy of the site — a baffling scenario as their 8 web heads and 2 database servers were mostly idle while the site struggled along.

Our performance analysis revealed two major issues. After implementing fixes, we saw the average time to save a Drupal view drop from 2 minutes 20 seconds to 4.6 seconds — a massive improvement. Likewise, the time to load the homepage on a warm cache improved from 2.3 seconds to 621 milliseconds. The two bugs that accounted for these huge gains turned out to be very interesting:</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Aggregates syndicated content (RSS, RDF, and Atom feeds).

One of our clients came to us with a performance issue on their Drupal 6 multi-site installation. Views were taking ages to save, the admin pages seemed unnecessarily sluggish, and clearing the cache put the site in danger of going down. They reported that the issue was most noticeable in their state-of-the-art hosting environment, yet was not reproducible on a local copy of the site — a baffling scenario as their 8 web heads and 2 database servers were mostly idle while the site struggled along.

Our performance analysis revealed two major issues. After implementing fixes, we saw the average time to save a Drupal view drop from 2 minutes 20 seconds to 4.6 seconds — a massive improvement. Likewise, the time to load the homepage on a warm cache improved from 2.3 seconds to 621 milliseconds. The two bugs that accounted for these huge gains turned out to be very interesting:

1. Intermediary system causes MySQL queries to slow down

Simple queries that are well indexed and cached, can see significant lag when delivering packets through an intermediary. This actually has nothing to do with Drupal, as it is reproducible from the MySQL command line utility. (It’s probably a bug in the MySQL libraries but we’re not entirely sure.) It could also be a problem with the intermediary but we’ve reproduced it in two fairly different systems: F5’s load balancer proxy and VMWare Fusion’s network drivers/stack.

For example:

SELECT cid, data, created, expire, serialized FROM cache_menu WHERE cid IN (x)

A query like this one should execute in a millisecond or less. In our client’s case, however, we found that 40ms was being added to the query time. The strange part is that this extra delay only occurred when the size of the data payload returned was above a certain threshold, so most of the time, similar queries returned quickly, but around 10–20 of these simple queries had 40ms or more added to their execution time, resulting in significant slowdowns.

We briefly debugged the MySQL process and found it to be waiting for data. Unfortunately, we didn’t pursue this much further as the simple workaround was apparent: reroute the MySQL traffic directly to the database instead of through the F5 load balancer. The net change from applying this simple modification is that the time to save a view was reduced to 25.3 seconds.
2. Database prefixing isn’t designed to scale as the number of prefixes increases

Drupal can be configured to share a database with another system or Drupal install. To do this, it uses a function called db_prefix_tables() to add prefixes to table names so they don’t collide with other applications’ table names. Our client was using the table prefixing system to allow various sub-sites to share data such as views and nodes, and thus they had 151 entries in the db_prefixes list.

The problem is that db_prefix_tables() is not well optimized for this implementation edge case. It will run an internal PHP function called strtr() (string token replace) for each prefix, on every database query string. In our case, saving a view executed over 9200 queries, meaning strtr() was called more than 1.4 million times!

We created a fix using preg_replace_callback() which resulted in both the number of calls and execution time dropping dramatically. Our view could now be saved in a mere 10.3 seconds. The patch is awaiting review in the Drupal issue queue, and there’s a patch for Pressflow 6, too, in case someone needs it before it lands in core.

The final tweaks included disabling the administration menu and the query logger. At that point, we finally reached a much more palatable 4.6 seconds for saving a view — still not as fast as it could be, but given the large number of views in the shared system, a respectable figure.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_blog__7.0" name="blog" version="7.0" core="true" required="false">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>The &quot;User Details&quot; module come with two block: user details: logged-in user and user details: authored user. Both of these block work the same with a different purpose. The &quot;User Details: logged-in user&quot; block supports the logged-in user variables displaying: name, avatar, ...Enables multi-user blogs.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>The &quot;User Details&quot; module come with two block: user details: logged-in user and user details: authored user. Both of these block work the same with a different purpose. The &quot;User Details: logged-in user&quot; block supports the logged-in user variables displaying: name, avatar, ...Enables multi-user blogs.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_book__7.0" name="book" version="7.0" core="true" required="false">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>The Book helper module improves Drupal's core book module's functionality. Drupal's Book module, included in core, does a great job at building custom site sections. The Book helper module enables additional features from Drupal's menu system to improve the ordering of a book's pages. ...Allows users to create and organize related content in an outline.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>The Book helper module improves Drupal's core book module's functionality. Drupal's Book module, included in core, does a great job at building custom site sections. The Book helper module enables additional features from Drupal's menu system to improve the ordering of a book's pages. ...This module allows users to create and organize related content in an outline.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_color__7.0" name="color" version="7.0" core="true" required="false">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>
The Color module allows users with the Administer site configuration permission to quickly and easily change the color scheme of themes that have been built to be compatible with it. In order for color module to work, a theme must be specifically designed to use the color changing features. ...
Allows administrators to change the color scheme of compatible themes.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>
The Color module allows users with the Administer site configuration permission to quickly and easily change the color scheme of themes that have been built to be compatible with it. In order for color module to work, a theme must be specifically designed to use the color changing features. ...
This module allows administrators to change the color scheme of compatible themes.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_comment__7.0" name="comment" version="7.0" core="true" required="false">
        <dependentModules>mod_text__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Both comment.load and comment.loadNodeComments currently return the raw column data from the database query in _comment_load(). Contrib modules can add information to the comment object inside hook_comment's &quot;view&quot; operation, however this hook isn't currently being called by either of the Services API ...Allows users to comment on and discuss published content.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Both comment.load and comment.loadNodeComments currently return the raw column data from the database query in _comment_load(). Contrib modules can add information to the comment object inside hook_comment's &quot;view&quot; operation, however this hook isn't currently being called by either of the Services API ...This module allows users to comment on and discuss published content.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_contact__7.0" name="contact" version="7.0" core="true" required="false">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>This is a project to serve as experimentation and backporting of features for core's Contact module. It will serve as a drop-in replacement for the contact module. Enables the use of both personal and site-wide contact forms.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This is a project to serve as experimentation and backporting of features for core's Contact module. It will serve as a drop-in replacement for the contact module. This module enables the use of both personal and site-wide contact forms.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_content_translation__7.0" name="content_translation" version="7.0" core="true" required="false">
        <dependentModules>mod_locale__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>The internationalization group might also be interesting, dealing with content translation support issues in and around ... Description: Translation and internationalization of Drupal You intend to help to translate the Drupal interface to a language? This is the place! Look into the translator's guide ...Allows content to be translated into different languages.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>The internationalization group might also be interesting, dealing with content translation support issues in and around ... Description: Translation and internationalization of Drupal You intend to help to translate the Drupal interface to a language? This is the place! Look into the translator's guide ...This module allows content to be translated into different languages.When the Content Translation module is enabled you can translate site content into different ... for the site interface), the Content Translation module is key to creating and maintaining translated site content.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_contextual_links__7.0" name="contextual_links" version="7.0" core="true" required="true">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Inspired by this discussion http://drupal.org/node/951088 but with some modifikation, I have added the possibility to check the option that all the local task tabs move into the nice contextual links hover menu and that it also appears on full node views and not only on list pages. ...Provides contextual links to perform actions related to elements on a page.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Inspired by this discussion http://drupal.org/node/951088 but with some modifikation, I have added the possibility to check the option that all the local task tabs move into the nice contextual links hover menu and that it also appears on full node views and not only on list pages. ...This module provides contextual links to perform actions related to elements on a page.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_dashboard__7.0" name="dashboard" version="7.0" core="true" required="false">
        <dependentModules>mod_block__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Provides a dashboard page in the administrative interface for organizing administrative tasks and tracking information within your site.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>The Dashboard module provides users with personalized dashboard pages similar to iGoogle ... Multi-dashboard configuration configurable dashboard default setup This module provides a dashboard page in the administrative interface for organizing administrative tasks and tracking information within your site.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_database_logging__7.0" name="database_logging" version="7.0" core="true" required="false">
        <dependentModules>mod_field__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>The username constraint compare the submited password with the login in database ... on create user form as there is no login in database to compare with So basically this username ... with the login database and not with the login form).Logs and records system events to the database.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>The username constraint compare the submited password with the login in database ... on create user form as there is no login in database to compare with So basically this username ... with the login database and not with the login form).This module logs and records system events to the database.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_field_ui__7.0" name="field_ui" version="7.0" core="true" required="false">
        <dependentModules>mod_field__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>User interface for the Field API.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This is the user interface module for Field API module</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_forum__7.0" name="forum" version="7.0" core="true" required="false">
        <dependentModules>mod_field__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_options__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_taxonomy__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_comment__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_text__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Provides discussion forums.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>To a hard question , no amount of short forum posts will provide a good answer. However, the following best practice tips can make participating in the forums a more pleasurable and productive experience ... to at least try to solve your problem before posting to the forums. Why would anyone take the time to help ...This module provides discussion forums.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_help__7.0" name="help" version="7.0" core="true" required="false">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Manages the display of online help.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This is a relatively simple help popup module that provides either: A standard popup window A javascript modal using the script supplied by jqmodal Any number of help popup templates can be created for different purposes on one site, with different dimensions. These can then be implemented ....This module manages the display of online help.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_image__7.0" name="image" version="7.0" core="true" required="false">
        <dependentModules>mod_field__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_file__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Provides image manipulation tools.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>A special interest group focused on dealing within images At its core, image handling also deals with files, so the FileAPI SIG will have content of related interest. A few of the image handling items to discuss include: file storage, derivatives (thumbnails, resizing).This module provides image manipulation tools.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_list__7.0" name="list" version="7.0" core="true" required="false">
        <dependentModules>mod_field__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_options__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Defines list field types. Use with Options to create selection lists.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>The listing location module now has a release candidate. The Listing Premium module is now in place to create paid listings of different levels for different periods of time in conjunction with node checkout , node checkout scheduler and scheduler . The listing module ....This module defines list field types. Use with Options to create selection lists.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_locale__7.0" name="locale" version="7.0" core="true" required="false">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Adds language handling functionality and enables the translation of the user interface to languages other than English.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>You start off with the Localized Drupal installation profile or use the Localization update ... localize.drupal.org. The new files and sources are better in many ways, so we are/were continually migrating to use localize.drupal.org only. It is suggested you look at localize.drupal.org as the primary source of language ....This module adds language handling functionality and enables the translation of the user interface to languages other than English.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_menu__7.0" name="menu" version="7.0" core="true" required="false">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Allows administrators to customize the site navigation menu.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module allows administrators to customize the site navigation menu.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_number__7.0" name="number" version="7.0" core="true" required="false">
        <dependentModules>mod_field__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Defines numeric field types.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>The Format Number API module provides a method to configure number formats (site ... the user enter numbers using the configured thousands separator and decimal point (site default or user ... by the module that can be used by other contributed or custom modules to display numbers accordingly, from PHP ....This module defines numeric field types.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_openid__7.0" name="openid" version="7.0" core="true" required="false">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Allows users to log into your site using OpenID.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module allows users to log into your site using OpenID.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_overlay__7.0" name="overlay" version="7.0" core="true" required="false">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Displays the Drupal administration interface in an overlay.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>The overlay got much darker. It's now almost black, which defeats the purpose of the overlay. See this early sketch? The idea is that the user of the overlay understands that they are in an overlay, hovering over the page they were just on. And when ....This module displays the Drupal administration interface in an overlay.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_path__7.0" name="path" version="7.0" core="true" required="false">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Allows users to rename URLs.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>The path module lets you create custom urls for your Drupal paths. For example, assume you want to post your resume for potential employers. Without the paths module enabled, the URL to view your ... the necessary sql statements for the new drupal installation. .This module allows users to rename URLs.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_php_filter__7.0" name="php_filter" version="7.0" core="true" required="true">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Allows embedded PHP code/snippets to be evaluated.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module is add-on for FeedAPI Item Filter , implementing hook hook_feedapi_itemfilter(). This module creates new item filter to run custom PHP code on already parsed $feed object. This useful ... development, Modules, Syndication) (feedapi php filter) ....This module allows embedded PHP code/snippets to be evaluated.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_poll__7.0" name="poll" version="7.0" core="true" required="false">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Allows your site to capture votes on different topics in the form of multiple choice questions.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>The Poll core module lets you create simple polls. You ask a question, provide possible answers, and let your users vote. Drupal then keeps a running tally of the results..This module allows site to capture votes on different topics in the form of multiple choice questions.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_rdf__7.0" name="rdf" version="7.0" core="true" required="false">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Enriches your content with metadata to let other applications (e.g. search engines, aggregators) better understand its relationships and attributes.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>The Drupal 7 RDF contrib project has now a new home: RDF Extensions (RDFx) . The reasons for this move are explained in this issue. . If you are new to RDF, watch this introduction . RDF is a W3C standard for modeling and sharing distributed knowledge based ....This module enriches  content with metadata to let other applications better understand its relationships and attributes.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_search__7.0" name="search" version="7.0" core="true" required="false">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Enables site-wide keyword searching.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module offers users the ability to save searches executed with the Search API module ... be configured both by admins and/or users and saved searches can also be created without first executing the search. Facet, Views or other filters set for the search will also be included in a saved search, thus ... .It Enables site wide searching</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_shortcut__7.0" name="shortcut" version="7.0" core="true" required="false">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Allows users to manage customizable lists of shortcut links.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This project is being move to Keyboard Shortcut Utility because of a conflict with another core module in D7. This module allow you to create keyboard shortcuts that you can associate with paths, addresses or javascript functions. It also contains a block to display the available shortcuts ....To manage customizable lists of shortcut links</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_statistics__7.0" name="statistics" version="7.0" core="true" required="false">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Logs access statistics for your site.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>The Statistics module shows you how often a given page is viewed, who viewed it, the previous page the user visited (referrer URL), and when it was viewed. These statistics are useful in determining how users are visiting and navigating your site. For more information, see the online handbook entry for the Statistics module..This module logs access statistics for your site.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_syslog__7.0" name="syslog" version="7.0" core="true" required="false">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Logs and records system events to syslog.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Syslog is an operating system administration logging tool, where messages are routed by facility and severity. It is more suitable for medium to large sites, and would not be suitable for shared hosting environments. In the file /etc/syslog.conf you define where messages go for any combination of facility and severity..This module logs and records system events to syslog.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_taxonomy__7.0" name="taxonomy" version="7.0" core="true" required="false">
        <dependentModules>mod_field__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_options__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Managing taxonomy: a group for users and developers to discuss tips ... for developing and using taxonomy and its contributed modules (and, where relevant, the more general topic ... Used taxonomy in such a great way that you have to share? Want to talk about taxonomy so advanced even ....Enables the categorization of content.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>.Managing taxonomy: a group for users and developers to discuss tips ... for developing and using taxonomy and its contributed modules (and, where relevant, the more general topic ... Used taxonomy in such a great way that you have to share? Want to talk about taxonomy so advanced even ...It enables the categorization of content</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_testing__7.0" name="testing" version="7.0" core="true" required="false">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Provides a framework for unit and functional testing.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>If there's a patch, test it. See below for further details. Note that if you ... reports and feature requests Tips for reviewing patches Setting up a testing environment (helping with testing, helping with testing, helping with testing) ....It Provides a framework for unit and functional testing.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_tracker__7.0" name="tracker" version="7.0" core="true" required="false">
        <dependentModules>mod_field__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_text__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_comment__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>The Tracker core module displays a site's most recently added or updated content. The Tracker module also provides user level tracking, which allows you to follow the contributions of specific authors..Enables tracking of recent content for users.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>The Tracker core module displays a site's most recently added or updated content. The Tracker module also provides user level tracking, which allows you to follow the contributions of specific authors..This module enables tracking of recent content for users.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_trigger__7.0" name="trigger" version="7.0" core="true" required="false">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>The Trigger module provides the ability to take a particular action when a trigger occurs.Enables actions to be fired on certain system events, such as when new content is created.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>The Trigger module provides the ability to take a particular action when a trigger occurs.It Enables actions to be fired on certain system events.Actions include functional tasks that are defined by Drupal core modules, and advanced actions that can be defined by the system administrator. Contributed modules can introduce new actions. Some examples of actions are sending an email, publishing a node, banning a user or promoting a node to the front page of a website.
Triggers are defined by modules, and typically result from some characteristic change in an entity maintained by that module. Some examples of triggers are: deleting content, adding a comment, a user has logged in, or adding a term. In addition to the triggers provided by Drupal core modules, more triggers may be added by installed contributed modules.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_update_manager__7.0" name="update_manager" version="7.0" core="true" required="true">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Manager is a set of modules focused on &quot;content manager&quot; users, that is, users that maintain the content of a website (adding, editing and deleting nodes, managing comments, etc), ... The objective is to let things simple even for users that aren't familiar with Drupal. The Main Manager ....Checks for available updates, and can securely install or update modules and themes via a web interface.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Manager is a set of modules focused on &quot;content manager&quot; users, that is, users that maintain the content of a website (adding, editing and deleting nodes, managing comments, etc), ... The objective is to let things simple even for users that aren't familiar with Drupal. The Main Manager ....It checks for available updates.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_toolbar__7.0" name="toolbar" version="7.0" core="true" required="false">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>The Admin and Admin Tools modules create the ultimate Admin Toolbar.Provides a toolbar that shows the top-level administration menu items and links from other modules.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>The Admin and Admin Tools modules create the ultimate Admin Toolbar.It provides the toolbar to show the top level administration menu items and links</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_acl_7.x-1.0-rc1" name="acl" version="7.x-1.0-rc1" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/acl/acl-7.x-1.0-rc1.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/acl/acl-7.x-1.0-rc1.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_acl_7.x-1.0-rc1/7.x-1.0-rc1/mod_acl_7.x-1.0-rc1-7.x-1.0-rc1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>The ACL module, short for Access Control Lists, is an API for other modules to create lists of users and give them access to nodes. It has no UI of its own and will not do anything by itself; install this module only if some other module tells you to.Access control list API. Has no features on its own.
</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>The ACL module, short for Access Control Lists, is an API for other modules to create lists of users and give them access to nodes. It has no UI of its own and will not do anything by itself; install this module only if some other module tells you to.Access control list API. Has no features on its own.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_addtoany_7.x-3.1" name="addtoany" version="7.x-3.1" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/addtoany/addtoany-7.x-3.1.zip" artifactId="modules/addtoany/addtoany-7.x-3.1.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_addtoany_7.x-3.1/7.x-3.1/mod_addtoany_7.x-3.1-7.x-3.1.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Bookmarked this&quot; tabs with a click of a mouse. Go to your Views administration page (Administer › Site ... this module provides --one tab view for each bookmark-type you have created. These views are initially ... for the tab to appear on the nodes (A button for clearing the cache can be found ...Helps readers share, bookmark, and email your articles and pages using any service, such as Facebook, Twitter, Delicious, Digg, and over 100 more using the AddToAny widget. Add to any share :-The share widget (AddToAny) module by Lockerz helps readers share, bookmark, and email your pages and articles (stories) using any service, such as Facebook, Twitter, Google+, StumbleUpon, and over 100 more sharing and social bookmarking sites. Services are updated automatically.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Bookmarked this&quot; tabs with a click of a mouse. Go to your Views administration page (Administer › Site ... this module provides --one tab view for each bookmark-type you have created. These views are initially ... for the tab to appear on the nodes (A button for clearing the cache can be found ...It helps readers to shar, bookmark and email the contents.Add to any share:-The share widget (AddToAny) module by Lockerz helps readers share, bookmark, and email your pages and articles (stories) using any service, such as Facebook, Twitter, Google+, StumbleUpon, and over 100 more sharing and social bookmarking sites. Services are updated automatically.
The button comes with a customizable Smart Menu, which places the services visitors use at the top of the menu, based on each visitor's browsing and sharing history.
• Drupal integration
• Display on articles (stories)
• Display on article (story) teasers
• Display on pages
• Display in blocks
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_backup_migrate_7.x-2.2" name="backup_migrate" version="7.x-2.2" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/backup_migrate/backup_migrate-7.x-2.2.zip" artifactId="modules/backup_migrate/backup_migrate-7.x-2.2.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_backup_migrate_7.x-2.2/7.x-2.2/mod_backup_migrate_7.x-2.2-7.x-2.2.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Backup and Migrate simplifies the task of backing up and restoring your Drupal database or copying your database from one Drupal site to another. It supports gzip, bzip and zip compression as well as automatic scheduled backups.Backup or migrate the Drupal Database quickly and without unnecessary data.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module backup or migrate the Drupal Database quickly and without unnecessary data.Backup and Migrate simplifies the task of backing up and restoring your Drupal database or copying your database from one Drupal site to another. It supports gzip, bzip and zip compression as well as automatic scheduled backups.With Backup and Migrate you can dump some or all of your database tables to a file download or save to a file on the server, and to restore from an uploaded or previously saved database dump. You can chose which tables and what data to backup and cache data is excluded by default.Security Notice backup files saved to the server are protected from the public by default by a .htaccess rule which will only work on correctly configured Apache Servers. If you are using a server other than Apache, it is recommended that you do not save backups to the server or that you find another way to protect the backup directory from the public.
The module will attempt to check if the destination directory is publicly readable before writing to it, but users are strongly encouraged to confirm this manually by trying to directly download the backup files with a web browser.

This module is not intended for migrating just part of your site from one environment to another. If you want a solution that migrates only certain content, check out this discussion on groups.drupal.org.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_ctools_7.x-1.0-rc1" name="ctools" version="7.x-1.0-rc1" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/ctools/ctools-7.x-1.0-rc1.zip" artifactId="modules/ctools/ctools-7.x-1.0-rc1.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_ctools_7.x-1.0-rc1/7.x-1.0-rc1/mod_ctools_7.x-1.0-rc1-7.x-1.0-rc1.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>This suite is primarily a set of APIs and tools to improve the developer experience. It also contains a module called the Page Manager whose job is to manage pages. In particular it manages panel pages, but as it grows it will be able to manage far more than just Panels.A library of helpful tools by Merlin of Chaos.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This suite is primarily a set of APIs and tools to improve the developer experience. It also contains a module called the Page Manager whose job is to manage pages. In particular it manages panel pages, but as it grows it will be able to manage far more than just Panels..A library of helpful tools by Merlin of Chaos.For the moment, it includes the following tools:

    Plugins -- tools to make it easy for modules to let other modules implement plugins from .inc files.
    Exportables -- tools to make it easier for modules to have objects that live in database or live in code, such as 'default views'.
    AJAX responder -- tools to make it easier for the server to handle AJAX requests and tell the client what to do with them.
    Form tools -- tools to make it easier for forms to deal with AJAX.
    Object caching -- tool to make it easier to edit an object across multiple page requests and cache the editing work.
    Contexts -- the notion of wrapping objects in a unified wrapper and providing an API to create and accept these contexts as input.
    Modal dialog -- tool to make it simple to put a form in a modal dialog.
    Dependent -- a simple form widget to make form items appear and disappear based upon the selections in another item.
    Content -- pluggable content types used as panes in Panels and other modules like Dashboard.
    Form wizard -- an API to make multi-step forms much easier.
    CSS tools -- tools to cache and sanitize CSS easily to make user-input CSS safe.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_ckeditor_7.x-1.3" name="ckeditor" version="7.x-1.3" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/ckeditor/ckeditor_3.5.3.zip" artifactId="modules/ckeditor/ckeditor_3.5.3.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_ckeditor_7.x-1.3/7.x-1.3/mod_ckeditor_7.x-1.3-7.x-1.3.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>This module will allow Drupal to replace textarea fields with the CKEditor - a visual HTML editor, sometimes called WYSIWYG editor. This HTML text editor brings many of the powerful WYSIWYG editing functions of known desktop editors like Word to the web. It's very fast and doesn't require any kind of installation on the client computer.Enables the usage of CKEditor (WYSIWYG) instead of plain text fields.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module will allow Drupal to replace textarea fields with the CKEditor - a visual HTML editor, sometimes called WYSIWYG editor. This HTML text editor brings many of the powerful WYSIWYG editing functions of known desktop editors like Word to the web. It's very fast and doesn't require any kind of installation on the client computer.It enables the usage of CKEditor (WYSIWYG) instead of plain text fields.CKEditor is the next version of FCKeditor. The editor has been rebranded and completely rewritten. It is now much faster (the code has been optimized), loads faster (the number of files has been reduced, so the browser will perform less HTTP requests) and developers friendly.

    End user features
    Developer features

Some features of the CKEditor module:

    ready to use plugins and buttons for &lt;!--break--&gt;and &lt;!--pagebreak--&gt; tags
    support for external file browsers, like CKFinder, IMCE
    CKEditor Link support for easily create links to Drupal internal paths
    CKEditor SWF support for enhance functionality of Flash embedding plugin
    Linkit support for internal linking to nodes, users, views and terms using an autocomplete field
    each user may have it's own configuration (choose skin, toolbar, language, default state of CKEditor, etc.)
    and much more!
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_colorbox_7.x-1.2" name="colorbox" version="7.x-1.2" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/colorbox/colorbox-7.x-1.2.zip" artifactId="modules/colorbox/colorbox-7.x-1.2.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_colorbox_7.x-1.2/7.x-1.2/mod_colorbox_7.x-1.2-7.x-1.2.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Colorbox example with the default style Colorbox is a light-weight, customizable lightbox plugin for jQuery 1.3 through 1.6. This module allows for integration of Colorbox into Drupal. Images, iframed or inline content etc. can be displayed in a overlay above the current page.A light-weight, customizable lightbox plugin for jQuery 1.3 through 1.6.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Colorbox example with the default style.Colorbox is a light-weight, customizable lightbox plugin for jQuery 1.3 through 1.6. This module allows for integration of Colorbox into Drupal.Images, iframed or inline content etc. can be displayed in a overlay above the current page.A light-weight, customizable lightbox plugin for jQuery 1.3 through 1.6.

The Colorbox module:
Excellent integration with Imagefield, Imagecache and Insert modules
Integration Image module
Choose between a default style and a number of other styles that are included.
Style the Colorbox with a custom Colorbox style in your theme.
Drush command to download and install the Colorbox plugin in sites/all/libraries.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_comment_notify_7.x-1.0-rc1" name="comment_notify" version="7.x-1.0-rc1" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/comment_notify/comment_notify-7.x-1.0-rc1.zip" artifactId="modules/comment_notify/comment_notify-7.x-1.0-rc1.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_comment_notify_7.x-1.0-rc1/7.x-1.0-rc1/mod_comment_notify_7.x-1.0-rc1-7.x-1.0-rc1.zip</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_comment__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_text__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_token_7.x-1.0-beta5</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Comment notify is a lightweight tool to send notification e-mails to visitors about new, published comments on pages where they have commented. Comment notify works for both registered and anonymous users.Comment follow-up e-mail notification for anonymous as well as registered users.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Comment notify is a lightweight tool to send notification e-mails to visitors about new, published comments on pages where they have commented. Comment notify works for both registered and anonymous users..Comment follow-up e-mail notification for anonymous as well as registered users.Providing comment notifications for anonymous users is an important tool in bringing anonymous users back to your site, which helps convert anonymous users to registered users. Anonymous comment notification is a critical tool in building a blog comment community; all the major blogging platforms include this functionality.

Many other notification modules do not allow notifications for anonymous users but comment notify does. On the other hand, comment notify's goal of being lightweight means it is missing lots of features. Learn more about different notification modules.)

Features

Mail registered and anonymous users about comment follow-ups
Allow users to unsubscribe from notifications on a specific post with a single click
Allow registered users to preset their follow-up setting in their profile
Users can choose to get notifications about all comments on a node or just replies to their comment
Registered authors can get notifications about comments on their nodes
Note: Since it only notifies you about published comments, this is not a solution to notify admins when they need to moderate comments on their site
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_rules_7.x-2.0-rc2" name="rules" version="7.x-2.0-rc2" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/rules/rules-7.x-2.0-rc2.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/rules/rules-7.x-2.0-rc2.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_rules_7.x-2.0-rc2/7.x-2.0-rc2/mod_rules_7.x-2.0-rc2-7.x-2.0-rc2.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_token_7.x-1.0-beta5</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>The rules module allows site administrators to define conditionally executed actions based on occurring events (known as reactive or ECA rules). It's a replacement with more features for the trigger module in core and the successor of the Drupal 5 workflow-ng module.The rules modules allows site administrators to define conditionally executed actions based on occurring events</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>The rules module allows site administrators to define conditionally executed actions based on occurring events (known as reactive or ECA rules). It's a replacement with more features for the trigger module in core and the successor of the Drupal 5 workflow-ng module.It allows site administrators to define conditionally executed actions based on occurring events.

Features

Obviously, you may use reaction rules to react upon any event with custom conditions and actions.
Allows functionality to be re-used via components (Drupal 6: Rule sets only).
Flexible scheduling system that allows scheduling any component / action.
Users can share their customizations by using the built-in import/export feature. For that the module also integrates with Features.
Modular input evaluation system - for example you can install the Token module and use it in every action.
The module has been developed with site performance in mind, so it makes use of caching routines to speed up rule evaluation.
Rules 2.x (Drupal 7 only) features improved APIs, a new admin UI, support for all entity types, parameter configuration via simple data selection (i.e. just pass node:author as argument) and much more. See this blog post for more details.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_devel_7.x-1.2" name="devel" version="7.x-1.2" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/devel/devel-7.x-1.2.zip" artifactId="modules/devel/devel-7.x-1.2.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_devel_7.x-1.2/7.x-1.2/mod_devel_7.x-1.2-7.x-1.2.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Helper functions for Drupal developers and inquisitive admins. This module can print a summary of all database queries for each page request at the bottom of each page. The summary includes how many times each query was executed on a page (shouldn't run same query multiple times), and how long each query took (short is good - use cache for complex queries).Various blocks, pages, and functions for developers.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Helper functions for Drupal developers and inquisitive admins. This module can print a summary of all database queries for each page request at the bottom of each page. The summary includes how many times each query was executed on a page (shouldn't run same query multiple times), and how long each query took (short is good - use cache for complex queries).Various blocks, pages, and functions for developers.
Also a dprint_r($array) function is provided, which pretty prints arrays. Useful during development. Similarly, a ddebug_backtrace() is offerred.
much more. See this helpful demo page.

Generate content
Accelerate development of your site or module by quickly generating nodes, comments, terms, users, and more.
Devel Node Access (DNA)

View the node access entries for the node(s) that are shown on a page. Essential for developers of node access modules and useful for site admins in debugging problems with those modules.
Performance Logging

This module was removed from devel in 7/2011. It has been revived over at the performance project. Please use its issue queue for discussion.
Compatibility Note:

The Devel module will not work with the old and buggy Zend optimizer 3.2.8 and below (and possibly 3.2.x in general). More info at this comment and the rest of that issue.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_diff_7.x-2.0" name="diff" version="7.x-2.0" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/diff/diff-7.x-2.0.zip" artifactId="modules/diff/diff-7.x-2.0.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_diff_7.x-2.0/7.x-2.0/mod_diff_7.x-2.0-7.x-2.0.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>This module adds a tab for sufficiently permissioned users. The tab shows all revisions like standard Drupal but it also allows pretty viewing of all added/changed/deleted words between revisions.Show difference between node revisions.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module adds a tab for sufficiently permissioned users. The tab shows all revisions like standard Drupal but it also allows pretty viewing of all added/changed/deleted words between revisions.Show difference between node revisions.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_email_7.x-1.0" name="email" version="7.x-1.0" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/email/email-7.x-1.0.zip" artifactId="modules/email/email-7.x-1.0.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_email_7.x-1.0/7.x-1.0/mod_email_7.x-1.0-7.x-1.0.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>This module provides a field type for email addresses.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module provides a field type for email addresses.Features:

Validation of emails
Turns addresses into mailto links
Encryption of email addresses with
Invisimail (Drupal 5 + 6)
SpamSpan (Drupal 6 only)
contact form (see Display settings)
provides Tokens (for D7: use Entity tokens from the Entity API)
exposes fields to Views
can be used with Rules
Panels Integration
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_currency_7.x-1.0" name="currency" version="7.x-1.0" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/currency/currency-7.x-1.0.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/currency/currency-7.x-1.0.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_currency_7.x-1.0/7.x-1.0/mod_currency_7.x-1.0-7.x-1.0.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>This module provides visitors to your web site with currency exchange rates. Provides feature management for Drupal.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module provides visitors to your web site with currency exchange rates. 

Features

This module provides several options that customize its look and feel:

An overview section on the top of the page can contain any text you want.
Users can enter an amount, and that amount will calculated in the target currency.
Provides a link to a detailed history and chart page on Yahoo Finance.
All currency exchange operations are logged to the watchdog (optional).
Provides a callable API for other modules to do currency exchange calculations.
See API.txt for details.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_nicemessages_7.x-1.0-rc1" name="nicemessages" version="7.x-1.0-rc1" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/nicemessages/nicemessages-7.x-1.0-rc1.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/nicemessages/nicemessages-7.x-1.0-rc1.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_nicemessages_7.x-1.0-rc1/7.x-1.0-rc1/mod_nicemessages_7.x-1.0-rc1-7.x-1.0-rc1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Nice messages module changes the way Drupal messages are showing up using stylable jQuery-popups provided by the small and fast jGrowl plugin.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Nice messages module changes the way Drupal messages are showing up using stylable jQuery-popups provided by the small and fast jGrowl plugin. It prevends breaking the look and feel of a website by the massive red, yellow and green boxes showing up frequently when Drupal message system is invoked. Apart from other jQuery plugin libraries like Purr and similar, the jQuery jGrowl plugin supports all browsers including older Browsers like IE6, has only a small size of only 6kb.

Setup instructions

Download latest Nice messages module version from the release section below (for extended users: drush pm-download nicemessages --dev) and download jGrowl jQuery plugin from the authors website here.

Upload the Nice message module archive to your Drupal installation in the folder where you usually install modules, typically it should be under sites/all/modules. If not already, unpack it here and make sure the zip or tar.gz archive is removed.

Upload the jGrowl plugin archive to your Drupal installation in the folder where you usually install libraries, typically it should beunder sites/all/libraries. If not already, unpack jGrowl plugin archive here and make sure the zip or tar.gz archive is removed.

Go to http://yoursite.com/admin/modules or follow it in the admin menu to active the module by checking the box and press save.
Finally go to your userprofile edit page and activate displaying system messages with Nice messages for your user account. The option can be found quite on the bottom of your user profile setup page. Now press save and see Nice messages in action the first time. :)

To style in detail, administrators can customize module behavior at http://yoursite.com/admin/config/system/nicemessages or follow it in the admin menu to set up Nice messages to your needs. Popup delay, holding time, where on the screen (left, right,center,top,bottom), and many more. Additionally, to style font, color, images, background, borders, etc. to fit the look and feel to your needs, it is possible to use css theme overrides (styles presets and export planned). I also recommend to check out the CSS Injector module for that. it changes the look and feel on both, the admin theme side of the world and the actually website front side

Permission settings: It is possible to modify user permissions for 'enable/disable' Nice messages per user role.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_agenda_7.x-1.3" name="agenda" version="7.x-1.3" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/agenda/agenda-7.x-1.3.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/agenda/agenda-7.x-1.3.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_agenda_7.x-1.3/7.x-1.3/mod_agenda_7.x-1.3-7.x-1.3.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_block__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>The Agenda module allows you to display a list of upcoming events from Google Calendar as a block on your website..Show an agenda of events from a remote source</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>The Agenda module allows you to display a list of upcoming events from Google Calendar as a block on your website.The events are automatically downloaded and cached from the Calendar IDs specified in the Agenda administration page. Unlimited calendars can be added, and the colours for each calendar can be specified in the CSS file.

The output is fully themeable, and uses jQuery for dynamic effects such as rounded corners, and click-toggling extra information.

Note: If your dates are displaying a day off, you might be suffering the effects of Daylight Savings Time. Try installing and enabling the Date API and Date Timezone modules, then Daylight Saving Times are handled correctly.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_filefield_sources_7.x-1.4" name="filefield_sources" version="7.x-1.4" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/filefield_sources/filefield_sources-7.x-1.4.zip" artifactId="modules/filefield_sources/filefield_sources-7.x-1.4.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_filefield_sources_7.x-1.4/7.x-1.4/mod_filefield_sources_7.x-1.4-7.x-1.4.zip</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_field__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_file__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>FileField Sources is an extension to the FileField module. The FileField module lets you upload files from your computer through a CCK field. Extends File fields to allow referencing of existing files, remote files, and server files.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>FileField Sources is an extension to the FileField module. The FileField module lets you upload files from your computer through a CCK field. Extends File fields to allow referencing of existing files, remote files, and server files.

The FileField Sources module expands on this ability by allowing you to select new or existing files through additional means, including:

Re-use files by an auto-complete textfield
Attach server-side files uploaded via FTP
Transfer files from a remote server (cURL required)
Select existing files through the IMCE file browser

Although FileField Sources provides several built-in sources, it can be extended by any module through an API for creating new sources. Users can toggle between any of the available methods for selecting a file.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_faq_7.x-1.0-rc1" name="faq" version="7.x-1.0-rc1" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/faq/faq-7.x-1.0-rc1.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/faq/faq-7.x-1.0-rc1.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_faq_7.x-1.0-rc1/7.x-1.0-rc1/mod_faq_7.x-1.0-rc1-7.x-1.0-rc1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>The Frequently Asked Questions (faq) module allows users, with appropriate permissions, to create question and answer pairs which they want displayed on the 'faq' page.Manages configuration of questions for a FAQ page.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module manages configuration of questions for a FAQ page.The 'faq' page is automatically generated from the FAQ nodes configured. Basic Views layouts are also provided and can be customised via the Views UI (rather than via the module settings page).

Features

The layout of the FAQ page can be modified on the settings page. There are four question and answer layouts to choose from. In addition, if the 'Taxonomy' module is enabled, it is possible to put the questions into different categories when editing. Users will need the 'view faq page' permission to view the built-in 'faq' page and will need the 'administer faq' permission to configure the layout, etc.

There are 3 blocks included in this module. The first shows a list of FAQ categories. The other two can show a configurable number of FAQs - one shows recent FAQs, while the other just displays random ones. </content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_front_7.x-2.0" name="front" version="7.x-2.0" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/front/front-7.x-2.0.zip" artifactId="modules/front/front-7.x-2.0.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_front_7.x-2.0/7.x-2.0/mod_front_7.x-2.0-7.x-2.0.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>The Front Page module allows for customised home pages dependant on role. The pages can be of the following types.Allows site admins setup custom front pages for the site.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>The Front Page module allows for customised home pages dependant on role. The pages can be of the following types:This module allows site admins setup custom front pages for the site.

Alias (only 2.x branch) - Allows for another Drupal path to be shown as the home page without redirecting the user.
Redirect - Allows you to redirect users to a local or remote URL.
Themed - Allows you to enter some static text that will be placed into the content area of a standard Drupal page.
Full - Allows for static content to be displayed to the screen as is. This method does not pass through Drupal's theming system.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_getid3_7.x-1.0" name="getid3" version="7.x-1.0" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/getid/getid3-7.x-1.0.zip" artifactId="modules/getid/getid3-7.x-1.0.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_getid3_7.x-1.0/7.x-1.0/mod_getid3_7.x-1.0-7.x-1.0.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>getID3() extracts useful information from multimedia file formats.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>The getID3() Drupal module facilitates the installation and management of the getID3() PHP library, used to extract useful information from MP3s and other multimedia file formats.

This API module is used by other modules to ensure that getID3() is correctly installed. Developers who need the getID3() functionality can make this a dependency by their module, and then call the getid3_load() function to properly use the getID3() library without having to worry about whether it's installed or not..It extracts useful information from multimedia file formats.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_globalredirect_7.x-1.3" name="globalredirect" version="7.x-1.3" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/globalredirect/globalredirect-7.x-1.3.zip" artifactId="modules/globalredirect/globalredirect-7.x-1.3.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_globalredirect_7.x-1.3/7.x-1.3/mod_globalredirect_7.x-1.3-7.x-1.3.zip</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_redirect_7.x-1.0-beta3</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>GlobalRedirect is a simple module which checks the current URL for an alias and does a 301 redirect to it if it is not being used..Searches for an alias of the current URL and 301 redirects if found. Stops duplicate content arising when path module is enabled.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>GlobalRedirect is a simple module which checks the current URL for an alias and does a 301 redirect to it if it is not being used..Searches for an alias of the current URL and 301 redirects if found. Stops duplicate content arising when path module is enabled..Searches for an alias of the current URL.

Checks the current URL for a trailing slash, removes it if present and repeats check 1 with the new request. 
•  Checks if the current URL is the same as the site_frontpage and redirects to the frontpage if there is a match. 
•  Checks if the Clean URLs feature is enabled and then checks the current URL is being accessed using the clean method rather than the 'unclean' method. 
•  Checks access to the URL. If the user does not have access to the path, then no redirects are done. This helps avoid exposing private aliased node's. 
•  Make sure the case of the URL being accessed is the same as the one set by the author/administrator. For example, if you set the alias &quot;articles/cake-making&quot; to node/123, then the user can access the alias with any combination of case. 
•  Most of the above options are configurable in the settings page. In Drupal 5 you can access this after enabling the globalredirect_admin module. In Drupal 6, the settings page is bundled into the module.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_google_analytics_7.x-1.2" name="google_analytics" version="7.x-1.2" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/google_analytics/google_analytics-7.x-1.2.zip" artifactId="modules/google_analytics/google_analytics-7.x-1.2.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_google_analytics_7.x-1.2/7.x-1.2/mod_google_analytics_7.x-1.2-7.x-1.2.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Adds the Google Analytics web statistics tracking system to your website..Allows your site to be tracked by Google Analytics by adding a Javascript tracking code to every page.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Adds the Google Analytics web statistics tracking system to your website.

The module allows you to add the following statistics features to your site:

Single/multi/cross domain tracking
Selectively track/exclude certain users, roles and pages
Monitor what type of links are tracked (downloads, outgoing and mailto)
Monitor what files are downloaded from your pages
Custom variables support with tokens
Custom code snippets
Site Search support
AdSense support
Tracking of Goals
Anonymize visitors IP address
Cache the Google Analytics code on your local server for improved page loading times
Access denied (403) and Page not found (404) tracking
DoNotTrack support (non-cached content only)
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_search_autocomplete_7.x-1.0" name="search_autocomplete" version="7.x-1.0" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/search_autocomplete/search_autocomplete-7.x-1.0.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/search_autocomplete/search_autocomplete-7.x-1.0.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_search_autocomplete_7.x-1.0/7.x-1.0/mod_search_autocomplete_7.x-1.0-7.x-1.0.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_search__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>This module allows you to add autocomplete functionality to the search fields of a Drupal site. During the input, the field will be expanded and offer a list of suggestions before you start the search.

The module integrates with search forms from the Drupal core Search.Provides aucompletion for Drupal search forms.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module allows you to add autocomplete functionality to the search fields of a Drupal site. During the input, the field will be expanded and offer a list of suggestions before you start the search.

The module integrates with search forms from the Drupal core Search.Provides aucompletion for Drupal search forms.

Features

This module offers similar behaviors to versions D5, D6 and D7.
New in v1.0

Offers integration with Search from Drupal core. Autocompletion can be set to:
      Search Page content search form
      Search Block form
      Theme Search Form (no more existing in Drupal 7)
      Suggestions come from the search_index table. In other words, it can be any word appearing in your content.
      Autocompletion is made thought Drupal Form API capacities (misc/autocomplete.js), in other words it enables the Drupal core 
      autocompletion.
      Choice of the number of characters to be input before autocompletion suggestions appears.
      Choice of the number of suggestions to display.
Suggestions can be sorted:
    naturally (none)
    alphabetically
    by keyword score
    by keyword relevancy

New in v2.0

Autocomplete potentially any form in your website using id selector.
Use a standalone jquery plugin for autocompletion providing more settings, such as coloration, highlighting, caching, etc...
Forms to autocomplete are individually configurable
More types of suggestions to display are available:

      words (any word in your site)
      node titles
      comment titles (if optional module comment enabled)
      taxonomies (if optional module taxonomy enabled)

Each type of suggestion is prefixable (to indicate your user what the suggestion stand for)
Add your own suggestion type for even more convenience.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_image_resize_filter_7.x-1.13" name="image_resize_filter" version="7.x-1.13" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/image_resize_filter/image_resize_filter-7.x-1.13.zip" artifactId="modules/image_resize_filter/image_resize_filter-7.x-1.13.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_image_resize_filter_7.x-1.13/7.x-1.13/mod_image_resize_filter_7.x-1.13-7.x-1.13.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>The easiest end-user solution for resizing inline images.Filter to automatically scale images to their height and width dimensions.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>The easiest end-user solution for resizing inline images.Filter to automatically scale images to their height and width dimensions.

This filter makes it easy to resize images, especially when combined with a WYSIWYG editor such as tinyMCE or CKeditor. Users never have to worry about scaling image sizes again, just insert an image and set it's height and width properties in HTML (this is done automatically by WYSIWYG editors) and the image is resized on output to match the HTML.

Features:

Automatically resizes both local and (optionally) remote images.
Optionally create a link to full size images from the resized inline versions.
Prevents inline &quot;hot linking&quot; of images from other sites by storing them locally.
Adds height and width attributes to inline images when your users are too lazy to add them.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_imagecache_profiles_7.x-1.0-rc2" name="imagecache_profiles" version="7.x-1.0-rc2" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/imagecache_profiles/imagecache_profiles-7.x-1.0-rc2.zip" artifactId="modules/imagecache_profiles/imagecache_profiles-7.x-1.0-rc2.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_imagecache_profiles_7.x-1.0-rc2/7.x-1.0-rc2/mod_imagecache_profiles_7.x-1.0-rc2-7.x-1.0-rc2.zip</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_field__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_file__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_image__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>ImageCache_Profiles module allows you to set user profile pictures that are consistent .Utilizes image styles for user profile pictures.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>ImageCache_Profiles module allows you to set user profile pictures that are consistent .It utilizes image styles for user profile pictures.Throughout your site and allows avatars on the user profile pages, nodes and comments to be a different size. </content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_paypal_api_7.x-1.1" name="paypal_api" version="7.x-1.1" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/paypal_api/paypal_api-7.x-1.1.zip" artifactId="modules/paypal_api/paypal_api-7.x-1.1.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_paypal_api_7.x-1.1/7.x-1.1/mod_paypal_api_7.x-1.1-7.x-1.1.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Implements the Paypal API for Drupal sites.With this module you may configure content types to require payment for creating or viewing. You may further limit viewing to payment per instance, or payment to view any instance of a given type. .Implements the PayPal API for Drupal sites</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Implements the Paypal API for Drupal sites.With this module you may configure content types to require payment for creating or viewing. You may further limit viewing to payment per instance, or payment to view any instance of a given type. .Implements the PayPal API for Drupal sites. 

This module does not seek to be a full-blown e-commerce system, so it will never provide a shopping cart or other e-commerce tools.

Rather, it allows developers to build e-commerce systems, using this module for the payment gateway.

Out of the box, you can configure the system to require payment to view or create given content. Paypal API manages a simple ledger to control user access to paid content.

Payments may be configured to be made either through a Pay Now button you create through your Paypal account, or Paypal API can create them for you.

If you choose to use the Paypal API, you will need to store your Paypal account email in your Drupal web site. Use of Pay Now buttons created through your control panel do not have this requirement.

Either way, the Paypal API module handles your IPN (instant payment notification) for you, and you may create custom code in your own module to handle the payment notification (through hook_paypal_api_ipn()) or else query Paypal API as necessary. See paypal_api.api.php in this package for more documentation. 

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_imagefield_crop_7.x-1.0" name="imagefield_crop" version="7.x-1.0" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/imagefield_crop/imagefield_crop-7.x-1.0.zip" artifactId="modules/imagefield_crop/imagefield_crop-7.x-1.0.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_imagefield_crop_7.x-1.0/7.x-1.0/mod_imagefield_crop_7.x-1.0-7.x-1.0.zip</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_field__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_file__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_image__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Add cropping ability to images using javascript. imagefield_crop provides a widget for cropping an image after upload.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module adds cropping ability to images using javascript. imagefield_crop provides a widget for cropping an image after upload.

When the user uploads an image, the image is presented inside a cropping area. A cropping box is shown inside, and the user can resize and move it. Upon clicking 'preview' or 'submit', the image is cropped and the result is saved instead of the original image.

Watch the screencast by capellic (Note: the screencast was made for the 6.x version of this module).
Features

Seamless, intuitive cropping, almost like using a desktop photo editing app
All major browsers supported
Dynamic preview - you see how your crop will look like, in real time!
Original image is saved for recropping.
No matter what resolution the cropping area is, the original image is used for cropping (for highest quality)
The sizes of the cropping area, cropping box and resulting image can be controlled by the administrator

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_starrating_7.x-1.0" name="starrating" version="7.x-1.0" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/starrating/starrating-7.x-1.0.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/starrating/starrating-7.x-1.0.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_starrating_7.x-1.0/7.x-1.0/mod_starrating_7.x-1.0-7.x-1.0.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_field__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Star Rating is a simple module that provides star rating field and display formatter using Drupal 7's Field Type API..Provides star rating field type and formatter</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>.Star Rating is a simple module that provides star rating field and display formatter using Drupal 7's Field Type API.It provides star rating field type and formatter

Unlike Fivestar module and other voting/rating module, it supports neither end user voting nor nice AJAX interface. It is inteded for the rating only by the author of the article (node). Of course, you may be able to do this with Fivestar module and other voting/rating modules, but unlike most of them, it does not require other modules such as voting API module. It's born to be simple but good enough for those who want star rating only by authors.

For example, if you are creating a restaurant review web site and you want to add three 5 star ratings (food, price and service) with different icon type for each rating within a node, then this module would be the best match.

Features

Very simple and no other modules required.
Utilizes Drupal 7's Field API.
Fully supports Views module.
Different icon type and color can be assigned for each field and each view mode.
(Total 16 icon type x 8 colors = 128 different icons)
Please read the enclosed README.txt for more information.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_insert_7.x-1.1" name="insert" version="7.x-1.1" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/insert/insert-7.x-1.1.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/insert/insert-7.x-1.1.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_insert_7.x-1.1/7.x-1.1/mod_insert_7.x-1.1-7.x-1.1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Insert is a utility that makes inserting images and links to files into text areas or WYSIWYGs much easier. It adds a simple JavaScript-based button to FileField and ImageField widgets. When used with ImageField and ImageCache, images may be inserted into text areas with a specific ImageCache preset.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>To Insert images and links to files into text areas or WYSIWYGs much easier. This module was previously known as FileField Insert.

Features

Support for all major WYSIWYG editors, including tinyMCE, CKeditor, the WYSIWYG project (the recommended approach), and plain text areas.
Insert images using ImageCache presets
Maximum width setting for inserted images (for combined use with the Image Resize Filter module)
Per-field insert configuration

See this module in action in the excellent FileField Insert / Image Resize Filter screencast by MustardSeed Media.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_i18n_i18n-7.x-1.0" name="i18n" version="i18n-7.x-1.0" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/i18n/i18n-7.x-1.0.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/i18n/i18n-7.x-1.0.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_i18n_i18n-7.x-1.0/i18n-7.x-1.0/mod_i18n_i18n-7.x-1.0-i18n-7.x-1.0.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:nil="true"/>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>This is a collection of modules to extend Drupal core multilingual capabilities and be able to build real life multilingual sites.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This is a collection of modules to extend Drupal core multilingual capabilities

Taxonomy translation (both, per language terms and translatable terms)
Multilingual variables
Multilingual blocks (control visibility per language and translate title and content)
Language selection (when you switch the site language you'll see only the content for that language)
Requires the Variable module (Drupal 7)
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_jquery_plugin_7.x-1.0" name="jquery_plugin" version="7.x-1.0" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/jquery_plugin/jquery_plugin-7.x-1.0.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/jquery_plugin/jquery_plugin-7.x-1.0.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_jquery_plugin_7.x-1.0/7.x-1.0/mod_jquery_plugin_7.x-1.0-7.x-1.0.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>The jquery_plugin module allows you to load miscellaneous jQuery plugins  from any module by calling the drupal_add_library() function.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module allows you to load miscellaneous jQuery plugins  from any module.

The goal of this project is to reduce the overhead of developers and site maintainers in keeping their jQuery plugins up-to-date and compatible with a given version of Drupal core. It is increasingly common for multiple Drupal modules and themes to require (or optionally use) the same jQuery plugin. So it can make sense for these components to have a dependency on one tiny module which provides the plugin. There would also be overhead (in CVS maintenance, PHP code, etc.) in having a Drupal module for each plugin, so this project bundles multiple plugins in one module.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_jquery_update_7.x-2.2" name="jquery_update" version="7.x-2.2" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/jquery_update/jquery_update-7.x-2.2.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/jquery_update/jquery_update-7.x-2.2.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_jquery_update_7.x-2.2/7.x-2.2/mod_jquery_update_7.x-2.2-7.x-2.2.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Upgrades the version of jQuery in Drupal core to a newer version of jQuery.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>It upgrades the version of jQuery in Drupal core to a newer version of jQuery.

The jquery_plugin module provides miscellaneous jQuery plugins, which can be loaded from any module or theme by calling jquery_plugin_add($plugin) in Drupal 6 or drupal_add_library('jquery_plugin', $plugin) in Drupal 7. The Drupal 6 version supports jQ, a jQuery plugin registry.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_login_destination_7.x-1.0" name="login_destination" version="7.x-1.0" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/login_destination/login_destination-7.x-1.0.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/login_destination/login_destination-7.x-1.0.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_login_destination_7.x-1.0/7.x-1.0/mod_login_destination_7.x-1.0-7.x-1.0.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>The Login Destination module allows you to customize the destination that a user is redirected to after logging in, registering to the site , using a one-time login link or logging out .</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>It allows you to customize the destination that a user is redirected to after logging in, registering to the site.

The Login Destination module allows you to customize the destination that a user is redirected to after logging in, registering to the site (7.x), using a one-time login link or logging out (7.x).

The destination can be an internal page or an external URL. It is possible to specify certain conditions like referring pages or user roles and make the destination depend upon them. You may use PHP snippets to provide custom conditions and destinations. It is also possible to keep users on the currently visited page after logging in or out.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_logintoboggan_7.x-1.2" name="logintoboggan" version="7.x-1.2" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/logintoboggan/logintoboggan-7.x-1.2.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/logintoboggan/logintoboggan-7.x-1.2.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_logintoboggan_7.x-1.2/7.x-1.2/mod_logintoboggan_7.x-1.2-7.x-1.2.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>The Login Toboggan module improves the Drupal login system in an external module by offering several features</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module improves the Drupal login system in an external module by offering several features.

Allow users to login using either their username OR their e-mail address.
Allow users to login immediately.
Provide a login form on Access Denied pages for non-logged-in (anonymous) users.
The module provides two login block options: One uses JavaScript to display the form within the block immediately upon clicking &quot;log in&quot;. The other brings the user to a separate page, but returns the user to their original page upon login.
Customize the registration form with two e-mail fields to ensure accuracy.
Optionally redirect the user to a specific page when using the 'immediate login' feature.
Optionally redirect the user to a specific page upon validation of their e-mail address.
Optionally display a user message indicating a successful login.
Optionally combine both the login and registration form on one page.
Optionally have unvalidated users purged from the system at a pre-defined interval (please read the CAVEATS section of INSTALL.txt for important information on configuring this feature!).
Integrates with Rules module to do various tasks when a user validates via email validation process (see http://drupal.org/node/880904 for an example)
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_masquerade_7.x-1.0-rc4" name="masquerade" version="7.x-1.0-rc4" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/masquerade/masquerade-7.x-1.0-rc4.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/masquerade/masquerade-7.x-1.0-rc4.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_masquerade_7.x-1.0-rc4/7.x-1.0-rc4/mod_masquerade_7.x-1.0-rc4-7.x-1.0-rc4.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>The masquerade module is designed as a tool for site designers and site administrators. It allows a user with the right permissions to switch users. While masquerading, a field is set on the $user object, and a menu item appears allowing the user to switch back. Watchdog entries are made any time a user masquerades or stops masquerading.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>The masquerade module is designed as a tool for site designers and site administrators. It allows a user with the right permissions to switch users. While masquerading, a field is set on the $user object, and a menu item appears allowing the user to switch back. Watchdog entries are made any time a user masquerades or stops masquerading.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_media_7.x-1.0-rc1" name="media" version="7.x-1.0-rc1" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/media/media-7.x-1.0-rc1.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/media/media-7.x-1.0-rc1.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_media_7.x-1.0-rc1/7.x-1.0-rc1/mod_media_7.x-1.0-rc1-7.x-1.0-rc1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_field__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_ctools_7.x-1.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_image__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_file__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>The Media module provides an extensible framework for managing files and multimedia assets, regardless of whether they are hosted on your own site or a 3rd party site - it is commonly refered to as a 'file browser to the internet'</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>The Media module provides an extensible framework for managing files and multimedia assets, regardless of whether they are hosted on your own site or a 3rd party site - it is commonly referred to as a 'file browser to the internet'.

Media is a drop-in replacement for the Drupal core upload field with a unified User Interface where editors and administrators can upload, manage, and reuse files and multimedia assets. Any files uploaded before Media was enabled will automatically take advantage of for many of the features it comes with.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_menu_admin_per_menu_7.x-1.0" name="menu_admin_per_menu" version="7.x-1.0" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/menu_admin_per_menu/menu_admin_per_menu-7.x-1.0.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/menu_admin_per_menu/menu_admin_per_menu-7.x-1.0.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_menu_admin_per_menu_7.x-1.0/7.x-1.0/mod_menu_admin_per_menu_7.x-1.0-7.x-1.0.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_menu__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Allows administrators to customize the site navigation menu.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>By default, Drupal allows only users with &quot;administrer menu permission&quot; to add, modify or delete menu items.
In case you want for instance to let certain users manage primary links or secondary links but not navigation menu, this module provides this functionality.

Installation

Copy the menu_admin_per_menu folder to your sites/all/modules directory.
Navigate to admin/build/modules and enable the module
Navigate to admin/user/permissions and set permissions for each role and each menu: &quot;administer 'menuname' menu items&quot;

If users with &quot;administer 'menuname' menu items&quot; permissions don't have the &quot;access administration pages&quot; permission,
they will not by default be able to see Navigation's &quot;Menus&quot; item (admin/build/menu).
So don't forget to move this item to the root of Navigation menu or somewhere else it can be seen by those users.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_menu_attributes_7.x-1.0-rc1" name="menu_attributes" version="7.x-1.0-rc1" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/menu_attributes/menu_attributes-7.x-1.0-rc1.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/menu_attributes/menu_attributes-7.x-1.0-rc1.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_menu_attributes_7.x-1.0-rc1/7.x-1.0-rc1/mod_menu_attributes_7.x-1.0-rc1-7.x-1.0-rc1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_menu__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>This simple module allows you to specify some additional attributes for menu items such as id, name, class, style, and rel.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module allows you to specify some additional attributes for menu items .

This simple module allows you to specify some additional attributes for menu items such as id, name, class, style, and rel.

You should use this module when

You want to &quot;nofollow&quot; certain menu items to sculpt the flow of PageRank through your site
You want to give a menu item an ID so you can easily select it using jQuery
You want to add additional classes or styles to a menu item

The module currently allows you to set the following attributes for each menu item:

Id
Name
Target
Rel
Class
Style
Accesskey
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_menu_block_7.x-2.2" name="menu_block" version="7.x-2.2" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/menu_block/menu_block-7.x-2.2.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/menu_block/menu_block-7.x-2.2.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_menu_block_7.x-2.2/7.x-2.2/mod_menu_block_7.x-2.2-7.x-2.2.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_menu__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>For menu trees that start with the 1st level, the default block title will be  the menu name. For menu trees that start with the 2nd level or deeper, the    default block title will be the title for the parent menu item of the   specified level</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>It provides configurable blocks of menu trees starting with any level of any menu.

So… have you ever used the Main and Secondary menu links feature on your theme and wondered “how the hell do I display any menu items deeper than that?”

Well, that’s what this module does. It provides configurable blocks of menu trees starting with any level of any menu. And more!

So if you’re only using your theme’s Main menu links feature, you can add and configure a “Main menu (levels 2+)” block. That block would appear once you were on one of the Main menu’s pages and would show the menu tree for the 2nd level (and deeper) of your Main menu and would expand as you traversed down the tree. You can also limit the depth of the menu’s tree (e.g. “Main menu (levels 2-3)”) and/or expand all the child sub-menus (e.g. “Main menu (expanded levels 2+)”).</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_nice_menus_7.x-2.0" name="nice_menus" version="7.x-2.0" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/nice_menus/nice_menus-7.x-2.0.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/nice_menus/nice_menus-7.x-2.0.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_nice_menus_7.x-2.0/7.x-2.0/mod_nice_menus_7.x-2.0-7.x-2.0.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Nice Menus enables drop-down/right/left expandable menus. It uses only CSS for most browsers, with minimal Javascript for IE6. (Version 2 uses the Superfish jQuery plugin for all browsers, with an option to disable JS, and falls back to CSS-only for browsers that can handle it.)</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module enables drop-down/right/left expandable menus.

Three styles/types of menus are currently possible: horizontal, menus drop down; vertical, menus fly to the left; vertical, menus fly to the right. There is a handbook page that provides a list of sites that use Nice menus.

Nice Menus creates blocks that may be associated with any existing site menu which can be placed wherever normal blocks can be placed in a theme. For themers, it is also possible to theme a menu as a Nice Menu directly by using the provided theme functions so a block is not necessary. A specific theme function for the Primary Links menu is available. The theme functions also allow a developer to pass in a custom menu tree of their making (i.e. not using a Drupal menu.) There is more information on how to use theme functions in the documentation.

The module comes with a simple, generic color scheme which can be fully overridden either by adding the override CSS to the theme's normal stylesheet or by creating a Nice Menus CSS file and telling Nice Menus to use that rather than its own default one through the global theme configuration. Several CSS override examples are provided in the included README.txt file and in the handbook.

If you are having problems with Nice Menus, make sure you read the FAQ and search the issue queue to see if others have already addressed them.

CSS Problems: Nice menus will give you easy to use, plug and play blocks with flyout menus but does require CSS work to get customized styling. CSS support issues are not supported in this issue queue and will be closed. If you have CSS styling questions, you can try asking on the forums, #drupal-themes IRC or the Themes mailing list.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_sharethis_7.x-2.2" name="sharethis" version="7.x-2.2" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/sharethis/sharethis-7.x-2.2.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/sharethis/sharethis-7.x-2.2.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_sharethis_7.x-2.2/7.x-2.2/mod_sharethis_7.x-2.2-7.x-2.2.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>This module adds the ShareThis widget to your site.The share widget (AddToAny) module by Lockerz helps readers share, bookmark, and email your pages and articles (stories) using any service, such as Facebook, Twitter, Google+, StumbleUpon, and over 100 more sharing and social bookmarking sites. Services are updated automatically.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module adds the ShareThis widget to your site.

The button comes with a customizable Smart Menu, which places the services visitors use at the top of the menu, based on each visitor's browsing and sharing history.

Drupal integration
Display on articles (stories)
Display on article (story) teasers
Display on pages
Display in blocks

Every service

Lockerz Share (AddToAny) includes every service, and lets you add custom services (using the JavaScript API) if you need to.

Emailing

The E-mail tab makes it easy to share via Gmail, Yahoo! Mail, Hotmail, AOL, and any other web-based emailer or desktop email client.

Browser bookmarking

The Bookmark or Add to Favorites button helps users bookmark using any browser (Firefox, Internet Explorer, Google Chrome, Safari, Opera etc.).

Optimized for performance

The module is optimized to load asynchronously so that all of your content loads before or at the same time as this module's assets under all circumstances. The buttons are locally hosted, and the script is minified, cached and served instantly from a world-class CDN.

Customizable

Your choice of sharing buttons come packaged with the module, including the open share icon, or you can use a button of your own like many others do.

Choose the colors of the menu using the Menu Styler
Fine-tune the styling of the menu using CSS
Customize using a powerful JavaScript API (documentation)

Localization (i18n)

The share menu has been translated into over 50 languages
Menus are automatically localized based on user's browser/OS settings
Most relevant services are displayed first based on locale
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_nodequeuequeue_7.x-1.0" name="nodequeuequeue" version="7.x-1.0" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/nodequeuequeue/nodequeuequeue-7.x-1.0.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/nodequeuequeue/nodequeuequeue-7.x-1.0.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_nodequeuequeue_7.x-1.0/7.x-1.0/mod_nodequeuequeue_7.x-1.0-7.x-1.0.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_nodequeue_7.x-2.0-beta1</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>The Nodequeue module allows users to collect nodes in an arbitrarily ordered list. The order in the list can be used for a any purpose</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>The Nodequeue module allows users to collect nodes in an arbitrarily ordered list. The order in the list can be used for a any purpose, such as:

A block listing teasers for the five top news stories on a site
A user’s favorite music albums
A group of favorite from which one is randomly displayed

Nodequeue provides a simple drag-and-drop interface to manually order any queue. Additionally, it allows nodes to be added and removed from queues without needing edit permissions to the node. Nodes can be added to queues either from a queue management tab or by links on the node teaser.

Smartqueue API

Nodequeue provides a robust API that allows other modules to define smartqueues, which are associated with external data. For example, the included taxonomy smartqueue creates subqueues for a given queue for every term in the chosen vocabulary. Nodes are then only eligible for subqueues whose term matches the nodes terms. This makes it very easy to have queues for each category without cluttering the management page.

Modules that Extend Nodequeue:

Smartqueue per-user: Makes a personal queue available to users of one or more roles.
Smartqueues for Organic Groups: Makes a queue available for ordering by members of an Organic Group or Group admins only.

Apache Solr Search Integration

The latest version of Nodequeue for Drupal 6 includes integration with Apache Solr Search, making it possible to boost nodes that are part of a queue.

Nodequeue contains an extensive API. It integrates well with Views and Actions, as well as providing a host of functions to interface with it directly, making it possible to manipulate queues programmatically for whatever purposes that are customized to your website.

Releases for 5.x and prior are unsupported at this time.

You may wish to read the comparison page for node ordering modules

Nodequeue was originally written by merlinofchaos and is maintained by ezra-g and amateescu.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_og_7.x-1.1" name="og" version="7.x-1.1" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/og/og-7.x-1.1.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/og/og-7.x-1.1.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_og_7.x-1.1/7.x-1.1/mod_og_7.x-1.1-7.x-1.1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_entity_7.x-1.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_list__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>An add-on for the Organic Groups (og) module that makes one group mandatory for all new users and/or requires new users to pick a group.
Choose one group that all new users will be put into. You can chose either an open or a closed group. Any new user will be auto-approved as member of the group. The group manager(s) of groups that a new user joins will get an automatic e-mail notice.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>An add-on for the Organic Groups (og) module that makes one group mandatory for all new users and/or requires new users to pick a group.

Enable users to create and manage their own 'groups'. Each group can have subscribers, and maintains a group home page where subscribers communicate amongst themselves.

They do so by posting the usual node types: blog, story, page, etc. A block is shown on the group home page which facilitates these posts. The block also provides summary information about the group.

Groups may be selective or not. Selective groups require approval in order to become a member, or even invitation -only groups. There are lots of preferences to configure groups as you need.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_page_title_7.x-2.5" name="page_title" version="7.x-2.5" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/page_title/page_title-7.x-2.5.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/page_title/page_title-7.x-2.5.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_page_title_7.x-2.5/7.x-2.5/mod_page_title_7.x-2.5-7.x-2.5.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_token_7.x-1.0-beta5</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>The word &quot;title&quot; is a bit overloaded. Every piece of content in Drupal has a title, and so does every page. </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module gives you granular control over the page title. 

The page title is the one found in the HTML head inside the &lt;title&gt; tag. It is also used on SERPs (Search Engine Result Pages) and can greatly enhance your websites SEO (Search Engine Optimization).

This module gives you granular control over the page title. You can specify patterns for how the title should be structured and, on content creation pages, specify the page title separately to the content's title.

Token Integration: This module integrates with the fantstic Token module. This opens up a whole world of extra stuff you can put into the page title such as the highest weighted term for a node or, in fact, any other content you'd like to shove in their via the Token API (you can even build your own TokenAPI addons to get stuff into the Page Title)! This is made even more funky when you enable the CCK module as CCK exposes field values to the Token Module.

Granular Control: Want the page title override field for the Book and Story node types, but not for Banner or Image? It's possible to enable the Page Title field for specific node types and, as a new feature, even on non-nodes too. Page titles can be set for terms and for users (since Page Title 2.1). This feature can be configured on the Admin &gt; Content &gt; Page Title page.

Token Patterns per-content type: You can configure each individual content types pattern (this applied to nodes and terms). For example: you may want a generic default pattern, however you want your forum nodes to use a different pattern (eg highest weighted term for a forum might be the board it's in). You simply set a default pattern and an overriding specific pattern for other content types, independent of whether the Page Title field is enabled for the type or not.

Other contexts... Page Title supports user profile, forum root and blog homepage contexts too. This means you could create a user with a username such as jbloggs but define the page title for user profiles and blog homepages to use a better name such as Joe Bloggs.

Pagination Suffix: One of the things you may noticed about Drupal in terms of SEO is that whenever you go through a paged list of content, the page title never changes. Google Webmaster Tools will flag this up as a problem as you essentially have several different pages all being identified with the same page title. A new feature, introduced in Page Title 2.1, is the ability to append the page number as a suffix pattern. This means any URL which contains something like page=2 in the query string will also have an optional token pattern suffixed onto the end of it. Important: for this feature to work properly, you need to be running Token 1.12 or later.

Views Integration: Paeg Title provides its own Page Display which allows you to provide a Page Title separately to the normal Title. There is also an option to provide a Page Title for each argument as well. This feature is still early and in need of testing. Feedback would be appreciated!
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_pathauto_7.x-1.0-rc2" name="pathauto" version="7.x-1.0-rc2" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/pathauto/pathauto-7.x-1.0-rc2.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/pathauto/pathauto-7.x-1.0-rc2.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_pathauto_7.x-1.0-rc2/7.x-1.0-rc2/mod_pathauto_7.x-1.0-rc2-7.x-1.0-rc2.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_path__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_token_7.x-1.0-beta5</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>The Pathauto module automatically generates path aliases for various kinds of content (nodes, categories, users) without requiring the user to manually specify the path alias. This allows you to get aliases like /category/my-node-title.html instead of /node/123. The aliases are based upon a &quot;pattern&quot; system which the administrator can control.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>The Pathauto module automatically generates path aliases for various kinds of content without requiring the user to manually specify the path alias. 

The Pathauto module automatically generates URL/path aliases for various kinds of content (nodes, taxonomy terms, users) without requiring the user to manually specify the path alias. This allows you to have URL aliases like /category/my-node-title instead of /node/123. The aliases are based upon a &quot;pattern&quot; system that uses tokens which the administrator can change.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_privatemsg_7.x-1.2" name="privatemsg" version="7.x-1.2" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/privatemsg/privatemsg-7.x-1.2.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/privatemsg/privatemsg-7.x-1.2.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_privatemsg_7.x-1.2/7.x-1.2/mod_privatemsg_7.x-1.2-7.x-1.2.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Privatemsg allows your site's visitors to send private messages to each other. Perfect for community oriented sites, such as forums and social networking sites. Many additional features are available as separate modules.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Privatemsg allows your site's visitors to send private messages to each other. Perfect for community oriented sites, such as forums and social networking sites. Many additional features are available as separate modules.

Current features

Send and receive private messages on a site (between multiple recipients)
Threaded conversations (make it easier to keep track of messages and replies)
Search private messages
Tagging and filtering (helps organise conversations)
User blocking
E-mail notifications of new messages
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_quicktabs_7.x-3.0" name="quicktabs" version="7.x-3.0" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/quicktabs/quicktabs-7.x-3.0.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/quicktabs/quicktabs-7.x-3.0.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_quicktabs_7.x-3.0/7.x-3.0/mod_quicktabs_7.x-3.0-7.x-3.0.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_ctools_7.x-1.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>This module provides a form for admins to create a block of tabbed content by selecting a view, a node, a block or an existing Quicktabs instance as the content of each tab.

The Quick Tabs module allows you to create blocks of tabbed content, specifically views, blocks, nodes* and other quicktabs*. You can create a block on your site containing multiple tabs with corresponding content. Clicking on the tabs makes the corresponding content display instantly, using jQuery. With the 6.x-2.x branch, this can be done in either ajax or non-ajax mode:
</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module provides a form for admins to create a block of tabbed content by selecting a view, a node, a block or an existing Quicktabs instance as the content of each tab.

The Quick Tabs module allows you to create blocks of tabbed content, specifically views, blocks, nodes* and other quicktabs*. You can create a block on your site containing multiple tabs with corresponding content. Clicking on the tabs makes the corresponding content display instantly, using jQuery. With the 6.x-2.x branch, this can be done in either ajax or non-ajax mode:


if you choose ajax mode for your Quick Tabs block (and this is chosen on an individual QT basis), only the content of the active tab will be loaded on page load and the content of the other tabs will be loaded via ajax on tab click (this is good for performance if you are loading, for example, several large views)

In non-ajax mode the tab content is just hidden / shown on tab-click. This latter method is an ideal way to do something like the Most Popular / Most Emailed stories tabs you see on many news websites, where it is used more as a space-saving device in your sidebar. If however, you want a QT block as the main content of your entire page, then the chances are that ajax mode will be more appropriate.

Once created, the Quick Tabs blocks show up in your block listing, ready to be configured and enabled like other blocks. Multiple Quick Tabs blocks can be placed on a single page.

For theming of the tabs, several styles have been provided for you to choose from (in the 7.x-3.x branch this functionality comes in a separate submodule, Quicktabs Tabstyles), along with the default option of no style, if you prefer to add your own theming instead.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_recaptcha_7.x-1.7" name="recaptcha" version="7.x-1.7" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/recaptcha/recaptcha-7.x-1.7.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/recaptcha/recaptcha-7.x-1.7.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_recaptcha_7.x-1.7/7.x-1.7/mod_recaptcha_7.x-1.7-7.x-1.7.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Uses the reCAPTCHA web service to improve the CAPTCHA system</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Uses the reCAPTCHA web service to improve the CAPTCHA system

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_scheduler_7.x-1.0" name="scheduler" version="7.x-1.0" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/scheduler/scheduler-7.x-1.0.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/scheduler/scheduler-7.x-1.0.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_scheduler_7.x-1.0/7.x-1.0/mod_scheduler_7.x-1.0-7.x-1.0.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>This module allows nodes to be published and unpublished on specified dates and time.

</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module allows nodes to be published and unpublished on specified dates and time.

Dates can be entered either as plain text or with Javascript calendar popups (JSCalendar in Drupal 5, Date Popup in Drupal 6).

JSCalendar is part of the JSTools module.
The Date Popup module is part of the the Date module.

Notice:

Please check if cron is running correctly if scheduler does not publish your scheduled nodes.
Scheduler does only schedule publishing and unpublishing of nodes. If you want to schedule any other activity check out Workflow, Rules and Actions.

Scheduler is the work of many people. Some of them are listed here: http://drupal.org/project/developers/3292. But there are even more: All the people who created patches but did not check them in themselfs, who posted bug or feature request and those who provided translations and documentation.

Translations to other languages than English can be found over there: http://localize.drupal.org/translate/projects/scheduler
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_search404_7.x-1.1" name="search404" version="7.x-1.1" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/search404/search404-7.x-1.1.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/search404/search404-7.x-1.1.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_search404_7.x-1.1/7.x-1.1/mod_search404_7.x-1.1-7.x-1.1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_search__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Instead of showing a standard &quot;404 Page not found&quot;, this module performs a search on the keywords in the URL.

It also includes search engine keywords detections as well as regular expression based term filtering from the URL.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module
performs a search on the keywords in the URL.

It also includes search engine keywords detections as well as regular expression based term filtering from the URL.

Features

Supports 404 Searches via Apache Solr Search Module if it is enabled
Supports searching via Google CSE, if the module is present
Supports Search by Page module as an option
Supports Lucene Search when available
Supports Lucene Did You Mean when available
Supports Xapian Search when available
Supports Fuzzy Search module as an option
Support for Custom Text and Title to be displayed in search404 pages
Option to choose between 301 and 302 redirects
Option to show side blocks when a 404 error occurs
Option to disable auto search for performance considerations and come up with the search form populated

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_site_map_7.x-1.0" name="site_map" version="7.x-1.0" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/site_map/site_map-7.x-1.0.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/site_map/site_map-7.x-1.0.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_site_map_7.x-1.0/7.x-1.0/mod_site_map_7.x-1.0-7.x-1.0.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>This module provides a site map that gives visitors an overview of your site. It can also display the RSS feeds for all blogs and categories.

Drupal generates the RSS feeds automatically but few seems to be aware that they exist.
</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module provides a site map that gives visitors an overview of your site. It can also display the RSS feeds for all blogs and categories.

Drupal generates the RSS feeds automatically but few seems to be aware that they exist.

The site map can display the following items:

A message to be displayed above the site map
The latest blogs.
Any books.
Any menus that will be displayed fully expanded.
Any categories, i.e vocabulary, with all the terms expanded. Optionally with node counts and RSS feeds.
A syndication block, the &quot;more&quot; link goes to the site map.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_site_verify_7.x-1.0" name="site_verify" version="7.x-1.0" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/site_verify/site_verify-7.x-1.0.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/site_verify/site_verify-7.x-1.0.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_site_verify_7.x-1.0/7.x-1.0/mod_site_verify_7.x-1.0-7.x-1.0.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Verifies ownership of a site for use with search engines.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>It verifies ownership of a site for use with search engines.


This module assists with the site/domain ownership authentication/verification for search engines. There are two types of verification methods supported: adding meta tags, or uploading a specific file. If you are provided with a file to upload, this module makes it easy because you can upload the file in the module's interface and the proper filename and file contents will be saved and used in the authentication process.

This module is useful for the following search engine verifications:

Google Webmaster Tools
Google Apps
Bing Webmaster Central (formerly Live Search)
Yahoo! Site Explorer
Yandex.ru
Any search engine or web service that uses META tags or file upload to verify that you are the owner of a site.

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_stringoverrides_7.x-1.8" name="stringoverrides" version="7.x-1.8" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/stringoverrides/stringoverrides-7.x-1.8.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/stringoverrides/stringoverrides-7.x-1.8.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_stringoverrides_7.x-1.8/7.x-1.8/mod_stringoverrides_7.x-1.8-7.x-1.8.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Provides a quick and easy way to replace any text on the site.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module provides a quick and easy way to replace any text on the site.

Features

Easily replace anything that's passed through t()
Locale support, allowing you to override strings in any language
Ability to import/export *.po files, for easy migration from the Locale module
Note that this is not a replacement to Locale as having thousands of overrides can cause more pain then benefit. Use this only if you need a few easy text changes.

Installation

Extract to your sites/all/modules directory.
Enable the module in admin/build/modules.
Configure the access permission in admin/user/access or admin/user/permissions.
Visit admin/settings/stringoverrides and fill in the strings you'd like to replace.
Dance (if you arn't dancing, then try emptying your cache)!

Credits

This module was written by Rob Loach, however, the idea came from the Lullabot team when they mentioned someone should put a module together that takes advantage of the new functionality in Drupal 6. Jeff Eaton suggested the name Swappy, but String Overrides was a bit more descriptive. Nathan Haug gets the credit for producing the brilliant Drupal 5 backport. Thank you goes to John VanDyk for usability enhancements. Pasqualle was a major help with the Drupal 7 port.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_superfish_7.x-1.8" name="superfish" version="7.x-1.8" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/superfish/superfish-7.x-1.8.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/superfish/superfish-7.x-1.8.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_superfish_7.x-1.8/7.x-1.8/mod_superfish_7.x-1.8-7.x-1.8.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_menu__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>jQuery Superfish plugin for your Drupal menus.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>jQuery Superfish plugin for your Drupal menus.


Overview:

Supporting all the Superfish options.
Block-specific settings.
Unobtrusive JavaScript.
Supersubs plug-in.
Supposition plug-in.
Touchscreen compatible (for iPad, Android, etc.)
Accessible. (Keyboard-accessible, screen reader compatible)
Multi-column sub-menus. (Megamenus)
RTL (Right-to-left) language support.
Lots of built-in options for designers.
And a whole lot more...
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_swfembed_7.x-1.4" name="swfembed" version="7.x-1.4" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/swfembed/swfembed-7.x-1.4.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/swfembed/swfembed-7.x-1.4.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_swfembed_7.x-1.4/7.x-1.4/mod_swfembed_7.x-1.4-7.x-1.4.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>SWF Embed is a simple developer-centered module for working with Macromedia Flash-based content. It provides the necessary hooks for adding Flash content on the server-side, as well as the necessary JavaScript and jQuery for working with the Flash on the client-side.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>SWF Embed is a simple developer-centered module for working with Macromedia Flash-based content. It provides the necessary hooks for adding Flash content on the server-side, as well as the necessary JavaScript and jQuery for working with the Flash on the client-side.

Developers, get started by reading the SWF Embed Handbook Page. The handbook walks you through the process of using SWF Embed in your own code.

For an example of SWF Embed in action, see the Flashy movie player, a 100% open source video player for Drupal.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_comicdrop_7.x-1.5" name="comicdrop" version="7.x-1.5" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/comicdrop/comicdrop-7.x-1.5.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/comicdrop/comicdrop-7.x-1.5.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_comicdrop_7.x-1.5/7.x-1.5/mod_comicdrop_7.x-1.5-7.x-1.5.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_field__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_image__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Comicdrop is a single stop module designed to create and manage a set of features to support the webcomic use case.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>It is a single stop module designed to create and manage a set of features to support the webcomic use case.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_spritesheets_7.x-1.0" name="spritesheets" version="7.x-1.0" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/spritesheets/spritesheets-7.x-1.0.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/spritesheets/spritesheets-7.x-1.0.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_spritesheets_7.x-1.0/7.x-1.0/mod_spritesheets_7.x-1.0-7.x-1.0.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Automatically consolidate images and icons into a single image to cut down on http requests</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Automatically consolidate images and icons into a single image to cut down on http requests.


An easy way to optimize css background images into sprite sheets.

Spritesheets is a module that will optimize css background images in themes and modules on to one image asset. You have the ability to configure which directories Spritesheets module will search, and it will parse your CSS to find images that can be included on a spritesheet. You can then configure which images should be optimized to a spritesheet. Spritesheets can greatly reduce page load time, bandwidth, and the tax on your server by combining
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_views_7.x-3.0-rc1" name="views" version="7.x-3.0-rc1" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/views/views-7.x-3.0-rc1.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/views/views-7.x-3.0-rc1.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_views_7.x-3.0-rc1/7.x-3.0-rc1/mod_views_7.x-3.0-rc1-7.x-3.0-rc1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_ctools_7.x-1.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>The Views module provides a flexible method for Drupal site designers to control how lists and tables of content (nodes in Views 1, almost anything in Views 2) are presented. Traditionally, Drupal has hard-coded most of this, particularly in how taxonomy and tracker lists are formatted.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module provides a flexible method for Drupal site designers to control how lists and tables of content are presented. 

When installing Views on Drupal 7, you should have the current stable version of CTools (currently rc1) and you may need to flush cache as much as twice. There are currently issues with core's cache flushing that means one cache flush isn't necessarily enough.
What is Views

The Views module provides a flexible method for Drupal site designers to control how lists and tables of content (nodes in Views 1, almost anything in Views 2) are presented. Traditionally, Drupal has hard-coded most of this, particularly in how taxonomy and tracker lists are formatted.

This tool is essentially a smart query builder that, given enough information, can build the proper query, execute it, and display the results. It has four modes, plus a special mode, and provides an impressive amount of functionality from these modes.

Among other things, Views can be used to generate reports, create summaries, and display collections of images and other content.
You need Views if

You like the default front page view, but you find you want to sort it differently.
You like the default taxonomy/term view, but you find you want to sort it differently; for example, alphabetically.
You use /tracker, but you want to restrict it to posts of a certain type.
You like the idea of the 'article' module, but it doesn't display articles the way you like.
You want a way to display a block with the 5 most recent posts of some particular type.
You want to provide 'unread forum posts'.
You want a monthly archive similar to the typical Movable Type/Wordpress archives that displays a link to the in the form of &quot;Month, YYYY (X)&quot; where X is the number of posts that month, and displays them in a block. The links lead to a simple list of posts for that month. 

Views can do a lot more than that, but those are some of the obvious uses of Views.
Dependencies

The Drupal 7 version of Views requires the Chaos Tool Suite also known as CTools.
Views' bug squad

The Views' bug squad is a group of people who have dedicated a few hours a week to help provide support and fix bugs in the issue queue. They are the first line for answering questions and properly filing issues. Anyone who wishes to join the Bug Squad to help others may do so to help contribute to the Drupal community!
Views documentation

Views 1
Views 2 (This link goes to the Advanced Help project page. All Views documentation is included with its installation. For your convenience, you may also visit http://views-help.doc.logrus.com. This site may or may not be fully up to date at any given time.)
Views 2 API (doxygen generated from Views 2 source. Only useful to developers.)
Views 3 documentation hasn't been written yet. Items of note are:
Only UID1 can import a View.

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_votingapi_7.x-2.4" name="votingapi" version="7.x-2.4" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/votingapi/votingapi-7.x-2.4.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/votingapi/votingapi-7.x-2.4.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_votingapi_7.x-2.4/7.x-2.4/mod_votingapi_7.x-2.4-7.x-2.4.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>VotingAPI is a framework for content voting and rating systems in Drupal. It does not directly provide any voting 'features' to users -- instead, it offers a consistent API for other module developers to build their voting and rating systems on top of. If you're an end user who just wants to rate nodes, check out some of the modules that use VotingAPI's framework:
</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>VotingAPI is a framework for content voting and rating systems in Drupal. 

VotingAPI helps developers who want to use a standardized API and schema for storing, retrieving, and tabulating votes for Drupal content.

Among other things, it supports:

Rating of any content (comments, nodes, users, fish, whatever)
Multi-criteria voting (rate a game based on video, audio, and replayability)
Automatic tabulation of results (with support for different voting styles, like 'percentage' and '+1/-1')
Efficient caching of results (sorting and filtering doesn't require any recalculation)
Hooks for additional vote calculations

Note that this module does NOT directly expose any voting mechanisms to end users. It's a framework designed to make life easier for other developers, and to standardize voting data for consumption by other modules (like Views).

For some examples of simple voting systems based on VotingAPI, check Is Useful, Fivestar, and Plus1.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_webform_7.x-3.13" name="webform" version="7.x-3.13" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/webform/webform-7.x-3.13.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/webform/webform-7.x-3.13.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_webform_7.x-3.13/7.x-3.13/mod_webform_7.x-3.13-7.x-3.13.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Webform is the module for making surveys in Drupal. After a submission, users may be sent an e-mail &quot;receipt&quot; as well as sending a notification to administrators.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Webform is the module for making surveys in Drupal. 

Webform is the module for making surveys in Drupal. After a submission, users may be sent an e-mail &quot;receipt&quot; as well as sending a notification to administrators. Results can be exported into Excel or other spreadsheet applications. Webform also provides some basic statistical review and has and extensive API for expanding its features.

Some good examples could be contests, personalized contact forms, or petitions. Each of these could have a customized form for end-users to fill out. If you need to build a lot of customized, one-off forms, Webform is a more suitable solution than creating content types and using CCK or Field module. </content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_wysiwyg_7.x-2.1" name="wysiwyg" version="7.x-2.1" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/wysiwyg/wysiwyg-7.x-2.1.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/wysiwyg/wysiwyg-7.x-2.1.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_wysiwyg_7.x-2.1/7.x-2.1/mod_wysiwyg_7.x-2.1-7.x-2.1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Allows to use client-side editors to edit content. It simplifies the This module replaces all other editor integration modules. No other Drupal module is required.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Allows to use client-side editors to edit content.

It simplifies the installation and integration of the editor of your choice. This module replaces all other editor integration modules. No other Drupal module is required.

Wysiwyg module is capable to support any kind of client-side editor. It can be a HTML-editor (a.k.a. WYSIWYG), a &quot;pseudo-editor&quot; (buttons to insert markup into a textarea), or even Flash-based applications. The editor library needs to be downloaded separately. Various editors are supported (see below).

Wysiwyg module also provides an abstraction layer for other Drupal modules to integrate with any editor. This means that other Drupal modules can expose content-editing functionality, regardless of which editor you have installed.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_antispam_7.x-1.1" name="antispam" version="7.x-1.1" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/antispam/antispam-7.x-1.1.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/antispam/antispam-7.x-1.1.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_antispam_7.x-1.1/7.x-1.1/mod_antispam_7.x-1.1-7.x-1.1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>It provides spam protection to your drupal site using external antispam service like Akismet. </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>It provides spam protection to your drupal site using external antispam service like Akismet. 

AntiSpam module is the successor of the Akismet module, and it provides spam protection to your drupal site using external antispam service like Akismet.

AntiSpam module is fully compatible with Drupal 6.x (Akismet module for Drupal 6.x release had many compatibility issues and was not usable as it was), and it expanded the support of the external antispam service with TypePad AntiSpam and Defensio service as well as Akismet service. Now you can choose one of the antispam service you wish to use.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_mollom_7.x-1.1" name="mollom" version="7.x-1.1" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/mollom/mollom-7.x-1.1.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/mollom/mollom-7.x-1.1.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_mollom_7.x-1.1/7.x-1.1/mod_mollom_7.x-1.1-7.x-1.1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Mollom handles incoming posts intelligently, in much the same way a human moderator decides what posts are acceptable. Therefore, Mollom enables you to allow anonymous users to post comments and other content on your site.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Mollom handles incoming posts intelligently, in much the same way a human moderator decides what posts are acceptable.

Mollom is in a unique position to determine if a post is potentially spam; not only based on the posted content, but also on the past activity and reputation of the poster. In short, Mollom handles incoming posts intelligently, in much the same way a human moderator decides what posts are acceptable. Therefore, Mollom enables you to allow anonymous users to post comments and other content on your site.

How it works

Mollom may block a post outright if it is from a known spammer. If Mollom is unsure how to classify a post, it may require the completion of a CAPTCHA to accept the post. Posts that do not match a &quot;spammy&quot; text pattern and do not originate from known spammers are accepted without the need to complete a CAPTCHA. Essentially, Mollom acts as a proactive content moderator that is on the job 24 hours a day, 7 days a week.

A stand-alone CAPTCHA solution, which neither considers user behavior nor point of origin, can never achieve this level of informed protection, and generally requires users to solve a CAPTCHA on every post. Using Mollom's text analysis, users must only solve CAPTCHAs when Mollom is unsure about a post.

The Mollom module allows other modules to integrate their forms with Mollom. Forms exposed by Drupal core, including the user registration and comment forms, are supported by default.

Mollom is actively developed and maintained by Dries Buytaert, the founder and project lead of Drupal, and Benjamin Schrauwen. Mollom is currently used by more than 30,000 sites, including Sony, Adobe, LinuxJournal, Warner Bros Records, Netlog, NBC, and others. As of September, 2010, Mollom currently protects over 30,000 websites with an average efficiency rate of 99.93% - which means that only 7 in 10,000 spam messages are not routinely caught by Mollom's filters. Since Mollom began operating, it has prevented almost 300 million spam posts from littering the web.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_addthis_7.x-2.1-beta1" name="addthis" version="7.x-2.1-beta1" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/addthis/addthis-7.x-2.1-beta1.zip" artifactId="modules/addthis/addthis-7.x-2.1-beta1.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_addthis_7.x-2.1-beta1/7.x-2.1-beta1/mod_addthis_7.x-2.1-beta1-7.x-2.1-beta1.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Creates AddThis button as a block, to be used in themes and to node links.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>It creates AddThis button as a block, to be used in themes and to node links.

AddThis is the #1 bookmarking and sharing button on the Internet. AddThis has become the standard button for bookmarking and sharing. The AddThis button spreads your content across the Web by making it easier for your visitors to bookmark and share it with other people, again…and again…and again. This simple yet powerful button is very easy to install and provides valuable Analytics about the bookmarking and sharing activity of your users. AddThis helps your visitors create a buzz for your site and increase its popularity and ranking. (source: addthis.com)


</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_adsense_7.x-1.x-dev" name="adsense" version="7.x-1.x-dev" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/adsense/adsense-7.x-1.x-dev.zip" artifactId="modules/adsense/adsense-7.x-1.x-dev.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_adsense_7.x-1.x-dev/7.x-1.x-dev/mod_adsense_7.x-1.x-dev-7.x-1.x-dev.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Displays Google AdSense ads on your site to earn revenue. Requires at least one additional ad unit generator module.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module displays Google AdSense ads.

This module provides web content providers with the means to earn revenue from visitors by displaying ads from Google AdSense™ advertising service on their sites.

Why should you use it:

AdSense for Search and Drupal are incompatible as both use the 'q' query for different purposes. Using this module, you can display the search results in your site.
Protects you from displaying more ads in a page than the maximum allowed by Google
The module provides easy-to-use ad blocks.
You can easily disable the ads for certain roles.
Provides simple controls for troubleshooting the ads before going live with the site.
If Google changes some minor details in the script in , your script can be updated site-wide just by upgrading the module.
If you want to do ad revenue sharing, there's really no other option

Why shouldn't you use it:

Strictly speaking, this module is not in compliance with the AdSense TOS, since you're not exactly copy-pasting the script code in your site. No one has ever reported being banned because of using this module, and Google knows of its existence, and seem not to mind.

The module is composed by the following sub-modules:

AdSense core: Common module stuff. Required, but useless without an ad generator module.
Managed ads: Ad generator that produces the same ad script code as currently generated by Google.
CSE Search: Generates a Custom Search Engine form and the results page.
Ads (old): Ad generator using the old script generated by Google upto 2008, but which is still supported by Google for displaying ads.
Search (old): Generates a Search form and the results page using the old method which allowed the user to select the domain being searched.
Revenue sharing (old): Enables the site owner to share the revenue between page authors in a configurable percentage. Only works with the old ad generator modules.
Click Tracking: tries to track clicks on the displayed ads, usually failing to do so.

The module provides an API for selecting the publisher ID to be used to display ads.

Please read the README.txt that is included in the module for more details.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_advanced_forum_7.x-2.0-beta1" name="advanced_forum" version="7.x-2.0-beta1" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/advanced_forum/advanced_forum-7.x-2.0-beta1.zip" artifactId="modules/advanced_forum/advanced_forum-7.x-2.0-beta1.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_advanced_forum_7.x-2.0-beta1/7.x-2.0-beta1/mod_advanced_forum_7.x-2.0-beta1-7.x-2.0-beta1.zip</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_forum__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_taxonomy__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_options__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_comment__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_options__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_ctools_7.x-1.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_views_7.x-3.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Enables the look and feel of other popular forum software.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>It enables the look and feel of other popular forum software.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_advanced_help_7.x-1.0" name="advanced_help" version="7.x-1.0" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/advanced_help/advanced_help-7.x-1.0.zip" artifactId="modules/advanced_help/advanced_help-7.x-1.0.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_advanced_help_7.x-1.0/7.x-1.0/mod_advanced_help_7.x-1.0-7.x-1.0.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>The advanced help module allows module developers to store their help outside the module system, in pure .html files. The files can be easily translated simply by copying them into the right translations directory. The entire system can appear in a popup or not as the module prefers (and by taking away access to view the popups, a site can force the popups to not exist).</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>The advanced help module allows module developers to store their help outside the module system, in pure .html files. The files can be easily translated simply by copying them into the right translations directory. The entire system can appear in a popup or not as the module prefers (and by taking away access to view the popups, a site can force the popups to not exist).

The system ties into Drupal's search system and is fully indexed, so the entire contents can be searched for keywords. the help files can be placed in a hierarchy as well, allowing for top down navigation of the help.

By itself, this module doesn't do much; it requires another module to support it, but it does come with a nice little sample of text from Wikipedia to demonstrate the system.
Accessing Advanced_help

When this module is installed, users with the view advanced help index permission can access the advanced help index by going to Administer -&gt; Advanced Help (http://www.example.com/admin/advanced_help). Additional view advanced help popup and view advanced help topic permissions enable them to access the actual help pages and popups.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_author_pane_7.x-2.0-alpha1" name="author_pane" version="7.x-2.0-alpha1" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/author_pane/author_pane-7.x-2.0-alpha1.zip" artifactId="modules/author_pane/author_pane-7.x-2.0-alpha1.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_author_pane_7.x-2.0-alpha1/7.x-2.0-alpha1/mod_author_pane_7.x-2.0-alpha1-7.x-2.0-alpha1.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Gathers information from core and user related contrib modules and displays it in a template.

Author Pane is a block of information about a given user, like those typically found on a forum post, but can be used in other places as well. From core, it collects the user picture, name, join date, online status, contact link, and profile information. In addition, any module or theme can feed it more information via the preprocess system. All of this information is then gathered and displayed using a template file.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>It gathers information from core and user related contrib modules and displays it in a template.

Author Pane is a block of information about a given user, like those typically found on a forum post, but can be used in other places as well. From core, it collects the user picture, name, join date, online status, contact link, and profile information. In addition, any module or theme can feed it more information via the preprocess system. All of this information is then gathered and displayed using a template file.

Module integrations:

The following modules will automatically add information to Author Pane when enabled. Some of these integrations are included in the Author Pane project while others are included in the individual projects. More integrations can be added as explained here Non-core integrations are not supported and may be removed if they break and no one is willing to supply a patch.

Contact*
Facebook-style Statuses
Fast Toggle*
Organic Groups*
Privatemsg 1.4 (or later) (Untested against 2.x so YMMV.)
Profile
QTChat
Troll*
User Badges*
User Relationships
User Stats
User Titles* (text version by default; image version must be added to template)
Userpoints*
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_custom_pagers_7.x-1.x-dev" name="custom_pagers" version="7.x-1.x-dev" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/custom_pagers/custom_pagers-7.x-1.x-dev.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/custom_pagers/custom_pagers-7.x-1.x-dev.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_custom_pagers_7.x-1.x-dev/7.x-1.x-dev/mod_custom_pagers_7.x-1.x-dev-7.x-1.x-dev.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Allows administrators to define custom pagers for navigation in lists of nodes.

Custom Pagers allows administrators to define context-sensitive previous/next pagers for any node type. The list of nodes to be cycled through is generated by a user-selectable view, and each pager can be displayed above or below the node body or in a sidebar block. This makes it possible to duplicate the paging functions of forum.module and book.module, as well as more complex stuff like comic strip navigation. Requires token.module and views.module.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>It allows administrators to define custom pagers for navigation in lists of nodes.

Custom Pagers allows administrators to define context-sensitive previous/next pagers for any node type. The list of nodes to be cycled through is generated by a user-selectable view, and each pager can be displayed above or below the node body or in a sidebar block. This makes it possible to duplicate the paging functions of forum.module and book.module, as well as more complex stuff like comic strip navigation. Requires token.module and views.module.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_boost_7.x-1.x-dev" name="boost" version="7.x-1.x-dev" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/boost/boost-7.x-1.x-dev.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/boost/boost-7.x-1.x-dev.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_boost_7.x-1.x-dev/7.x-1.x-dev/mod_boost_7.x-1.x-dev-7.x-1.x-dev.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Boost provides static page caching for Drupal enabling a very significant performance and scalability boost for sites that receive mostly anonymous traffic.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module  provides static page caching for Drupal enabling a very significant performance and scalability boost for sites that receive mostly anonymous traffic.

Boost is very easy to install and has been throughly tested on Shared, VPS and Dedicated hosting. Apache is fully supported, with Nginx, Lighttpd and IIS 7 semi-supported. Boost will cache &amp; gzip compress html, xml, ajax, css, &amp; javascript. Boosts cache expiration logic is very advanced; it's fairly simple to have different cache lifetimes for different parts of your site. The built in crawler makes sure expired content is quickly regenerated for fast page loading. For shared hosting this is your best option in terms of improving performance.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_calendar_7.x-3.0-alpha1" name="calendar" version="7.x-3.0-alpha1" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/calendar/calendar-7.x-3.0-alpha1.zip" artifactId="modules/calendar/calendar-7.x-3.0-alpha1.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_calendar_7.x-3.0-alpha1/7.x-3.0-alpha1/mod_calendar_7.x-3.0-alpha1-7.x-3.0-alpha1.zip</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_views_7.x-3.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_ctools_7.x-1.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_date_7.x-2.0-alpha4</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Views plugin to display views containing dates as Calendars.

This module will display any Views date field in calendar formats, including CCK date fields, node created or updated dates, etc. Switch between year, month, and day views. Back and next navigation is provided for all views. </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Views plugin to display views containing dates as Calendars.

This module will display any Views date field in calendar formats, including CCK date fields, node created or updated dates, etc. Switch between year, month, and day views. Back and next navigation is provided for all views. 

Lots of the Calendar functionality comes from the Date module, so any time you update the Calendar module you should be sure you also update to the latest version of the Date module at the same time.

See also Date iCal, a project that will contain code and features needed to either import or export dates using iCal feeds.

Be sure to read Debugging Information before reporting a problem. Going through those steps may resolve your problems and will help provide enough information to tell if this is a bug.
D7 Version
D7 Notes

New Method For Creating Calendars! The previously-recommended method of creating calendars was to clone the default calendar view provided by this module. This caused lots of problems because the default view had to use a known date field so ends up being a view of every node on the site, a potential performance issue. Plus you had to find and change every place that field was used to switch to the date field you actually want. The new method is to create new calendars from a template. You'll see an 'Add view from template' option at the top of the list of Views. Select that and you'll find a template for every date field that the Date API can manage which will create a calendar specific to that date field.

I just added a new row plugin to the 7.3 version of Calendar that should work with any entity, not just nodes. The old plugin has been marked as deprecated and will be removed in the final release, so please update your views to use the new plugin, 'Calendar Entities'.

The Calendar iCal module is being deprecated in favor of Date iCal. This will be marked as deprecated and hidden as much as possible until it is safe to completely remove it.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_captcha_7.x-1.0-alpha3" name="captcha" version="7.x-1.0-alpha3" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/captcha/captcha-7.x-1.0-alpha3.zip" artifactId="modules/captcha/captcha-7.x-1.0-alpha3.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_captcha_7.x-1.0-alpha3/7.x-1.0-alpha3/mod_captcha_7.x-1.0-alpha3-7.x-1.0-alpha3.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Base CAPTCHA module for adding challenges to arbitrary forms.

A CAPTCHA is a challenge-response test most often placed within web forms to determine whether the user is human.
</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Base CAPTCHA module for adding challenges to arbitrary forms.

A CAPTCHA is a challenge-response test most often placed within web forms to determine whether the user is human. The purpose of CAPTCHA is to block form submissions by spambots, which are automated scripts that post spam content everywhere they can. The CAPTCHA module provides this feature to virtually any user facing web form on a Drupal site. </content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_computed_field_7.x-1.x-dev" name="computed_field" version="7.x-1.x-dev" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/computed_field/computed_field-7.x-1.x-dev.zip" artifactId="modules/computed_field/computed_field-7.x-1.x-dev.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_computed_field_7.x-1.x-dev/7.x-1.x-dev/mod_computed_field_7.x-1.x-dev-7.x-1.x-dev.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Defines a field type that allows values to be &quot;computed&quot; via PHP code.

Computed Field is a very powerful CCK field module that lets you add a custom &quot;computed fields&quot; to your content types.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module defines a field type that allows values to be &quot;computed&quot; via PHP code.

Computed Field is a very powerful CCK field module that lets you add a custom &quot;computed fields&quot; to your content types.


These computed fields are populated with values that you define via PHP code. You may draw on anything available to Drupal, including other fields, the current user, database tables, you name it. (Feeling the power yet? :) ) You can also choose whether to store your computed field values in the database with other content fields, or have them &quot;calculated&quot; on the fly during node views. (Although you should note that Views use requires database stored values.) This field is literally the Swiss Army knife of CCK fields. So start cooking up your PHP based values!
Important

This module is intended to be used by PHP developers to insert &amp; execute PHP code on a Drupal website. It does not provide a macro interface, a code builder or anything other than insert your working code here into this text area. You need to have a good working knowledge of PHP and the Drupal API to use this module. To get the best results with this module, pre-test your PHP code in the Body field of a Page in Drupal.

Please do not post questions to the issue queue asking for unpaid help with your specific PHP code snippet. They will generally be ignored or closed. Use Computed Field code snippets for code examples and seeking assistance. If you have another useful (or instructive) example please add it to the manual pages, and if you'd like to help with support, please answer support questions over there.

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_cck_7.x-2.x-dev" name="cck" version="7.x-2.x-dev" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/cck/cck-7.x-2.x-dev.zip" artifactId="modules/cck/cck-7.x-2.x-dev.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_cck_7.x-2.x-dev/7.x-2.x-dev/mod_cck_7.x-2.x-dev-7.x-2.x-dev.zip</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_field__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_ui__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Miscellaneous field functions not handled by core.



</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>The Content Construction Kit allows you to add custom fields to nodes using a web browser.

The Content Construction Kit allows you to add custom fields to nodes using a web browser.
Drupal 7 and Fields in Core

Most of CCK has moved to core in the Drupal 7 version.

Please note that this is not the place to get support for D7 Fields! We are getting a number of support requests, bug reports, and even feature requests for D7 fields. Fields are in core in D7, you must file issues there, not here.

The D7 version of the contrib CCK package currently contains:

D6 -&gt; D7 data migration code, see Migrating D6 Content Construction Kit (CCK) to D7 Fields for an explanation of how to upgrade your data.
some miscellaneous helpers to do things that core will not do, like maintain the PHP code snippets some fields may have been using to define allowed values (partially working)

The following features are now handled by separate, dedicated projects:

nodereference and userreference : References project - co-maintainer needed
content_permissions: Field permissions module. See this issue for progress on the D7 version.
fieldgroup : Field group module - with much more awesomeness than in D6 !
content_copy: Either use Bundle copy or the Features module which supports exporting and importing content types and fields in 'feature' modules. 

Integration with other modules:

Views - all Views field integration is handled by Views in D7.
Panels - all Panels field integration is handled by Panels in D7.
Token - see the D7 version of the Token module.
Devel - the Devel module will handle field generation code in D7.

Everything else is in Drupal 7 core.
CCK Resources

CCK is a very powerful system with many different contributed modules to extend its functionality. Install the Advanced Help module for additional help, and use the Views module to display CCK information in a variety of ways.

Here are a few other comprehensive documentation and tutorial resources to help get you started:

Text: The CCK Handbook on Drupal.org
Text: CCK Module basics tutorial
Video: Adding Fields With CCK video
Video: CCK &amp; Views Tutorial (for Drupal 5)
DVD: Learning CCK in-depth training by Lullabot
Book: Using Drupal O'Reilly covers CCK with lots of examples
Video: Karen Stevenson's CCK Presentation at the Do It With Drupal Seminar (paid access) </content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_custom_breadcrumbs_7.x-1.0-alpha1" name="custom_breadcrumbs" version="7.x-1.0-alpha1" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/custom_breadcrumbs/custom_breadcrumbs-7.x-1.0-alpha1.zip" artifactId="modules/custom_breadcrumbs/custom_breadcrumbs-7.x-1.0-alpha1.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_custom_breadcrumbs_7.x-1.0-alpha1/7.x-1.0-alpha1/mod_custom_breadcrumbs_7.x-1.0-alpha1-7.x-1.0-alpha1.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Allows administrators to define custom breadcrumb trails for node types.

This allows CCK-style node types to have &quot;Home &gt; User Blog &gt; 2005 &gt; January&quot; style breadcrumbs on the node view page itself, synchronizing cleanly with custom views or pathauto aliases. Breadcrumb visibility can be customized via a php snippet.

No new features are planned for these versions, but they are still supported and bug reports are encouraged.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>It Allows administrators to define custom breadcrumb trails for node types.

This allows CCK-style node types to have &quot;Home &gt; User Blog &gt; 2005 &gt; January&quot; style breadcrumbs on the node view page itself, synchronizing cleanly with custom views or pathauto aliases. Breadcrumb visibility can be customized via a php snippet.

No new features are planned for these versions, but they are still supported and bug reports are encouraged.

Many new features have been added to the 6.x-2.x branch including support for views, panels, taxonomy vocabularies and terms, paths, and a simple API that allows contributed modules to enable custom breadcrumbs for module pages and theme templates. These are implemented using optional, independent submodules that depend on the main custom breadcrumbs module.

In addition to breadcrumb visibility, this version provides an option that permits php code snippets to be used to form the breadcrumb titles and paths. Multiple languages are also supported.

The first release candidate of Custom breadcrumbs 2 is now available for testing. Additional feature requests can be considered for a future release, but the focus is now on working out any remaining bugs.

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_date_7.x-2.0-alpha4" name="date" version="7.x-2.0-alpha4" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/date/date-7.x-2.0-alpha4.zip" artifactId="modules/date/date-7.x-2.0-alpha4.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_date_7.x-2.0-alpha4/7.x-2.0-alpha4/mod_date_7.x-2.0-alpha4-7.x-2.0-alpha4.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>A Date API that can be used by other modules.Makes date/time fields available.

This package contains both a flexible date/time field type Date field and a Date API that other modules can use.

The D5 and D6 versions of the Date field require the Content Construction Kit (CCK) module. The D7 version works with the core Field functionality.

The Drupal Handbook pages are at Date/Calendar Documentation.

Be sure to read Debugging Information before reporting a problem. Going through those steps may resolve your problems and will help provide enough information to tell if this is a bug.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>A Date API that can be used by other modules.Makes date/time fields available.

This package contains both a flexible date/time field type Date field and a Date API that other modules can use.

The D5 and D6 versions of the Date field require the Content Construction Kit (CCK) module. The D7 version works with the core Field functionality.

The Drupal Handbook pages are at Date/Calendar Documentation.

Be sure to read Debugging Information before reporting a problem. Going through those steps may resolve your problems and will help provide enough information to tell if this is a bug.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_dhtml_menu_7.x-1.0-beta1" name="dhtml_menu" version="7.x-1.0-beta1" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/dhtml_menu/dhtml_menu-7.x-1.0-beta1.zip" artifactId="modules/dhtml_menu/dhtml_menu-7.x-1.0-beta1.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_dhtml_menu_7.x-1.0-beta1/7.x-1.0-beta1/mod_dhtml_menu_7.x-1.0-beta1-7.x-1.0-beta1.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Opens menus dynamically to reduce page reloads.

DHTML Menu uses Javascript to reduce the number of page loads when using nested menus; this is particularly useful with Drupal's administration system.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Opens menus dynamically to reduce page reloads.

DHTML Menu uses Javascript to reduce the number of page loads when using nested menus; this is particularly useful with Drupal's administration system.

Ordinarily in Drupal, in order to see the sub-items in a menu, you need to click the link of this item and wait for a full page load. After enabling DHTML Menu, clicking a menu link once will expand it to reveal its sub-items without reloading the page. A double-click on the item will load the page normally. Additionally, a cookie stores which menus are open and which are closed, so that the state of the menus remain consistent as you navigate around the site.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_media_embedded_7.x-1.0-beta3" name="media_embedded" version="7.x-1.0-beta3" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/media_embedded/media_embedded-7.x-1.0-beta3.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/media_embedded/media_embedded-7.x-1.0-beta3.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_media_embedded_7.x-1.0-beta3/7.x-1.0-beta3/mod_media_embedded_7.x-1.0-beta3-7.x-1.0-beta3.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_media_7.x-1.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Adds links from a text field as media files into the media field.

This extensible module will create fields for content types that can be used to display video, image, and audio files from various third party providers. When entering the content, the user will simply paste the URL or embed code from the third party, and the module will automatically determine which content provider is being used. When displaying the content, the proper embedding format will be used.
</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Adds links from a text field as media files into the media field.

This extensible module will create fields for content types that can be used to display video, image, and audio files from various third party providers. When entering the content, the user will simply paste the URL or embed code from the third party, and the module will automatically determine which content provider is being used. When displaying the content, the proper embedding format will be used.

The module is only an engine, and requires a supported module to function. These include 'Embedded Image Field', 'Embedded Video Field' and 'Embedded Audio Field'. These modules are included in the contrib folder of the module, so they can be easily activated from the module administration page.

Please note: As of emfield 2.x, provider files for these modules are no longer included with the main emfield module, and must be downloaded separately- please see the list of projects providing provider files below.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_entity_7.x-1.0-rc1" name="entity" version="7.x-1.0-rc1" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/entity/entity-7.x-1.0-rc1.zip" artifactId="modules/entity/entity-7.x-1.0-rc1.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_entity_7.x-1.0-rc1/7.x-1.0-rc1/mod_entity_7.x-1.0-rc1-7.x-1.0-rc1.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Enables modules to work with any entity type and to provide entities.

This module extends the entity API of Drupal core in order to provide a unified way to deal with entities and their properties. Additionally, it provides an entity CRUD controller, which helps simplifying the creation of new entity types.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>It enables modules to work with any entity type and to provide entities.

This module extends the entity API of Drupal core in order to provide a unified way to deal with entities and their properties. Additionally, it provides an entity CRUD controller, which helps simplifying the creation of new entity types.

Features

This is an API module, so it doesn't provide any end-user features. However, users may enable the entity tokens module, which provides token replacements for all entity properties that have no tokens and are known to the entity API.

Overview

The module provides API functions allowing modules to create, save, delete, view or to determine access for any entity, i.e. entity_create(), entity_save(), entity_delete(), entity_view() and entity_access().

The entity API introduces a unique place for metadata about entity relationships and entity properties: hook_entity_property_info(). This information about entity properties contains the data type and callbacks for how to get and set the data of a property. Modules may rely on this information in order to support any entity property, e.g. Rules and the Search API build upon that.

Furthermore the module provides data wrappers that make use of the available information to provide a simple and unified access to entities and their properties. For usage examples have a look at the README or the provided tests.

Beside that, the module helps you defining a new entity type. For that, it provides an entity controller, which implements full CRUD functionality for your entities. Optionally, entities may be created based on classes derived from the provided Entity class.

The entity API cares about creating fieldable entities as well as exportable entities, however it does not yet support revisions. Additionally it supports implementing bundle entities, i.e. bundle objects (like node types) for fieldable entities implemented as (exportable) entities, for which the appropriate field API callbacks get automatically invoked.

For entity types implemented based upon the provided CRUD API the API is providing additional module integration too, i.e. Rules events are provided for all CRUD-related hooks, some basic entity property information for hook_entity_property_info() is provided and exportable entities are automatically integrated with the Features module.

These module integrations are implemented in separate controller classes, which may be separately overridden or enabled/deactivated.
Optionally, the entity API also helps providing an administrative interface for managing entities, e.g. the UI for managing profile types of Profile 2 is built with that.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_features_7.x-1.0-beta4" name="features" version="7.x-1.0-beta4" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/features/features-7.x-1.0-beta4.zip" artifactId="modules/features/features-7.x-1.0-beta4.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_features_7.x-1.0-beta4/7.x-1.0-beta4/mod_features_7.x-1.0-beta4-7.x-1.0-beta4.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>The features module enables the capture and management of features in Drupal. A feature is a collection of Drupal entities which taken together satisfy a
certain use-case.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module enables the capture and management of features in Drupal.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_feeds_7.x-2.0-alpha4" name="feeds" version="7.x-2.0-alpha4" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/feeds/feeds-7.x-2.0-alpha4.zip" artifactId="modules/feeds/feeds-7.x-2.0-alpha4.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_feeds_7.x-2.0-alpha4/7.x-2.0-alpha4/mod_feeds_7.x-2.0-alpha4-7.x-2.0-alpha4.zip</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_ctools_7.x-1.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_job_scheduler_7.x-2.0-alpha2</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Aggregates RSS/Atom/RDF feeds, imports CSV files and more.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Aggregates RSS/Atom/RDF feeds, imports CSV files and more.

One-off imports and periodic aggregation of content
Import or aggregate RSS/Atom feeds
Import or aggregate CSV files
Import or aggregate OPML files
PubSubHubbub support
Create nodes, users, taxonomy terms or simple database records from import
Extensible to import any other kind of content
Granular mapping of input elements to Drupal content elements
Exportable configurations
Batched import for large files

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_filefield_paths_7.x-1.0-alpha1" name="filefield_paths" version="7.x-1.0-alpha1" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/filefield_paths/filefield_paths-7.x-1.0-alpha1.zip" artifactId="modules/filefield_paths/filefield_paths-7.x-1.0-alpha1.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_filefield_paths_7.x-1.0-alpha1/7.x-1.0-alpha1/mod_filefield_paths_7.x-1.0-alpha1-7.x-1.0-alpha1.zip</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_token_7.x-1.0-beta5</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Adds extra functionality to FileFields Path settings.

The File (Field) Paths module extends the default functionality of Drupal's core Upload module, the FileField module and many other File Upload modules by adding the ability to use node tokens in destination paths and filenames.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>It adds extra functionality to FileFields Path settings.

The File (Field) Paths module extends the default functionality of Drupal's core Upload module, the FileField module and many other File Upload modules by adding the ability to use node tokens in destination paths and filenames.

In simple terms, File (Field) Paths allows you to automatically sort and rename your uploaded files using token based replacement patterns to maintain a nice clean filesystem.

 
Features:

Configurable file paths now use node tokens instead of user tokens.
Configurable filenames.
Support for:
Drupal core Upload module.
FileField module.
ImageField module.
ImageField Crop module.
Image module.
Comment Upload module.
[D6] Audio module.
[D6] Video module.
File path and filename cleanup options:
Filter out words and punctuation by taking advantage of the Pathauto module.
Convert unicode characters into US-ASCII with the Transliteration module.
Automatically updates unprocessed file paths in the node body, teaser and CCK text fields on save.
Retroactive updates - rename and/or move previously uploaded files (Use with caution)
[D6] Active updating - actively rename and/or move previously uploaded files (Use with caution)

 </content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_flag_7.x-2.0-beta6" name="flag" version="7.x-2.0-beta6" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/flag/flag-7.x-2.0-beta6.zip" artifactId="modules/flag/flag-7.x-2.0-beta6.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_flag_7.x-2.0-beta6/7.x-2.0-beta6/mod_flag_7.x-2.0-beta6-7.x-2.0-beta6.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Create customized flags that users can set on content.

Flag is a flexible flagging system that is completely customizable by the administrator. Using this module, the site administrator can provide any number of flags for nodes, comments, or users. Some possibilities include bookmarks, marking important, friends, or flag as offensive. With extensive views integration, you can create custom lists of popular content or keep tabs on important content.
</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>To create customized flags that users can set on content.

Flag is a flexible flagging system that is completely customizable by the administrator. Using this module, the site administrator can provide any number of flags for nodes, comments, or users. Some possibilities include bookmarks, marking important, friends, or flag as offensive. With extensive views integration, you can create custom lists of popular content or keep tabs on important content.

Flags may be per-user, meaning that each user can mark an item individually, or global, meaning that the item is either marked or it is not marked, and any user who changes that changes it for everyone.

In this way, additional flags (similar to published and sticky) can be put on nodes, or other items, and dealt with by the system however the administration likes.
Features

Create unlimited arbitrary flags or bookmarks to flag content
Extensive Views integration to make lists of popular flagged content
Full support for Tokens in all messages and labels
Execute Actions when content is flagged past a certain threshold (Actions is now included in Drupal 6 core with no additional modules, requires 2.x version in Drupal 5)
Full Rules module integration
JavaScript based toggling of flags
Limit flag display by content type and roles
Optionally show each flag as a checkbox on the node form

Each flag provides data to the Views module, and provides a default view to list 'my bookmarks'. The default views are basic, but are easily tailored to whatever the system administrator would like them to do.

The module will come installed with a simple bookmark and two sample views for 'My bookmarks' both as a stand-alone page at &quot;bookmarks&quot;, and a page for each user as a tab under their profile at user/x/bookmarks.
Recommended Flag-related Projects

There are many modules that use or complement Flag. Some of them:

Views: Create lists of flagged content.
Flag Weights: Add weights to Flags to make items orderable.
Flag Friend: A pre-built flag for marking other users as friends with Flag.
Flag Abuse: A pre-built flag for marking offensive content, plus administrative features.
Flag Terms: Adds the ability to flag taxonomy terms. </content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_hierarchical_select_7.x-3.0-alpha5" name="hierarchical_select" version="7.x-3.0-alpha5" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/hierarchical_select/hierarchical_select-7.x-3.0-alpha5.zip" artifactId="modules/hierarchical_select/hierarchical_select-7.x-3.0-alpha5.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_hierarchical_select_7.x-3.0-alpha5/7.x-3.0-alpha5/mod_hierarchical_select_7.x-3.0-alpha5-7.x-3.0-alpha5.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Simplifies the selection of one or multiple items in a hierarchical tree.

This module defines the &quot;hierarchical_select&quot; form element, which is a greatly enhanced way for letting the user select items in a hierarchy.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>It simplifies the selection of one or multiple items in a hierarchical tree.

This module defines the &quot;hierarchical_select&quot; form element, which is a greatly enhanced way for letting the user select items in a hierarchy.

Hierarchical Select has the ability to save the entire lineage of a selection or only the &quot;deepest&quot; selection. You can configure it to force the user to make a selection as deep as possible in the tree, or allow the user to select an item anywhere in the tree. Levels can be labeled, you can configure limit the number of items that can be selected, configure a title for the dropbox, choose a site-wide animation delay, and so on. You can even create new items and levels through Hierarchical Select!

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_video_7.x-2.4" name="video" version="7.x-2.4" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/video/video-7.x-2.4.zip" artifactId="modules/video/video-7.x-2.4.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_video_7.x-2.4/7.x-2.4/mod_video_7.x-2.4-7.x-2.4.zip</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_field__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_file__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_image__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Upload and manage video content with Drupal</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>To upload and manage video contents.

This module allows users to submit videos to a Drupal site. Video module 7.x-2.x provide video field while 6.x-3-x and 6.x-4-x provides a CCK video upload field to upload videos with ease. The 5.x module and 6.x-2 version is not CCK-based and supports additional playback options in a single node.

Video module allows you to upload video in any format, play video in any format, transcode video to H246, Theora, VP8 using Zencoder , FFMPEG , automatically creates video thumbnails, stream videos from cloud, HTML5 videos with mobile device playback compatibility, Very reliable API for converting videos and auto thumbnail, embed video to node body using WYSIWYG module (D7 only) and many more ...
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_imageapi_7.x-1.x-dev" name="imageapi" version="7.x-1.x-dev" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/imageapi/imageapi-7.x-1.x-dev.zip" artifactId="modules/imageapi/imageapi-7.x-1.x-dev.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_imageapi_7.x-1.x-dev/7.x-1.x-dev/mod_imageapi_7.x-1.x-dev-7.x-1.x-dev.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>ImageAPI supporting multiple toolkits.

This API is meant to be used in place of the API provided by image.inc. You probably do not need to install this module unless another module are you using requires it. It provides no new features to your Drupal site. It only provides an API other modules can leverage. Currently GD2 and ImageMagick support are distributed with ImageAPI.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>ImageAPI supporting multiple toolkits.

This API is meant to be used in place of the API provided by image.inc. You probably do not need to install this module unless another module are you using requires it. It provides no new features to your Drupal site. It only provides an API other modules can leverage. Currently GD2 and ImageMagick support are distributed with ImageAPI.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_imagemagick_7.x-1.0-alpha2" name="imagemagick" version="7.x-1.0-alpha2" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/imagemagick/imagemagick-7.x-1.0-alpha2.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/imagemagick/imagemagick-7.x-1.0-alpha2.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_imagemagick_7.x-1.0-alpha2/7.x-1.0-alpha2/mod_imagemagick_7.x-1.0-alpha2-7.x-1.0-alpha2.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Provides ImageMagick integration</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>It Provides ImageMagick integration.

Allows to use ImageMagick as image toolkit for Image API in Drupal 7 core.

Requirements

ImageMagick needs to be installed on your server and the convert binary needs to be accessible and executable from PHP.
The PHP configuration must allow invocation of proc_open() (which is security-wise identical to exec()).

Consult your server administrator or hosting provider if you are unsure about these requirements.

Note: GraphicsMagick, a performance fork of ImageMagick (like Pressflow to Drupal) should work as well. Just replace the convert executable with gm in the image toolkit settings.
Installation and configuration

Install as usual, see http://drupal.org/node/70151 for further information.
Go to Administration » Configuration » Media » Image toolkit and change the image toolkit to ImageMagick.
If the convert binary cannot be found in the default shell path, you need to enter the full path to ImageMagick's convert executable, including the filename itself.



</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_jcarousel_7.x-2.6" name="jcarousel" version="7.x-2.6" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/jcarousel/jcarousel-7.x-2.6.zip" artifactId="modules/jcarousel/jcarousel-7.x-2.6.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_jcarousel_7.x-2.6/7.x-2.6/mod_jcarousel_7.x-2.6-7.x-2.6.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>This module allows developers and themers to make use of the jCarousel jQuery plugin. It includes a developer API that other modules can use, as well as Views integration in the 2.0 version so that you can turn any list of content or images into a carousel.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>It  allows developers and themers to make use of the jCarousel jQuery plugin.

Features

Built-in Views support.
AJAX-loading of additional items as needed.
Carousel pager/navigation to jump between multiple pages.
Circular wrapping of items.
API for direct usage of jCarousel without Views.

Usage

See the included README documentation for an introduction on using jCarousel.

Note that you will almost certainly need to do custom CSS in your theme in order to use this module. The default CSS only supports 100 pixel square items. A basic understanding of CSS is therefor required to use this module.
Recommended modules

Views (create carousels without coding)

Version differences

jCarousel recently was rewritten to include Views support and a better API. These changes are not compatible with the previous version of the module. Please upgrade from 1.x to 2.x with caution, as this will almost certainly require retheming or modifications to your code.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_job_scheduler_7.x-2.0-alpha2" name="job_scheduler" version="7.x-2.0-alpha2" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/job_scheduler/job_scheduler-7.x-2.0-alpha2.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/job_scheduler/job_scheduler-7.x-2.0-alpha2.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_job_scheduler_7.x-2.0-alpha2/7.x-2.0-alpha2/mod_job_scheduler_7.x-2.0-alpha2-7.x-2.0-alpha2.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Simple API for scheduling tasks once at a predetermined time or periodically at a fixed interval.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>It is a simple API for scheduling tasks.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_languageicons_7.x-1.0-beta1" name="languageicons" version="7.x-1.0-beta1" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/languageicons/languageicons-7.x-1.0-beta1.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/languageicons/languageicons-7.x-1.0-beta1.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_languageicons_7.x-1.0-beta1/7.x-1.0-beta1/mod_languageicons_7.x-1.0-beta1-7.x-1.0-beta1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_locale__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>This module provides icons for language links, both for the Language switcher block and (optionally) for node links. It is a spin-off from Internationalization (i18n) package.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module provides icons for language links, both for the Language switcher block and  for node links.
As basic multilingual support is now built into Drupal 6 core, it doesn't depend anymore on any other contributed module. This module will work as simple add-in for Drupal 6.

However, for a fully enabled multilingual site, the Internationalization package is recommended.

The default icons provided are png images with a fixed height of 12 pixels and a variable width per the official dimension of the respective flag. However this module can handle other image types and sizes too. More language icons and new full collections of icons are welcome - please see #319966: Add flag icon theme selector if you wish to get yours included in the standard distribution.

#D7CX: I pledge that this module will have a full Drupal 7 release on the day that Drupal 7 is released.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_lightbox2_7.x-1.x-dev" name="lightbox2" version="7.x-1.x-dev" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/lightbox2/lightbox2-7.x-1.x-dev.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/lightbox2/lightbox2-7.x-1.x-dev.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_lightbox2_7.x-1.x-dev/7.x-1.x-dev/mod_lightbox2_7.x-1.x-dev-7.x-1.x-dev.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>The Lightbox2 module is a simple, unobtrusive script used to overlay images on the current page. It's a snap to setup and works on most modern browsers.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module is to overlay images on the current page. 

The module places images above your current page, not within. This frees you from the constraints of the layout, particularly column widths. It keeps users on the same page. Clicking to view an image and then having to click the back button to return to your site is bad for continuity (and no fun!).
Features

The version 2 module has several benefits over the plain Lightbox module. Note, not all of these features are available when the &quot;Lightbox2 Lite&quot; option is enabled.

Image Sets: group related images and navigate through them with ease - ideal for your image galleries.
Slideshow Capability.
HTML Content Support: ability to show websites or other HTML content in a lightbox.
Video Content Support.
Visual Effects: fancy pre-loader and transition when you click on the image.
Keyboard Shortcuts: useful keyboard shortcuts for switching between images, toggling play / pause, etc.
Zoom Capability: larger images are reduced in size so they fit snugly inside the browser window. A zoom in button can then be clicked on to see it in its original size, while a zoom out button is provided to return you to the scaled down version.
Choice of Layouts.
Skin and Animation Configuration.
Right-to-Left Language Support.
Automatic Image Detection: configurable automatic re-formatting of image node thumbnails, previews, etc, so there is no need to add 'rel=&quot;lightbox&quot;' to each image node link on your site. Image, Inline, Flickr, Acidfree Albums, Image Assist, Embedded Media Field and CCK Imagefield modules are all supported.
Page Exclusion Capability: exclude certain pages on your site from having the lightbox2 functionality.
Login Support: ability to modify all user/login links so the login form appears in a lightbox.
Gallery 2 Support: support for Gallery 2 images via the Gallery module (beta). See here for information on how to customise your Gallery2 theme to work with lightbox.

Dependencies

Lightbox2 5.x-2.0 and later versions now all use the jQuery library instead of the Scriptaculous and Prototype libraries, so there is no need to download and install a separate third party package. The 5.x versions have a dependency on the jQuery update module since the version of jQuery included in Drupal core is not that recent. Both the 1.x and 2.x versions of this module should work with Lightbox2.

There is no such dependency for the 6.x versions.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_link_7.x-1.0" name="link" version="7.x-1.0" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/link/link-7.x-1.0.zip" artifactId="modules/link/link-7.x-1.0.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_link_7.x-1.0/7.x-1.0/mod_link_7.x-1.0-7.x-1.0.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>The link module provides a useful custom content field, which can be added to content types for validating and storing internal or external links and URLs supporting additional title, tokens, target and css class attribution and static title values</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>It provides a useful custom content field, which can be added to content types for validating and storing internal or external links 

The link module can be count to the top 50 modules in Drupal installations and provides a standard custom content field for links. With this module links can be added easily to any content types and profiles and include advanced validating and different ways of storing internal or external links and URLs. It also supports additional link text title, site wide tokens for titles and title attributes, target attributes, css class attribution, static repeating values, input conversion, and many more.

Installation

Drop the entire link module directory into your 'sites/all/modules' folder
Enable the module from the Administration area modules page (admin/build/modules)
Create or Edit a content-type and add a new field of type link (admin/content/types in D6, admin/structure/types in D7)
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_localization_update_7.x-1.0-beta2" name="localization_update" version="7.x-1.0-beta2" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/l10n_update/l10n_update-7.x-1.0-beta2.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/l10n_update/l10n_update-7.x-1.0-beta2.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_localization_update_7.x-1.0-beta2/7.x-1.0-beta2/mod_localization_update_7.x-1.0-beta2-7.x-1.0-beta2.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_locale__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Automatically download and update your translations fetching them from other Localization server.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Automatically download and update your translations fetching them from other Localization server.

Integrating with git checkouts

This module is based on concepts very similar to Drupal core's update module. Modules and themes with their corresponding drupal.org projects are identified and translations are downloaded for the appropriate versions. If you use git checkouts instead of package tarballs or zip files, use Git deploy module, so projects and versions are identified properly. (For legacy CVS checkouts, the CVS deploy module will work). 
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_signup_rules_7.x-1.0-beta1" name="signup_rules" version="7.x-1.0-beta1" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/signup_rules/signup_rules-7.x-1.0-beta1.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/signup_rules/signup_rules-7.x-1.0-beta1.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_signup_rules_7.x-1.0-beta1/7.x-1.0-beta1/mod_signup_rules_7.x-1.0-beta1-7.x-1.0-beta1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_logintoboggan_7.x-1.2</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Administrators can use this module to automatically modify users, nodes, and signups when certain site or Signup related events occur. Signup Rules can also be used to replace and enhance actions that are native to Signup module, like sending e-mails to users who have signed up for content.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Administrators can use this module to automatically modify users, nodes, and signups when certain site or Signup related events occur. 

The Signup Rules module has received an upgrade to include 5 new rules elements:

A new event for being able to suppress the signup form based on rules conditions. This includes a new condition to check the signup form display status and two new actions for allowing and forbidding the display of the signup form.
A second new condition allows to check the signup status of a user to the currently viewed content.

Full list of Signup Rules elements
Events

User signed up to content
User updated the signup to content
User canceled the signup to content
Signup to content was opened
Signup to content was closed
Displaying signup form is being inquired

Conditions

Is user signed up to content
Is display of signup form allowed

Actions

Allow displaying signup form
Forbid displaying signup form
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_media_gallery_7.x-1.0-beta6" name="media_gallery" version="7.x-1.0-beta6" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/media_gallery/media_gallery-7.x-1.0-beta6.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/media_gallery/media_gallery-7.x-1.0-beta6.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_media_gallery_7.x-1.0-beta6/7.x-1.0-beta6/mod_media_gallery_7.x-1.0-beta6-7.x-1.0-beta6.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_list__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_options__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_number__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_media_7.x-1.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_taxonomy__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Uses the Media module to provide a rich media gallery. It currently supports images and youtube videos well.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>To provide a rich media gallery.

Uses the Media module to provide a rich media gallery. It currently supports images and youtube videos well. Other file types may or may not work as well, but the facility is there to add them. This module was developed by the engineering team at Acquia
Demo

You can try it out yourself by creating a site on http://drupalgardens.com
Features

Add media from URL, upload or existing files
Multi-file upload
Set rows and columns and dynamically size images to fit space
Lightbox support
CC license settings
Title, description and tags on images
Drag and drop re-ordering
Gallery collections to group related galleries together
Creates gallery blocks
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_media_gallery_picker_7.x-1.0-beta1" name="media_gallery_picker" version="7.x-1.0-beta1" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/mg_picker/mg_picker-7.x-1.0-beta1.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/mg_picker/mg_picker-7.x-1.0-beta1.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_media_gallery_picker_7.x-1.0-beta1/7.x-1.0-beta1/mod_media_gallery_picker_7.x-1.0-beta1-7.x-1.0-beta1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_media_gallery_7.x-1.0-beta6</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_list__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_options__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_number__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_media_7.x-1.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_taxonomy__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>This module creates a filter and a wysiwyg plugin to select galleries in content.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>It creates a filter and a wysiwyg plugin to select galleries in content.

This page gives the essential Git commands for working with this project's source files.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_menu_per_role_7.x-1.x-dev" name="menu_per_role" version="7.x-1.x-dev" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/menu_per_role/menu_per_role-7.x-1.x-dev.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/menu_per_role/menu_per_role-7.x-1.x-dev.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_menu_per_role_7.x-1.x-dev/7.x-1.x-dev/mod_menu_per_role_7.x-1.x-dev-7.x-1.x-dev.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_menu__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>This module allows you to restrict access to menu items1 based on user roles. It depends on the Drupal core menu.module—just activate both modules and edit a menu item as usual. There will be a new fieldset that allows you to restrict access by role. The fieldset also appears in the node edit form.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module allows you to restrict access to menu items1 based on user roles. It depends on the Drupal core menu.module—just activate both modules and edit a menu item as usual. There will be a new fieldset that allows you to restrict access by role. The fieldset also appears in the node edit form.

1We wrote &quot;menu items&quot;, not &quot;nodes&quot;. This module does not prevent users from accessing the destination nodes. It only changes the visibility of the menu items.
Warning: Update in 6.x-1.x-dev (and next in 1.9)

The newest 6.x-1.x-dev reverts a change made in version 1.8 so administrators do not see hidden menus by default. However, the main administrator user (UID 1) still sees hidden menus unless you go to the new administrative screen and change the flags there.

Note also that the module was moved from the &quot;Others&quot; package to the &quot;Menu&quot; package. It seems to make sense to have it there since most menu related modules are found there.
Drupal 7

A Drupal 7 version is available although it doesn't work very well yet. The Drupal 7 users will appreciate if you can become a maintainer as Alexis is not working on Drupal 7 at all anymore.
Drupal 6
Maintainer &amp; Sponsor

Alexis Wilke is maintaining the D6 version.

The current sponsor is Made to Order Software Corp. Click to check out our other modules.
Where is this module used?

Cannot tell you which links are being hidden, but the module is now in use on the Linus Geek Page website. For this reason, I created an official version: 1.0.

I have used this module to allow a customer to edit a page (A) but not another (B). The end users see page B which includes node A in some way (i.e. InsertNode). So I wanted the end user to see the menu for B, but not the menu of A. However, my customer, once logged in, should see A because that's theirs to go and edit the content that appears on B.
Do I need this module?

[If you are using Drupal 5, ignore this and go to the Drupal 5 entry below!]
Short answer

It is very likely that you do not need this module at all.
Log In, Log Out, Register &amp; My Account

When you want to create a &quot;Log In&quot; menu item, in any menu, make it point to &quot;user/login&quot;. That way it will disappear once a user is logged in. You probably know about the &quot;Log Out&quot; path, it is shown in the Navigation menu: &quot;logout&quot;. To offer a Register menu item to anonymous users, make the link point to &quot;user/register&quot;. And if you want to show a &quot;My Account&quot; link, use &quot;user&quot;. That will always be visible and if an anonymous user tries that link, he will first be asked to log in.

Log In, user/login
Log Out, logout
Register, user/register
My Account, user

Consider the destination node access instead

You may want to use modules that control node access rights. In Drupal 6 a menu link that points to a node that cannot be accessed by the current user is not shown to that user. That's much simpler than having to edit each menu item for specific role permissions!

If you need finer control over node access rights, have a look at:

content access (Read node 220680, comment 1084593)
node_privacy_byrole
taxonomy_access
forum_access
image_gallery_access
config_perms

So?! What is this module for???

Now... There are a few cases when hiding a menu item by role can still be useful. Although rare, it happens.

You are dealing with external links (these are considered public and have full access rights by default.)
Menus that you do not want to show to certain users although the destination pages are still freely accessible.

For example, you could have a site with a menu for registered users and a menu used to appeal to new users so they create an account:

My Account
Edit my info
Send a message to my friends
Log Out
New to This Website?
Check out why you should register
Still not convince? Check our video!
Register Now
Already have an account? Log In now!

The &quot;My Account&quot; menu should probably not appear when your users are not yet logged in. Install menu_per_role, edit the &quot;My Account&quot; menu item, and select all the roles except &quot;anonymous&quot;. Note that this case can also be solved by changing the access rights of the node pointed to by &quot;My Account&quot; menu item.

The &quot;New to This Website&quot; menu should definitively be removed once the person is logged in. Install menu_per_role, edit the &quot;New to This Website&quot; menu item, and mark it for the &quot;anonymous&quot; role. This way, the reasons why this site is worth the trouble are still accessible to the logged in users, just not directly accessible through the menu.
Maintenance Consideration

Note that if you add a role later that should have access to (most) of the menu items and you already have some roles selected, you will have to edit each menu item to fix them. (If you have a patch for a mass update, it is welcome! Post it in this issue #940800: Bulk Conversion of Menu items.)
Installation

Up until Drupal 6.9, you had to apply a patch to fix the Drupal core menu module. If you have Drupal 6.10 or better, the patch is applied against the core already.

The patch is available inside the module. Extract the module first then check out the README.txt file for more information about this.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_message_7.x-1.0-alpha1" name="message" version="7.x-1.0-alpha1" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/message/message-7.x-1.0.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/message/message-7.x-1.0.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_message_7.x-1.0-alpha1/7.x-1.0-alpha1/mod_message_7.x-1.0-alpha1-7.x-1.0-alpha1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>This is a Messaging Framework to allow message sending in a channel independent way. It will provide a common API for message composition and sending while allowing plug-ins for multiple messaging methods.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This is a Messaging Framework to allow message sending in a channel independent way. It will provide a common API for message composition and sending while allowing plug-ins for multiple messaging methods.

When using this framework, you won't send e-mails to users anymore. You will send them 'messages' and they will decide how they want to get them delivered, that may be by mail, IM, SMS, depending on user's preferences...</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_nodequeue_7.x-2.0-beta1" name="nodequeue" version="7.x-2.0-beta1" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/nodequeue/nodequeue-7.x-2.0-beta1.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/nodequeue/nodequeue-7.x-2.0-beta1.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_nodequeue_7.x-2.0-beta1/7.x-2.0-beta1/mod_nodequeue_7.x-2.0-beta1-7.x-2.0-beta1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>The Nodequeue module allows users to collect nodes in an arbitrarily ordered list. The order in the list can be used for a any purpose</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>It  allows users to collect nodes in an arbitrarily ordered list. 

The Nodequeue module allows users to collect nodes in an arbitrarily ordered list. The order in the list can be used for a any purpose, such as:

A block listing teasers for the five top news stories on a site
A user’s favorite music albums
A group of favorite from which one is randomly displayed

Nodequeue provides a simple drag-and-drop interface to manually order any queue. Additionally, it allows nodes to be added and removed from queues without needing edit permissions to the node. Nodes can be added to queues either from a queue management tab or by links on the node teaser.

Smartqueue API

Nodequeue provides a robust API that allows other modules to define smartqueues, which are associated with external data. For example, the included taxonomy smartqueue creates subqueues for a given queue for every term in the chosen vocabulary. Nodes are then only eligible for subqueues whose term matches the nodes terms. This makes it very easy to have queues for each category without cluttering the management page.

Modules that Extend Nodequeue:

Smartqueue per-user: Makes a personal queue available to users of one or more roles.
Smartqueues for Organic Groups: Makes a queue available for ordering by members of an Organic Group or Group admins only.

Apache Solr Search Integration

The latest version of Nodequeue for Drupal 6 includes integration with Apache Solr Search, making it possible to boost nodes that are part of a queue.

Nodequeue contains an extensive API. It integrates well with Views and Actions, as well as providing a host of functions to interface with it directly, making it possible to manipulate queues programmatically for whatever purposes that are customized to your website.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_notifications_7.x-1.0-alpha1" name="notifications" version="7.x-1.0-alpha1" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/notifications/notifications-7.x-1.0-alpha1.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/notifications/notifications-7.x-1.0-alpha1.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_notifications_7.x-1.0-alpha1/7.x-1.0-alpha1/mod_notifications_7.x-1.0-alpha1-7.x-1.0-alpha1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_menu_block_7.x-2.2</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_trigger__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>This is a complete Subscriptions/Notifications Framework aiming at extendability and scalability. It allows any number of plug-ins defining new event types or subscription types or a different user interface.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This is a complete Subscriptions/Notifications Framework aiming at extendability and scalability. 

Features

Immediate or digested notifications, allowing multiple digest formats for deferred notifications. Digests are configurable and themeable.
By using the Messaging Framework, notifications are not limited to email. Other methods like SMS or XMPP can be used.
Pluggable subscription and event types. Currently included: Content subscriptions (thread or node, author, content type), Taxonomy
Event and message queueing, fully scalable and configurable. Uses token module for message composition and text replacement, thus it supports pluggable tokens
Pluggable and fully configurable user interface. A UI module is provided but it can be disabled and replaced by a custom UI module.
Configurable per content type. You can have different types of subscriptions and a different UI for each content type
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_panels_7.x-3.0-alpha3" name="panels" version="7.x-3.0-alpha3" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/panels/panels-7.x-3.0-alpha3.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/panels/panels-7.x-3.0-alpha3.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_panels_7.x-3.0-alpha3/7.x-3.0-alpha3/mod_panels_7.x-3.0-alpha3-7.x-3.0-alpha3.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_ctools_7.x-1.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>The Panels module allows a site administrator to create customized layouts for multiple uses. At its core it is a drag and drop content manager that lets you visually design a layout and place content within that layout. </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>The Panels module allows a site administrator to create customized layouts for multiple uses. 

The Panels module allows a site administrator to create customized layouts for multiple uses. At its core it is a drag and drop content manager that lets you visually design a layout and place content within that layout. Integration with other systems allows you to create nodes that use this, landing pages that use this, and even override system pages such as taxonomy and the node page so that you can customize the layout of your site with very fine grained permissions.
Integration with Ctools module

Panels 3 utilizes the CTools' system of &quot;context&quot; so that the content you place on the page can be aware of what is being displayed. For example, in the existing Drupal setup, a block has no real knowledge of what the primary page is displaying. There are all kinds of tricks and tools you can use to get information to the blocks, but this generally means writing PHP code to scan the URL and pull the data out, which is not a very good thing when that data should already exist.
Panels uses Contexts - What are they?

In a Panel, you can create contexts, which represent the objects being displayed. For example, when displaying the node view, NID argument on the page is converted into a context through the 'arguments' system. You can then create a relationship from that node to, say, the node author, or if you have a node reference from CCK, a related node [as of CCK 2.3]. Once the contexts are in place, content specifically about those contexts can be placed. For the node context you can add CCK fields, the node body, attached files and a host of other information that can be provided by plugins. For the user context you can display things like the user picture or profile. Note that CCK 2.3 and later only has support for Panels 3.

In addition, these contexts can be checked for information and use that not only to make content available to be displayed, but to choose which layout to display! For example, if your site is international, you can use context to see if the node being viewed is set for a particular language and choose to display it one way if it is in French or another way if it is in English. You can also select on attributes like node type, whether or not the user has access to edit the node, and more. This system is also pluggable and you can add your own custom criteria with only a small amount of code. Want to display nodes differently based on how a custom CCK field you've added to a node type is set? That is very simple to write and you can use this to change the presentation entirely.

Panels also includes simpler applications of the drag and drop system. There is a node type (the 'panel' node) that can simply be added as content to your system. By being a node it loses a lot of the features that the more powerful page system has, but it does have the advantage of simplicity, and gaining all of the functionality that nodes normally get.

Panels can also be used for items smaller than pages. What if you have a normal sidebar, and you have two pieces of content that waste a bunch of space because they're really too narrow, and your design looks significantly better if they are side by side? That's complex to do in Drupal because what you end up having to do is create a custom block with custom code to display these two pieces of content. With Panels, you just create a &quot;mini-panel&quot; with a two column layout. Add one block to the left, one block to the right, and finish. This mini panel will then be available to your system as an ordinary block, or as panel content to go in the other panels.
Other Features of Panels

Panels supports styles, which can control how individual content panes, regions within a panel, and the entire panel will be rendered. While Panels ships with few styles, styles can be provided as plugins by modules, as well as by themes!
The layout builder is nice for visually designing a layout, but a real HTML guru doesn't want the somewhat weighty HTML that this will create. Modules and themes can provide custom layouts that can fit a designer's exacting specifications, but still allow the site builder to place content wherever you like.

Panels includes a pluggable caching mechanism. A single cache type is included, the 'simple' cache which is time-based. Since most sites have very specific caching needs based upon the content and traffic patterns, this system was designed to let sites that need to devise their own triggers for cache clearing and implement plugins that will work with Panels. Panels can be cached as a whole, meaning the entire output of the panel can be cached, or individual content panes that are heavy can be cached.
Panels can be integrated with Organic Groups through the og_panels module to allow individual groups to have their own customized layouts.
Panels integrates with Views to allow administrators to add any view as content. Or, for uses where the layout editor needs more tightly controlled content, Views can be given custom displays to provide only what the site administrator wants the panels builder to use.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_redirect_7.x-1.0-beta3" name="redirect" version="7.x-1.0-beta3" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/redirect/redirect-7.x-1.0-beta3.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/redirect/redirect-7.x-1.0-beta3.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_redirect_7.x-1.0-beta3/7.x-1.0-beta3/mod_redirect_7.x-1.0-beta3-7.x-1.0-beta3.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_pathauto_7.x-1.0-rc2</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>This module allows you to specify a redirect from one path to another path or an external URL, using any HTTP redirect status.This is the new module home for a unified redirection API (also replaces
path_redirect and globalredirect).</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This is the new module home for a unified redirection API.

This module allows you to specify a redirect from one path to another path or an external URL, using any HTTP redirect status.

#D7CX: I pledge that Path redirect will have a full Drupal 7 release on the day that Drupal 7 is released. Note that the project has moved to http://drupal.org/project/redirect for Drupal 7.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_print_7.x-1.0-alpha2" name="print" version="7.x-1.0-alpha2" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/print/print-7.x-1.0-alpha2.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/print/print-7.x-1.0-alpha2.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_print_7.x-1.0-alpha2/7.x-1.0-alpha2/mod_print_7.x-1.0-alpha2-7.x-1.0-alpha2.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>This module allows you to generate the following printer-friendly versions of any node:
Printer-friendly version (webpage format),PDF version ,Send by-email </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module allows you to generate the following printer-friendly versions of any node.

PDF version (at www.example.com/printpdf/nid)
Send by-email (at www.example.com/printmail/nid)

where nid is the node id of content to render.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_references_7.x-2.0-beta3" name="references" version="7.x-2.0-beta3" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/references/references-7.x-2.0-beta3.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/references/references-7.x-2.0-beta3.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_references_7.x-2.0-beta3/7.x-2.0-beta3/mod_references_7.x-2.0-beta3-7.x-2.0-beta3.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_field__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_options__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Defines common base features for the various reference field types.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module defines common base features for the various reference field types.

As the past couple months showed, the current maintainers are not up to the task. This module accepts new maintainers.
References will most probably be deprecated in the near future in favor of Entity Reference, which should probably be considered first on fresh D7 projects. Another, more radical, alternative would be the Relation module.

This project provides D7 versions of the 'Node reference' and 'User reference' field types, that were part of the CCK package in D6, at functional parity with the D6 counterparts. See http://drupal.org/node/533222 for details.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_google_analytics_7.x-1.0-alpha3" name="google_analytics" version="7.x-1.0-alpha3" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/ga_stats/ga_stats-7.x-1.0-alpha3.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/ga_stats/ga_stats-7.x-1.0-alpha3.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_google_analytics_7.x-1.0-alpha3/7.x-1.0-alpha3/mod_google_analytics_7.x-1.0-alpha3-7.x-1.0-alpha3.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Allows you to pull in data that Google Analytics has gathered for your site and use it in Views.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module allows you to pull in data that Google Analytics has gathered for your site and use it in Views.

The module allows you to add the following statistics features to your site:

Single/multi/cross domain tracking
Selectively track/exclude certain users, roles and pages
Monitor what type of links are tracked (downloads, outgoing and mailto)
Monitor what files are downloaded from your pages
Custom variables support with tokens
Custom code snippets
Site Search support
AdSense support
Tracking of Goals
Anonymize visitors IP address
Cache the Google Analytics code on your local server for improved page loading times
Access denied (403) and Page not found (404) tracking
DoNotTrack support (non-cached content only)
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_securepages_7.x-1.x-dev" name="securepages" version="7.x-1.x-dev" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/securepages/securepages-7.x-1.x-dev.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/securepages/securepages-7.x-1.x-dev.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_securepages_7.x-1.x-dev/7.x-1.x-dev/mod_securepages_7.x-1.x-dev-7.x-1.x-dev.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>A small process which will redirect the required pages to a SSL version of the page.
This module makes sure that the user is running on a secure page when they create or edit content, view user details, or administer the site.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module makes sure that the user is running on a secure page when they create or edit content, view user details, or administer the site.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_seo_checklist_7.x-3.0-beta1" name="seo_checklist" version="7.x-3.0-beta1" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/seo_checklist/seo_checklist-7.x-3.0-beta1.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/seo_checklist/seo_checklist-7.x-3.0-beta1.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_seo_checklist_7.x-3.0-beta1/7.x-3.0-beta1/mod_seo_checklist_7.x-3.0-beta1-7.x-3.0-beta1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>This module provides a checklist of recommended Drupal modules and good Drupal SEO (Search Engine Optimization) best practices. Maximize the presence of your Drupal website in the major search engines like Google, Yahoo, Bing, etc.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module provides a checklist of recommended Drupal modules and good Drupal SEO (Search Engine Optimization) best practices. Maximize the presence of your Drupal website in the major search engines like Google, Yahoo, Bing, etc. This module will:

provide a checklist that helps you keep track of what needs to be done
look to see what modules you already have installed and check them off for you automatically (thanks, EclipseGC!)
provide a list of things that you haven't done so that you can do them.
time/date stamp each item as you complete it so that you have a report that you can give your boss/client to show them how awesome you are that you've done all the SEO stuff
make you look like an SEO genius!

With this module, all you have to do is use the checklist and you'll know exactly what SEO stuff was done. It's more than just a list of stuff to do - it's a powerful organization tool, as well.

This module is paid for and maintained by Volacci, the Drupal SEO company. If you've done everything in the module and you're still not getting the results you're expecting, please contact us. We're here to help make Drupal the best platform on the planet for SEO!</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_service_links_7.x-2.1" name="service_links" version="7.x-2.1" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/service_links/service_links-7.x-2.1.zip" artifactId="modules/service_links/service_links-7.x-2.1.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_service_links_7.x-2.1/7.x-2.1/mod_service_links_7.x-2.1-7.x-2.1.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Service Links allow the users to share the website's content on various social networks, bookmarking websites, social blogs and similiar, and help programmers to have a small framework thatprovide easily more services.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>It allow the users to share the website's content on various social networks, bookmarking websites, social blogs and similiar, and help programmers to have a small framework thatprovide easily more services.

Service Links allow the users to share a web page in various social networks like bookmarking services, social blogs and similiar, providing an easy way to extend their number. Built on Drupal for Drupal doesn't include commercial advertising codes and don't require third part libraries.

The services included are various: del.icio.us, Digg/Digg button, Facebook/Facebook Share/Facebook Like, Furl, Google Bookmark/Google Plus One, IceRocket, LinkedIn/Linkedin button counter, MySpace, Newsvine, Reddit, StumbleUpon, Technorati, Twitter/Twitter widget, Yahoo Bookmark, and many more, they are split for language in different packages: basque, dutch, farsi, german, hungarian, italian, russian, spanish, swedish.

Other services are availables as an extra module fully customizable with some click.

Features

show links as text, image or both;
display for content types or taxonomy;
display in teaser, full page or both;
display links for user roles;
provide links on: node content, node link, block;
provide blocks for node and not-node pages;
sortable services through a drag'n drop table;
custom icons may be specified in a different folder;
browser bookmarking (work with Firefox, IE, Opera, Chrome);
support for short links (enhanced with Shorten Urls);
support for widgets (also known like dynamic buttons): Digg Button, Facebook Share, Facebook Like, Linkedin button counter, Google Plus One, Twitter Button;
title tag used for build the link, can be override with a custom string including tokens (look to Token project);
support for icon sprites (through Service Links Sprites plugin);
support the page visibility as every block does;
provide two powerful APIs for print the whole set of selected services or a custom subset (look the documentation page) with the ability to override the default settings.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_smtp_7.x-1.0-beta1" name="smtp" version="7.x-1.0-beta1" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/smtp/smtp-7.x-1.0-beta1.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/smtp/smtp-7.x-1.0-beta1.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_smtp_7.x-1.0-beta1/7.x-1.0-beta1/mod_smtp_7.x-1.0-beta1-7.x-1.0-beta1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>This module allows Drupal to bypass the PHP mail() function and send email directly to an SMTP server. The module supports SMTP authentication and can even connect to servers using SSL if supported by PHP.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module allows Drupal to bypass the PHP mail() function and send email directly to an SMTP server. </content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_spamspan_7.x-1.1-beta1" name="spamspan" version="7.x-1.1-beta1" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/spamspan/spamspan-7.x-1.1-beta1.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/spamspan/spamspan-7.x-1.1-beta1.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_spamspan_7.x-1.1-beta1/7.x-1.1-beta1/mod_spamspan_7.x-1.1-beta1-7.x-1.1-beta1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_filter__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>The SpamSpan module obfuscates email addresses to help prevent spambots from collecting them</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>The SpamSpan module obfuscates email addresses to help prevent spambots from collecting them.

It implements the technique at the SpamSpan website (a German version is also available). The problem with most email address obfuscators is that they rely upon JavaScript being enabled on the client side. This makes the technique inaccessible to people with screen readers. SpamSpan however will produce clickable links if JavaScript is enabled, and will show the email address as example [at] example [dot] com if the browser does not support JavaScript or if JavaScript is disabled.

This technique is unlikely to be absolutely foolproof. It is possible in theory for a determined spambot to harvest addresses from your site no matter how you disguise them. But research suggests that the by far the great majority of spambots do not bother to attempt to collect addresses which have been hidden using JavaScript. Indeed, most spambots cannot currently read JavaScript at all.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_strongarm_7.x-2.0-beta3" name="strongarm" version="7.x-2.0-beta3" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/strongarm/strongarm-7.x-2.0-beta3.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/strongarm/strongarm-7.x-2.0-beta3.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_strongarm_7.x-2.0-beta3/7.x-2.0-beta3/mod_strongarm_7.x-2.0-beta3-7.x-2.0-beta3.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_ctools_7.x-1.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Strongarm gives site builders a way to override the default variable values that Drupal core and contributed modules ship with. It is not an end user tool, but a developer and site builder tool which provides an API and a limited UI. 

Enforces variable values defined by modules that need settings set to operate properly.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Strongarm gives site builders a way to override the default variable values that Drupal core and contributed modules ship with. It is not an end user tool, but a developer and site builder tool which provides an API and a limited UI.

An example of such a variable is site_frontpage. In Drupal this defaults to node, which ensures that the front page gets content as soon as some exists, but for many Drupal sites this setting is simply wrong. Strongarm gives the site builder a place in the equation - an opportunity to set the site_frontpage to something that makes sense for their site.

Strongarm leverages ctools to provide exportables of Drupal variables. This branch also allows Strongarm to be used with the Features module. More information about this work is available on this blog post.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_uiplog_7.x-1.0-beta2" name="uiplog" version="7.x-1.0-beta2" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/uiplog/uiplog-7.x-1.0-beta2.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/uiplog/uiplog-7.x-1.0-beta2.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_uiplog_7.x-1.0-beta2/7.x-1.0-beta2/mod_uiplog_7.x-1.0-beta2-7.x-1.0-beta2.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_views_7.x-3.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Logs users IP to db stable on user login.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>It logs users IP to db stable on user login.

The global user object contains some basic data from Drupal core. It does not automatically include data from other modules, including the core profile module. To get all data in the user object, you need to do a full user_load(). The following is a first attempt at documenting the information that core puts into the object. Items with (?) are where I didn't know and took my best guess. If anyone knows more on this and can fill in the blanks, please leave a comment. I will at some point gather all the comments together into one and then file an issue to get it added to the official documentation.

    uid - User ID
    name - User name
    pass - Encrypted password
    mail - User email address
    theme - (?) Name of the theme shown for this user (no longer changeable in core but can be in contrib)
    signature - Signature as set in the user account settings
    signature_format - Text format to apply to signature
    created - Unix timstamp for when the account was created
    access - Unix timstamp of the last time the user accessed the site
    login - (?) Unix timstamp of the last time the user logged in
    status - 1 if the user is active, 0 if blocked
    timezone - User's timezone, if user selectable timezones are enabled
    language - User's language code
    picture - User picture / avatar
    init - (?) Contains the user's email
    data - (?)
    sid - (?) Session ID
    ssid - (?)
    hostname - User's IP address
    timestamp - (?)
    cache - (?)
    session - (?) Variables stored in the session
    roles - Array of roles assigned to the user
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_token_7.x-1.0-beta5" name="token" version="7.x-1.0-beta5" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/token/token-7.x-1.0-beta6.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/token/token-7.x-1.0-beta6.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_token_7.x-1.0-beta5/7.x-1.0-beta5/mod_token_7.x-1.0-beta5-7.x-1.0-beta5.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Provides a user interface for the Token API and some missing core tokens.

Tokens are small bits of text that can be placed into larger documents via simple placeholders, like %site-name or [user]. The Token module provides a central API for modules to use these tokens, and expose their own token values.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module provides a user interface for the Token API and some missing core tokens.

Tokens are small bits of text that can be placed into larger documents via simple placeholders, like %site-name or [user]. The Token module provides a central API for modules to use these tokens, and expose their own token values.

Note that Token module doesn't provide any visible functions to the user on its own, it just provides token handling services for other modules.

For Drupal 6, the Token module provides a &quot;Token Actions&quot; module which can be enabled separately. This provides several &quot;actions&quot; for the Drupal core Actions/Trigger modules to use that take advantage of the Token replacement functionality.

Modules that use the Token module and provide tokens via the API include Organic Groups, Pathauto, Comment Notify, and Commerce. Also check out the full list of modules that use or provide tokens or the list of open issues tagged with 'token'.

Report any problems you find so that we can release a stable version.

Token is co-maintained by eaton and davereid. It was previously co-maintained by greggles.

#D7CX: The basic token API is now a part of Drupal 7! Unfortunately, other things like the a browsable token UI, and field &amp; profile tokens did not make it into core and will be supported here for Drupal 7.

#D7AX - I pledge to make this module as accessible as it can be. If you find any flaws, please submit an issue and tag it D7AX. Help me fix them if you can.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_transliteration_7.x-3.0" name="transliteration" version="7.x-3.0" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/transliteration/transliteration-7.x-3.0.zip" artifactId="modules/transliteration/transliteration-7.x-3.0.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_transliteration_7.x-3.0/7.x-3.0/mod_transliteration_7.x-3.0-7.x-3.0.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Converts non-latin text to US-ASCII and sanitizes file names.

Provides one-way string transliteration (romanization) and cleans file names during upload by replacing unwanted characters.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>It provides one-way string transliteration and cleans file names during upload by replacing unwanted characters.

Generally spoken, it takes Unicode text and tries to represent it in US-ASCII characters (universally displayable, unaccented characters) by attempting to transliterate the pronunciation expressed by the text in some other writing system to Roman letters.

According to Unidecode, from which most of the transliteration data has been derived, &quot;Russian and Greek seem to work passably. But it works quite bad on Japanese and Thai.&quot;

Do I need to use transliteration for uploaded files?

This question can't be generally answered, rather it depends on what you want to do with user submitted file uploads. There are two simple cases when you might not need transliteration:

you let users upload files to your site and offer these files as download without PHP processing, and you're on Drupal 6 or later, and not using a Windows-based web server. Or,

you are sure your users won't upload files or images containing non-ASCII characters in file names.

However, whenever you want to process uploaded files on the server, you most likely need transliteration. For example, if you are using ImageCache to provide modified versions of uploaded images. The reason is that PHP 5 doesn't fully support Unicode characters in filenames, and may not be able to access those files.

Whether you use transliteration for URLs (when using Pathauto 2.x), however, is a matter of personal taste. For example, the russian Wikipedia does not transliterate, but uses full Unicode in URLs. On the other hand, as a user noted, links containing Unicode look quite ugly in e-mails sent from your site.

By enabling this module, it will be easier for people to search with or without accents. Thus, if someone wanted to find references to the word 'conteúdo' they could type it with an accent or 'conteudo' and get the same result.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_avatar_selection_7.x-1.x-dev" name="avatar_selection" version="7.x-1.x-dev" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/avatar_selection/avatar_selection-7.x-1.x-dev.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/avatar_selection/avatar_selection-7.x-1.x-dev.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_avatar_selection_7.x-1.x-dev/7.x-1.x-dev/mod_avatar_selection_7.x-1.x-dev-7.x-1.x-dev.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Manages configuration of a default list of avatar icons that a user can use instead of uploading a picture.

When a user edits their account details they can choose to upload an image or photo of themselves, also known as an avatar.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>It manages configuration of a default list of avatar icons that a user can use instead of uploading a picture.

When a user edits their account details they can choose to upload an image or photo of themselves, also known as an avatar.

The Avatar Selection module allows the user to pick an avatar image from a list already loaded by an administrative user. It is also possible to disable the uploading of pictures by users and only allow them to select an avatar icon from this list.

No images are supplied with this module. It is recommended that all images you use are roughly of the same size.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_views_bulk_operations_7.x-3.0-beta2" name="views_bulk_operations" version="7.x-3.0-beta2" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/views_bulk_operations/views_bulk_operations-7.x-3.0-beta2.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/views_bulk_operations/views_bulk_operations-7.x-3.0-beta2.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_views_bulk_operations_7.x-3.0-beta2/7.x-3.0-beta2/mod_views_bulk_operations_7.x-3.0-beta2-7.x-3.0-beta2.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_entity_7.x-1.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_views_7.x-3.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_ctools_7.x-1.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Provides a way of selecting multiple rows and applying operations to them.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module augments Views by allowing bulk operations to be executed on the displayed rows. It does so by showing a checkbox in front of each node, and adding a select box containing operations that can be applied. Drupal Core or Rules actions can be used.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_views_slideshow_7.x-3.0" name="views_slideshow" version="7.x-3.0" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/views_slideshow/views_slideshow-7.x-3.0.zip" artifactId="modules/views_slideshow/views_slideshow-7.x-3.0.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_views_slideshow_7.x-3.0/7.x-3.0/mod_views_slideshow_7.x-3.0-7.x-3.0.zip</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_views_7.x-3.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_ctools_7.x-1.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Provides a View style that displays rows as a jQuery slideshow. This is an API and requires Views Slideshow Cycle or another module that supports the API.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Views Slideshow can be used to create a slideshow of any content (not just images) that can appear in a View. Powered by jQuery, it is heavily customizable: you may choose slideshow settings for each View you create.
Potential uses

News item slideshow (such as the title, image and teaser of the last 5 news articles submitted)
The Last X number of X submitted (images, videos, blog entries, forum posts, comments, testimonials, etc.).
Rotate any image, based on any filters you can apply in views.
Hottest new products for any ecommerce drupal site.
Rotate contact links, share links, etc.
Heck, you could rotate entire nodes, categories, image galleries, etc. I wouldn't suggest it, but you have that power.
Its also a great space saver. Places where you had multiple images or multiple items such as RSS feeds or category listings can now be presented in a slideshow.

The possibilities are really endless, as the more ways you can think of to categorize and add to views, the more you can rotate.
Views Slideshow Installation and Configuration

Read the documentation for instructions on how to install and configure views slideshow. You can also enable the Advanced Help module inside your site for tutorials on how to use views slideshow. (currently only 2.x version)
Thanks to Bob Christenson and mustard seed media for creating this tutorial on how to theme views slideshow: http://mustardseedmedia.com/podcast/episode42
Thanks to Ryan Szarama for creating a tutorial on how to setup a slideshow from beginning to end. http://www.bywombats.com/blog/06-08-2010/building-rotating-image-banner-...
Demonstration of using Views Slideshow and Views Slideshow DD Block from DrupalCamp LA http://bit.ly/aZQvYx
Thanks to Ciril Tharayil for creating a tutorial on how to setup a slideshow in Drupal 7. http://www.brightwebsitedesign.com/how-to-install-views-slideshow-module...
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_xmlsitemap_7.x-2.0-beta3" name="xmlsitemap" version="7.x-2.0-beta3" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/xmlsitemap/xmlsitemap-7.x-2.0-beta3.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/xmlsitemap/xmlsitemap-7.x-2.0-beta3.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_xmlsitemap_7.x-2.0-beta3/7.x-2.0-beta3/mod_xmlsitemap_7.x-2.0-beta3-7.x-2.0-beta3.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>The XML sitemap module creates a sitemap that conforms to the sitemaps.org specification. This helps search engines to more intelligently crawl a website and keep their results up to date. The module also comes with several submodules that can add sitemap links for content, menu items, taxonomy terms, and user profiles.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>The XML sitemap module creates a sitemap that conforms to the sitemaps.org specification. This helps search engines to more intelligently crawl a website and keep their results up to date. The sitemap created by the module can be automatically submitted to Ask, Google, Bing (formerly Windows Live Search), and Yahoo! search engines. The module also comes with several submodules that can add sitemap links for content, menu items, taxonomy terms, and user profiles.

Please read the included README.txt, the handbook documentation, and the current list of known issues for more information before using the module.
Development roadmap

The 6.x-2.x branch is a complete refactoring with considerations for performance, scalability, and reliability. Upgrading from any 6.x-1.x versions is now supported, but still in testing. Before upgrading, make sure to backup your site's database. Please report feedback on the success/errors for your update. Once we get an official 6.x-2.0 version, the 6.x-1.x branch will no longer be supported. The 6.x-1.x and 5.x branches are currently closed to feature requests.
Special thanks to:

The 6.x-2.x rewrite is sponsored by Symantec, WebWise Solutions, Volacci, lanetro, Coupons Dealuxe, and the individuals that have donated using ChipIn.
Past sponsor: EmpowHer.com.
Past contributors: Matthew Loar (GSOC 2005) and Darren Oh
Community: A special thanks to all those involved who remain unnamed and have contributed time reporting issues, helping debug, or submitting patches, or have contributed financially to sponsor improvement of the module.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_taxonomy_manager_7.x-1.0-beta2" name="taxonomy_manager" version="7.x-1.0-beta2" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/taxonomy_manager/taxonomy_manager-7.x-1.0-beta2.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/taxonomy_manager/taxonomy_manager-7.x-1.0-beta2.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_taxonomy_manager_7.x-1.0-beta2/7.x-1.0-beta2/mod_taxonomy_manager_7.x-1.0-beta2-7.x-1.0-beta2.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_taxonomy__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_options__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>This module provides a powerful interface for managing taxonomies. A vocabulary gets displayed in a dynamic tree view, where parent terms can be expanded to list their nested child terms or can be collapsed.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module provides a powerful interface for managing taxonomies. A vocabulary gets displayed in a dynamic tree view, where parent terms can be expanded to list their nested child terms or can be collapsed.

The Taxonomy Manager has following operations and key features:

    dynamic treeview
    mass deleting
    mass adding of new terms
    moving of terms in hierarchies
    merging of terms (using the Term merge module in 7.x)
    fast weight changing with up and down arrows (and AJAX saving)
    AJAX powered term editing form
    simple search interface
    CSV Export of terms
    i18n support for multilingual vocabularies (per language terms)
    Double Tree interface for moving terms in hierarchies, adding new translations and switching terms between different vocabularies

For using the Taxonomy Manager you should have JavaScript and automatically load of images enabled in your browser.

This is a Google Summer of Code 2007 project. Read my proposal and my status reports for more information.

Taxonomy Manager Drupal 5 and JQuery Upadate module:
In case you are using the JQuery Update module v2.x on your D5 installation, the Taxonomy Manager won't work. See this issue for more information.
To fix the problem download the tree.js file and replace it with the one included in the taxonomy manager folder under /js.

Taxonomy Manager Drupal 6 and Panels 3 / Taxonomy Breadcrumb:
Taxonomy Manager and other taxonomy modules might conflict, if both try to override the taxonomy/term/% path. Taxonomy Manager uses this to redirect previously merged terms to their new term. If you do not need this feature or if you want to used Panels 3 / Taxonomy Breadcrumb, you can disable it under Administer &gt; Site Configuration &gt; Taxonomy Manager. See this issue for more information.
Note: since 6.x-2.1, the redirect of taxonomy/term is disabled by default</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_taxonomy_subterms_7.x-1.x-dev" name="taxonomy_subterms" version="7.x-1.x-dev" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/taxonomy_subterms/taxonomy_subterms-7.x-1.x-dev.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/taxonomy_subterms/taxonomy_subterms-7.x-1.x-dev.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_taxonomy_subterms_7.x-1.x-dev/7.x-1.x-dev/mod_taxonomy_subterms_7.x-1.x-dev-7.x-1.x-dev.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_taxonomy__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_options__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage__7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Taxonomy Subterms is a simple module to force display child taxonomy terms on the parent taxonomy page of nodes belonging to the current term or/and the children of the current term.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Taxonomy Subterms is a simple module to force display child taxonomy terms on the parent taxonomy page of nodes belonging to the current term or/and the children of the current term.

Taxonomy subterms makes use of the exact same page callback of the default taxonomy terms page (or the one you put in place).
The module just add the depth param with an 'all' value to the original arguments and pass them to the &quot;normal&quot; page callback.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_fivestar_7.x-2.0-alpha1" name="fivestar" version="7.x-2.0-alpha1" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/fivestar/fivestar-7.x-2.0-alpha1.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/fivestar/fivestar-7.x-2.0-alpha1.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_fivestar_7.x-2.0-alpha1/7.x-2.0-alpha1/mod_fivestar_7.x-2.0-alpha1-7.x-2.0-alpha1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_votingapi_7.x-2.4</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Enables fivestar ratings on content, users, etc.

The Fivestar voting module adds a clean, attractive voting widget to nodes in Drupal 5, node and comments in Drupal 6, and any entity in Drupal 7. </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module enables fivestar ratings on content, users, etc.

The Fivestar voting module adds a clean, attractive voting widget to nodes in Drupal 5, node and comments in Drupal 6, and any entity in Drupal 7.

features:

jQuery rollover effects and AJAX no-reload voting
Configurable star sets
Graceful degradation to an HTML rating form when JavaScript is turned off
Support for anonymous voters
Spam protection to keep users from filling your DB with bogus votes
Easy-to-use integration with Views module for lists sorted by rating, or filtered by min/max ratings
A Fivestar CCK field for use in custom node types
An easy-to-use Form API element type for use in other modules
Compatible with all versions of jQuery (1.0 - 1.4.4)
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_ubercart_7.x-3.0-rc2" name="ubercart" version="7.x-3.0-rc2" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/ubercart/ubercart-7.x-3.0-rc2.tar.gz" artifactId="modules/ubercart/ubercart-7.x-3.0-rc2.tar.gz">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_ubercart_7.x-3.0-rc2/7.x-3.0-rc2/mod_ubercart_7.x-3.0-rc2-7.x-3.0-rc2.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_field__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_file__7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_rules_7.x-2.0-rc2</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_views_7.x-3.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_ctools_7.x-1.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_entity_7.x-1.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Ubercart out of the box is a great solution for stores that sell physical goods, digital product downloads, and site memberships.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Ubercart out of the box is a great solution for stores that sell physical goods, digital product downloads, and site memberships.

Current Features:



Configurable product catalog includes catalog pages and a block to display product categories.
Flexible product creation system with product classes.
Multiple product image support out of the box.
Flexible product attributes system.
Basic product stock level tracking and notification.
Product features to add file downloads, role promotions, and more to products.
Single page checkout.
Automatic account generation (anonymous checkout).
Customer and administrator checkout notifications.
Simple order processing (with workflow for automated order processing).
Simple order creation and editing.
Integrated payment system that acts as a bridge between acceptable payment methods (check, credit card, purchase order, etc.) and payment gateways (CyberSource, Authorize.net, PayPal, etc.).
Shipping quotes and fulfillment, including integration with UPS, FedEx, USPS.
Sales, product, and customer reports.
Activity logging.
Much more... and more to come.

Ubercart is PayPal certified and integrates PayPal Website Payments Standard, Website Payments Pro, and Express Checkout. For more information, you can read the Ubercart PayPal information page.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_variable_7.x-1.1" name="variable" version="7.x-1.1" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/variable/variable-7.x-1.1.zip" artifactId="modules/variable/variable-7.x-1.1.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_variable_7.x-1.1/7.x-1.1/mod_variable_7.x-1.1-7.x-1.1.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>This module extends the Drupal core variable API that handles persistent variables. </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Variable module provides a registry for meta-data about Drupal variables and some extended Variable API and administration interface.

This module extends the Drupal core variable API that handles persistent variables. It implements a class that:

allows finding the directory where a library has been installed (branch 2.x for Drupal 6 and 7),
forces Drupal to re-build the menus (branch 2.x for Drupal 6 and 7),
allows obtaining the value of a persistent variable without passing the default value to each function call,
deletes multiple persistent variables,
and implements functions to centralize static PHP variables. The functions are a back port of drupal_static(), and drupal_static_reset() implemented in Drupal 7.

Installation notes

Install the module only if you are instructed to do so, or you are a developer and want to use the module.

If you are installing Variable API because it is a dependency of another module, you need to first install (and enable) Variable API, and then install (and enable) the other module. If the modules are enabled at the same time, you will get the error message class Vars not found. The same problem is actually present if you install a module that depends from the Variable API using Drush; in the moment I am writing this note, Drush will not download the Variable API module, with the consequence that you will get the error message class Vars not found.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_shopmenu_7.0" name="shopmenu" version="7.0" core="false" required="false" groupId="modules/shopmenu/shopmenu.zip" artifactId="modules/shopmenu/shopmenu.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_shopmenu_7.0/7.0/mod_shopmenu_7.0-7.0.zip</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_ubercart_7.x-3.0-rc2</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Provideds shopping cart menu and contains ubercart module altered forms.

the &quot;menu&quot; hook (shop_menu). For each merchant from whom I'm using their datafeed, I make code like this in the shop_menu function: function shop_menu($may_cache) {   $items = array();   if ($may_cache) { .... ...</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Provideds shopping cart menu and contains ubercart module altered forms.

the &quot;menu&quot; hook (shop_menu). For each merchant from whom I'm using their datafeed, I make code like this in the shop_menu function: function shop_menu($may_cache) {   $items = array();   if ($may_cache) { .... ...</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_apachesolr_7.x-1.0-beta11.zip" name="apachesolr" version="7.x-1.0-beta11.zip" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/apachesolr/apachesolr-7.x-1.0-beta11.zip" artifactId="modules/apachesolr/apachesolr-7.x-1.0-beta11.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_apachesolr_7.x-1.0-beta11.zip/7.x-1.0-beta11.zip/mod_apachesolr_7.x-1.0-beta11.zip-7.x-1.0-beta11.zip.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>This module integrates Drupal with the Apache Solr search platform. Solr search
can be used as a replacement for core content search and boasts both extra
features and better performance. Among the extra features is the ability to have
faceted search on facets ranging from content author to taxonomy to arbitrary
Field API fields.

The module comes with a schema.xml, solrconfig.xml, and protwords.txt file which
must be used in your Solr installation.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module integrates Drupal with the Apache Solr search platform. Solr search can be used as a replacement for core content search and boasts both extra features and better performance. If you're looking for Apache Solr integration, this is possibly the best option available.
Drupal 7

Drupal 7 version of the module is almost ready to go to a RC status.
Faceted search is supported if you use the facet API module. Facets will be available for you ranging from content author to taxonomy to arbitrary fields.
This version also includes :

Search Pages (Multiple search pages with optionally customized search results)
Multiple Environment (support for Multiple Solr Servers)
Range Query type, that in combination with facet API and Facet Api Slider a very rich faceting experience delivers to the end user.
Supports Custom Entity indexing through hooks. Examples such as Apachesolr Commerce,
Apachesolr User indexing and
Apachesolr Term can give you a headstart in developing your own indexing code for your entity.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_workflow_7.x-1.x-dev" name="workflow" version="7.x-1.x-dev" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/workflow/workflow-7.x-1.x-dev.zip" artifactId="modules/workflow/workflow-7.x-1.x-dev.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_workflow_7.x-1.x-dev/7.x-1.x-dev/mod_workflow_7.x-1.x-dev-7.x-1.x-dev.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>The workflow module allows the creation and assignment of arbitrary workflows to Drupal node types. Workflows are made up of workflow states. For example, a workflow with the states Draft, Review, and Published could be assigned to the Story node type.
</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>The workflow module allows the creation and assignment of arbitrary workflows to Drupal node types. Workflows are made up of workflow states. For example, a workflow with the states Draft, Review, and Published could be assigned to the Story node type.

Transitions between workflow states can have actions assigned to them. In our example, we could assign an action so that when the story moves from the Draft state to the Review state an email is sent out. Another action could be assigned to the transition from Review to Published so that the node's status is set to Published (and becomes visible on your website).

If you are interested in the future of the workflow module, please join the workflow group on groups.drupal.org.

Watch the FOSDEM 2005 video where John VanDyk presents actions and workflows if you are unfamiliar with the concepts (video is at homepage.mac.com/drupal/*-drupalconf-workflow.ogg (replace the * in the filename with the word 'please') and requires something like VLC).

With work proceeding on the Drupal 7 version of this module and Drupal 5 depreciation, if you are still using Workflow 5.x it it strongly recommended that you update your site to Drupal 6 or 7.

Notes: If you are upgrading from Drupal 6 to Drupal 7 versions of Workflow, please be aware that there has been a complete overhaul of module layout. Many features of the module have been broken out into sub module that you will need to activate. There is an UPDATE.txt file in Workflow, please read it.

Developer notes: Part of this overhaul was a change in API functions. If you are upgrading your module to support Workflow in Drupal 7 please review the available functions. In addition: $node-&gt;_workflow has been removed in favor of the more standardized $node-&gt;workflow value.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_simplesamlphp_auth_7.x-1.2" name="simplesamlphp_auth" version="7.x-1.2" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/simplesamlphp_auth/simplesamlphp_auth-7.x-1.2.zip" artifactId="modules/simplesamlphp_auth/simplesamlphp_auth-7.x-1.2.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_simplesamlphp_auth_7.x-1.2/7.x-1.2/mod_simplesamlphp_auth_7.x-1.2-7.x-1.2.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Allows users to authenticate to a remote SAML identity provider (IdP) via a locally configured SimpleSAMLphp service point (SP).</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module integrates Drupal with SimpleSAMLphp, the most robust and complete implementation of SAML in PHP. It makes it possible for Drupal to communicate with SAML or Shibboleth identity providers (IdP) for authenticating users. The resulting Drupal site can effectively act as a SAML or Shibboleth service provider (SP).</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_geolocation_7.x-1.0-beta2" name="geolocation" version="7.x-1.0-beta2" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/geolocation/geolocation-7.x-1.0-beta2.zip" artifactId="modules/geolocation/geolocation-7.x-1.0-beta2.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_geolocation_7.x-1.0-beta2/7.x-1.0-beta2/mod_geolocation_7.x-1.0-beta2-7.x-1.0-beta2.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Provides a geolocation field.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Geolocation provides a Drupal 7 field for storing Longitude/Latitude pairs. It currently supports:                          Plain text
Google Maps
Geolocation (HTML 5) Service

         This module aims to provide a simple and solid way to associate geo-information to entities. You can add Geolocation fields to content types (nodes), users, taxonomy terms, comments and all other &quot;fieldable entities&quot; provided by contrib modules, e.g. private messages (Privatemsg).</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module id="mod_bundle_copy_7.x-1.0" name="bundle_copy" version="7.x-1.0" core="true" required="false" groupId="modules/bundle_copy/bundle_copy-7.x-1.0.zip" artifactId="modules/bundle_copy/bundle_copy-7.x-1.0.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_bundle_copy_7.x-1.0/7.x-1.0/mod_bundle_copy_7.x-1.0-7.x-1.0.zip</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_ctools_7.x-1.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Import and exports bundles through the UI.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Bundle copy is a replacement for the Content copy module which lives in the CCK project for Drupal 6.

Has export/import support for:

    Node types
    Taxonomy
    User
    Field API fields
    Field groups
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
</modules>
