<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<modules xmlns="http://www.example.org/Phresco">
    <module required="true" core="true" version="7.0" name="Block" id="mod_block_7.0">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Blocks are the boxes of content (such as &quot;User Login&quot; or &quot;Who's online&quot;) that can be displayed in regions (such as footer or sidebar) on your page.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Blocks are the boxes of content (such as &quot;User Login&quot; or &quot;Who's online&quot;) that can be displayed in regions (such as footer or sidebar) on your page. Blocks are made available to your site most commonly by enabling modules. Once created, a Block can be modified to adjust its appearance, shape, size and position - or which Website pages it appears on. For example, enabling the core Poll module makes the &quot;Most Recent Polls&quot; block available for you to place in a region. The block management screen also provides checkboxes (depending on your version of Drupal and what modules you have enabled), as well as a configure link, which takes you to the configuration screen. The checkboxes and configuration page let you customize the visibility of the block. A block's visibility depends on:

1) Whether it is Enabled and assigned to a region. Disabled blocks (blocks not assigned to any region in your theme) are never shown.
2) Page-specific visibility settings. Individual blocks can be configured to only show/hide on certain pages. You can also show/hide blocks based on the result of a PHP snippet.
3)Custom visibility settings. Individual blocks can be configured so that users decide whether to show/hide certain blocks.
4)This  function. Dynamic blocks (such as those defined by modules) may be empty on certain pages and will not be shown.

The block management screen also has an &quot;Add block&quot; link. This allows you to define a block containing content of your choice. Each administrator-defined block consists of a title, a description, and a body which can be as long as you wish; the Drupal engine will render the content of the block.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="true" core="true" version="7.0" name="Field" id="mod_field_7.0">
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Field API allows custom data fields to be attached to Drupal entities and takes care of storing, loading, editing, and rendering field data.

</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Field API allows custom data fields to be attached to Drupal entities and takes care of storing, loading, editing, and rendering field data. Any entity type (node, user, etc.) can use the Field API to make itself &quot;fieldable&quot; and thus allow fields to be attached to it. Other modules can provide a user interface for managing custom fields via a web browser as well as a wide and flexible variety of data type, form element, and display format capabilities.The Field API defines two primary data structures, Field and Instance, and the concept of a Bundle. A Field defines a particular type of data that can be attached to entities.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module artifactId="Dependency removed in order to avoid cyclic dependencies" groupId="Dependency removed in order to avoid cyclic dependencies" required="true" core="true" version="7.0" name="Field SQL storage" id="mod_field_sql_storage_7.0">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Field SQL Storage module provides data management for the Field module. This module uses the Field API to generate dynamic data tables for entities and fields. While this is a required core module, it may be replaced by other contributed modules that implement The Field Storage
</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Field SQL Storage module provides data management for the Field module. This module uses the Field API to generate dynamic data tables for entities and fields. While this is a required core module, it may be replaced by other contributed modules that implement The Field Storage API. The Field SQL Storage module provides data management for the Field module. This module uses the Field API to generate dynamic data tables for entities and fields. While this is a required core module, it may be replaced by other contributed modules that implement The Field Storage API.

Field API:-The Field API allows custom data fields to be attached to Drupal entities and takes care of storing, loading, editing, and rendering field data. Any entity type (node, user, etc.) can use the Field API to make itself &quot;fieldable&quot; and thus allow fields to be attached to it. Other modules can provide a user interface for managing custom fields via a web browser as well as a wide and flexible variety of data type, form element, and display format capabilities.

The Field API defines two primary data structures, Field and Instance, and the concept of a Bundle. A Field defines a particular type of data that can be attached to entities. A Field Instance is a Field attached to a single Bundle. A Bundle is a set of fields that are treated as a group by the Field Attach API and is related to a single fieldable entity type.


</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="true" core="true" version="7.0" name="File" id="mod_file_7.0">
        <dependentModules>mod_field_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>File module enables you to upload and attach files to content and to manage these uploads if you have the appropriate permissions.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>File module enables you to upload and attach files to content and to manage these uploads if you have the appropriate permissions. This module is responsible for validating file content and managing uploaded files. It also provides options for displaying file content. As a site administrator you will be able to control what type of files can be uploaded and their maximum size.File module provides its functionality by defining a File field type for the Field module</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="true" core="true" version="7.0" name="Filter" id="mod_filter_7.0">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Filter module allows you to configure formats for text input for your site.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Filter module allows you to configure formats for text input for your site. When users create or edit content, they can choose between the input formats you make available to their user role. You can configure which formats are available to which user roles, as well as choose a default input format. You can also create new input formats. And you can configure each input format to use your choice of filters.Despite the name &quot;filter,&quot; the module not only lets you keep out text you don't want but also lets you enhance the text you let in. So, for example, you can use a filter to turn ordinary line breaks into HTML paragraph tags.when you specify more than one format for a filter you can specify the order in which they are processed.


</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="true" core="true" version="7.0" name="Node" id="mod_node_7.0">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Node is any posting, such as a page, poll, article, forum topic, or blog entry.Content on a drupal website is stored and treated as &quot;nodes.&quot;  Treating all content as nodes allows the flexibility of creating new types of content. It also allows you to painlessly apply new features or changes to all content.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Node is any posting, such as a page, poll, article, forum topic, or blog entry.Content on a drupal website is stored and treated as &quot;nodes.&quot;  Treating all content as nodes allows the flexibility of creating new types of content. It also allows you to painlessly apply new features or changes to all content.

Behind the scenes, the nodes module manages these nodes. This module is what lets you:
1) List, sort through, and manage all the content on your site.
2) Set defaults for how all posts are displayed.
3) List and configure the &quot;content types&quot; for your site, and create new ones.
Offering &quot;content types&quot; is a way Drupal allows you to have different kinds of nodes for different purposes. For example, an &quot;article&quot; is one kind of node, a &quot;book page&quot; another, and a &quot;blog entry&quot; yet another. You can also create new content types of your own.
The Node module manages the creation, editing, deletion, settings, and display of the main site content. Content items managed by the Node module are typically displayed as pages on your site, and include a title, some meta-data (author, creation time, content type, etc.), and optional fields containing text or other data. (Fields are managed by the Field module in Drupal 7.)
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="true" core="true" version="7.0" name="Options" id="mod_options_7.0">
        <dependentModules>mod_field_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Options defines selection, check box and radio button widgets for text and numeric fields.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Option module defines selection, check box and radio button widgets for text and numeric fields.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="true" core="true" version="7.0" name="System" id="mod_system_7.0">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Systems handles general site configuration for administrators.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Systems handles general site configuration for administrators. system module provides system-wide defaults for running jobs at particular times, storing (caching) web pages to improve efficiency, and performing other essential tasks. The module also keeps track of various preferences you give for how you want your system to behave.Some of Drupal's modules require regularly scheduled actions. The statistics module periodically cleans up logfiles. The aggregator module periodically updates feeds.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="true" core="true" version="7.0" name="Text" id="mod_text_7.0">
        <dependentModules>mod_field_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Text defines simple text field types.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Text module defines simple text field types.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="true" core="true" version="7.0" name="User" id="mod_user_7.0">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>User manages the user registration and login system.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>User manages the user registration and login system. 

The user module allows users to register, login, and log out. Users benefit from being able to sign on because it associates content they create with their account and allows various permissions to be set for their roles. The user module supports user roles which establish fine grained permissions allowing each role to do only what the administrator wants them to each user is assigned to one or more roles. 

By default there are two roles anonymous - a user who has not logged in, and authenticated a user who has signed up and who has been authorized. Users can use their own name or handle and can specify personal configuration settings through their individual My account page. Users must authenticate by supplying a local username and password or through their OpenID, an optional and secure method for logging into many websites with a single username and password. In some configurations, users may authenticate using a username and password from another Drupal site, or through some other site-specific mechanism.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="true" version="7.0" name="Aggregator" id="mod_aggregator_7.0">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Aggregates syndicated content (RSS, RDF, and Atom feeds).

</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Aggregates syndicated content (RSS, RDF, and Atom feeds). Aggregator module in core will aggregate RSS-feeds as &quot;lightweight&quot; items. Aggregator is a powerful on-site syndicator and news reader that gathers fresh content from RSS-, RDF-, and Atom-based feeds made available across the web. Thousands of sites (particularly news sites and blogs) publish their latest headlines and posts in feeds, using a number of standardized XML-based formats. Formats supported by the aggregator include RSS, RDF, and Atom.
 


 

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="true" version="7.0" name="Blog" id="mod_blog_7.0">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Blogs are used enable multi user blogs.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Blogs are used enable multi user blogs. The core Blog module that comes with Drupal allows every authenticated and authorized user to maintain an individual online blog. Blogs are made up of individual posts that are time stamped and are typically viewed by date as you would view a journal. Blog entries can be made public or private to the site members, depending on which roles have access to view content.

Note that the blog module is not necessary for a &quot;single-user&quot; blog, that is a site that only has one individual blogging (the most common situation). For that it's easy to create a custom content type that will accommodate. Blog module is usually used when there is a need for &quot;multi-user&quot; blogs, where many different blogs, written by different users are all running on one site. If you would like more information on creating a single-user blog, here is a Single User Blog recipe to get you started.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="true" version="7.0" name="Book" id="mod_book_7.0">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Book allows users to create and organize related content in an outline.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Book allows users to create and organize related content in an outline.Book is a set of pages tied together in a hierarchical sequence, perhaps with chapters, sections, subsections, and so on. User can use books for manuals, site resource guides, Frequently Asked Questions (FAQs), or whatever you'd like.

Users who have permission can create a book and write, review, modify, or rearrange the pages. Many users can work together on a book -- user can allow or disallow collaboration, to whatever extent user want.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="true" version="7.0" name="Color" id="mod_color_7.0">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Color allows administrators to change the color scheme of compatible themes.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Color allows administrators to change the color scheme of compatible themes.The Color module allows users with the Administer site configuration permission to quickly and easily change the color scheme of themes that have been built to be compatible with it.

In order for color module to work, a theme must be specifically designed to use the color changing features. The Drupal 6 default theme, Garland, and the Drupal 7 default theme, Bartik, were both designed to take advantage of this module. </content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="true" version="7.0" name="Comment" id="mod_comment_7.0">
        <dependentModules>mod_text_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Comment allows users to comment on and discuss published content.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Comment allows users to comment on and discuss published content. The Comment module in Drupal allows users to comment on many types of site content, as allowed by the site administrator. When Comment module is enabled, users can post comments to discuss a forum topic, a blog post, a book page, etc. Comments behave like other user submissions. Filters, smileys and HTML that work in nodes will also work with comments if configured accordingly.

As an administrator, you can specify the default comment settings for each content type. You can specify content permissions (for example, you can specify whether anonymous users can make comments). You can also specify whether comments are allowed for a specific node.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="true" version="7.0" name="Contact" id="mod_contact_7.0">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Contact enables the use of both personal and site-wide contact forms.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Contact enables the use of both personal and site-wide contact forms. Contact module allows site visitors to send emails to other authenticated users and to the site administrator.Through personal contact forms users can send one another e-mail. And through site-wide contact forms, users can send e-mail to arbitrary email addresses, such as the site maintainers.

With either form, users can specify a subject, write their message, and also have a copy of their e-mail sent to their own address. Through contact forms, users allow themselves to be contacted yet keep their own e-mail addresses private until the message is replied to. As an administrator, you can enable or disable the contact module altogether.

As a user, you can also enable or disable your personal contact form if that option has been provided. When the form is enabled, a contact tab is displayed in your user profile, for everyone to see. (Privileged users such as site administrators can contact users who have turned their forms off, as they can access their user account email addresses.) When you visit your own profile, the contact tab is not displayed. However, it is displayed to other users (if it has been enabled).</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="true" version="7.0" name="Content translation" id="mod_content_translation_7.0">
        <dependentModules>mod_locale_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Content traslation allows content to be translated into different languages.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Content traslation allows content to be translated into different languages allows (fieldable) entities to be translated into different languages, by introducing entity/field translation for the new translatable fields capability. Maintained by the Drupal core i18n team.

This project does not replace the Internationalization project, which focuses on enabling a full multilingual workflow for site admins/builders. Some features, e.g. content language negotiation or taxonomy translation, might overlap but most of them are unrelated.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="true" version="7.0" name="Contextual links" id="mod_contextual_links_7.0">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Contextual links is to perform actions related to elements on a page.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Contextual links is to perform actions related to elements on a page. User will be changing the configuration of an object navigating from that object to admin page requires many clicks there are posibilities to loss the navigation point to over come this problem we have contextual links which will have the user links in drop down . The drop down only shows the operations applicable to the object. This links are used in front-end.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="true" version="7.0" name="Dashboard" id="mod_dashboard_7.0">
        <dependentModules>mod_block_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Dashboard page in the administrative interface for organizing administrative tasks and tracking information within your site.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Dashboard gives administrators a customizable overview of important site information. You can add and remove items from the dashboard, or you can disable the dashboard completely.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="true" version="7.0" name="Database logging" id="mod_database_logging_7.0">
        <dependentModules>mod_field_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Logs and records system events to the database.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Logs and records system events to the database.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="true" version="7.0" name="Field UI" id="mod_field_ui_7.0">
        <dependentModules>mod_field_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Filed UI is used as user interface for the Field API.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Field UI is the user interface module for Field API module</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="true" version="7.0" name="Forum" id="mod_forum_7.0">
        <dependentModules>mod_field_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_options_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_taxonomy_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_comment_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_text_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Forum provides discussion forums.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Forum provides discussion forums.Forum core module lets you create threaded discussion boards, called forums, on your site. This is similar to a message board system such as phpBB. Forums are very useful because they allow community members to discuss topics with one another, and the discussions are archived for future reference.Topics, or threaded discussions, are posted to a forum. Each topic is comprised of an initial post and replies, or comments. Forum topics can have their own URLs.

Multiple forums are often set up for different areas of discussion. Forums can also be placed inside other forums for a discussion area that is a subset of the parent forum, in which case they are often called child boards or child forums.Containers can also be created to hold a group of forums. However, unlike in parent forums, topics cannot be posted to containers. Both containers and forums can be placed inside other containers and forums. By planning the structure of your containers and forums well, you make it easier for users to find a discussion area of interest to them.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="true" version="7.0" name="Help" id="mod_help_7.0">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Help manages the display of online help.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Help manages the display of online help.Help module supports Drupal's help system. It displays context-sensitive help, as well as the core Help pages provided in the administrative section.The help text provided via the Help module (via help hooks in each individual module) displays a brief explanation of various settings, uses, and configuration options, to help guide administrators and users. Administrators cannot alter the help system's text, as it is built into each module's code.

Each module's help page also references its corresponding online documentation module page. The online documentation contains more extensive and up-to-date information and serves as the definitive reference point for all Drupal documentation.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="true" version="7.0" name="Image" id="mod_image_7.0">
        <dependentModules>mod_field_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_file_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Image provides image manipulation tools.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Image provides image manipulation tools.Image module allows you to display and manipulate images on your website. It exposes a setting for using the Image toolkit, allows you to configure image styles that can be used for resizing or adjusting images on display, and provides an image field (using the Field API) for attaching images to content.Image handling is part of Drupal core.

The Image module integrates the functionalities of the Imagefield module, and also parts of the ImageCache and Image module functionalities for image manipulations.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="true" version="7.0" name="List" id="mod_list_7.0">
        <dependentModules>mod_field_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_options_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>List module defines various list field types. Use with Options to create selection lists.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>List module defines various fields for storing a list of items, for use with the Field module. Usually these items are entered through a select list, checkboxes or radio buttons. This module is an internal element of the Field API.List module defines and creates interface elements for select lists, checkboxes and radio buttons used by the Field UI. 

When creating new fields for content nodes or users, you may use the four basic list options when creating fields:
1)List.
2)Boolean.
3)List (Numeric).
4)List (Text).</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="true" version="7.0" name="Locale" id="mod_locale_7.0">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Locale adds language handling functionality and enables the translation of the user interface to languages other than English.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Locale adds language handling functionality and enables the translation of the user interface to languages other than English. When enabled, the Locale core module allows you to present your Drupal site in a language other than the default English. You can use it to set up a multilingual web site or to replace the elements of the interface text with text which has been customized for your site. Whenever the Locale module encounters text, it tries to translate it into the currently selected language. If a translation is not available, the string is remembered, so you can look up untranslated strings easily.

The Locale module provides two options for providing translations. The first is the integrated web interface, which you can used to search for untranslated strings and to specify their translations. An easier and less time-consuming method is to import existing translations for your language. These translations are available as GNU gettext Portable Object files (.po files for short). You can download translation files from the Drupal translations server.

If an existing translation does not meet your needs, the .po files are easily edited with special editing tools. The Locale module's import feature allows you to add strings from such files into your site's database. The export functionality enables you to share your translations with others, generating Portable Object files from your site strings.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="true" version="7.0" name="Menu" id="mod_menu_7.0">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Menu allows administrators to customize the site navigation menu.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Menu allows administrators to customize the site navigation menu. Menus are a collection of links (menu items) used to navigate a website. The Menu module provides an interface to control and customize the powerful menu system that comes with Drupal. Menus are primarily displayed as a hierarchical list of links using Drupal's highly flexible blocks feature. Each menu automatically creates a block of the same name. By default, new menu items are placed inside a built-in menu labeled Navigation, but administrators can also create custom menus.

user can add, remove and rename menus and menu items. You can also configure a special block for a menu and you can specify the default menu to which new items will be added.In many themes there are at least two menus, the Main (or primary) menu, and a secondary menu. The Main menu's links drive the main navigation structure for your site, and are often displayed prominently across the top or side of the site. The Secondary menu is often used for items like the copyright and privacy notices and are often displayed at the bottom or very top of the page in smaller text. You can specify which menus are used for the main and secondary links.

When adding or editing site content, you can also specify the content's menu item. user can specify a default menu for the content authoring form. Each default or custom menu has a corresponding block.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="true" version="7.0" name="Number" id="mod_number_7.0">
        <dependentModules>mod_field_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Number defines numeric field types.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Number defines numeric field types.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="true" version="7.0" name="OpenID" id="mod_openid_7.0">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Open ID allows users to log into your site using OpenID.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Open ID allows users to log into your site using OpenID. The OpenID module adds a feature to the User login block and displays a new link allowing a user to sign in using OpenID. OpenID is a secure method for logging into many websites with a single username and password. It does not require special software, and it does not share passwords with any site to which it is associated; including your site.

Users can create Drupal accounts using their OpenID. This lowers the barrier to registration, which is good for the site, and offers convenience and security to the users. OpenID is not a trust system, so email verification is still necessary. The benefit stems from the fact that users can have a single password that they can use on many websites. This means they can easily update their single password from a centralized location, rather than having to change dozens of passwords individually.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="true" version="7.0" name="Overlay" id="mod_overlay_7.0">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Overlay displays the drupal administration interface in an overlay.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Overlay displays the drupal administration interface in an overlay. The administrative overlay makes it easier to administer a Drupal site by displaying administrative pages as a layer over the current page (using JavaScript), rather than replacing the page in your browser window. Once an overlay is active, you can use the close link on the overlay to return to the page you were viewing before you clicked the link. In a &quot;Standard&quot; install, the Overlay module is enabled by default. 

When enabled, the overlay will appear when you click on administrative links. If you manually enter a URL in your browser, overlay will not be used. To reset so that overlay is used again, leave the admin section of your site, then return to the page on which you want to use overlay.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="true" version="7.0" name="Path" id="mod_path_7.0">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Path allows users to rename URLs.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Path allows users to rename URLs. The core Path module lets you optionally create URL aliases for your Drupal pages. By default, Drupal automatically creates web addresses like http://www.example.com/?q=node/67, which are not user- or search engine-friendly. Search engines will give better rankings to pages that have more human-friendly URLs, especially if they include relevant keywords - for instance, http://www.example.com/?q=all-about-tarantulas.

Using Path module:

1)Set the path for an individual node with the Path module (on the node/add or node edit form).
2) Add a URL alias at Administer &gt; Configuration &gt; Search and metadata &gt; URL aliases in Drupal 7, Administer &gt; Site building &gt; URL aliases &gt; add alias in Drupal 6.
3)Administer the list of URL aliases at Administer &gt; Configuration &gt; Search and metadata in Drupal 7; Administer &gt; Site building &gt; URL aliases in Drupal 6.

When combined with using Drupal's &quot;Clean URLs&quot; feature http://www.example.com/?q=all-about-tarantulas becomes www.example.com/all-about-tarantulas, which is the ideal readable form.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="true" version="7.0" name="PHP filter" id="mod_php_filter_7.0">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Php filter allows embedded PHP code/snippets to be evaluated.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Php filter allows embedded PHP code/snippets to be evaluated.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="true" version="7.0" name="Poll" id="mod_poll_7.0">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Poll  allows your site to capture votes on different topics in the form of multiple choice questions.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Poll  allows your site to capture votes on different topics in the form of multiple choice questions.The Poll core module lets you create simple polls. You ask a question, provide possible answers, and let your users vote. Drupal then keeps a running tally of the results. When you create a poll you can also specify the &quot;base&quot; vote counts (how many votes an item has at the start) and decide how long the voting will run. The poll item in the navigation menu will take users to a page where they can see all of the current polls, vote on them (if they haven't already) and view the results.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="true" version="7.0" name="RDF" id="mod_rdf_7.0">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>RDF Enriches your content with metadata to let other applications (e.g. search engines, aggregators) better understand its relationships and attributes.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>RDF Enriches your content with metadata to let other applications (e.g. search engines, aggregators) better understand its relationships and attributes.

The Resource Description Framework project is an ensemble of modules providing comprehensive RDF functionality and interoperability.RDF is a W3C standard for modeling and sharing distributed knowledge based on a decentralized open-world assumption. Any knowledge about anything can be decomposed into triples (3-tuples) consisting of subject, predicate, and object; essentially, RDF is the lowest common denominator for exchanging data between systems.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="true" version="7.0" name="Search" id="mod_search_7.0">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Search enables site-wide keyword searching.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Search enables site-wide keyword searching. Search module lets users search for specific content on your site. You can search both for users and for particular words. When you are on the &quot;content&quot; tab of Search, you will be able to search for words appearing in the default rendering of node content on your site, which would include the default rendering of any CCK fields, Location fields, Taxonomy, etc., as well as comments. When you are on the &quot;users&quot; tab of Search, you will be able to search the user names of registered users on your site, and if you have sufficient permissions, also their email addresses.

In Content search, if you enter more than one search term the search module will look for content that has all the terms you've entered. If instead you want either one term or another, join your terms with &quot;or.&quot; If you're looking for an exact phrase, enclose it in quotation marks.

With Advanced Search you can also look for &quot;any of these words&quot; or &quot;this phrase,&quot; or both, you can rule out words you don't want, and you can choose content types within which to confine your search.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="true" version="7.0" name="Shortcut" id="mod_shortcut_7.0">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Shortcut allows users to manage customizable lists of shortcut links.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Shortcut allows users to manage customizable lists of shortcut links. The Shortcut module provides a toolbar on the top of the page to which you can add links. This is useful for creating links to commonly-used pages within your site. You can organize these links in multiple sets of shortcuts. By default, two links are available in your shortcut toolbar: &quot;Add content&quot; and &quot;Find content&quot;. To add and edit shortcuts click the &quot;Edit shortcuts&quot; link in the toolbar.

The core Seven administration theme displays a + sign next to the page title which allows you to create a shortcut to that page. (With the overlay module active, the page title appears above the overlay, not under the breadcrumbs as you see here.) If the page is already part of your shortcut set, the link will be a - sign, to remove the shortcut.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="true" version="7.0" name="Statistics" id="mod_statistics_7.0">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Statistics Logs access statistics for your site.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Statistics Logs access statistics for your site.

The Statistics module shows you how often a given page is viewed, who viewed it, the previous page the user visited (referrer URL), and when it was viewed. These statistics are useful in determining how users are visiting and navigating your site.

To enable collection of statistics, the Enable access log checkbox on the Statistics settings page must be checked. This access log is used to store data about every page accessed, such as the remote host's IP address, where they came from (referrer), what node they've viewed, and their user name. Enabling the log adds one database call per page displayed by Drupal.

The Discard access logs older than setting on the settings page specifies the length of time entries are kept in the log before they are deleted. This setting requires a correctly configured cron maintenance task to run.

Enable Count content views to turn on and off the node-counting functionality of this module. If it is turned on, an extra database query is added for each node displayed, which increments a counter.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="true" version="7.0" name="Syslog" id="mod_syslog_7.0">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Syslog logs and records system events to syslog.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Syslog logs and records system events to syslog. Syslog is an operating system administration logging tool, where messages are routed by facility and severity. It is more suitable for medium to large sites, and would not be suitable for shared hosting environments. In the file /etc/syslog.conf you define where messages go for any combination of facility and severity.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="true" version="7.0" name="Taxonomy" id="mod_taxonomy_7.0">
        <dependentModules>mod_field_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_options_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Taxonomy enables the categorization of content.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Taxonomy, a powerful core module, gives your sites use of the organizational keywords known in other systems as categories, tags, or metadata. In Drupal, these terms are gathered within &quot;vocabularies.&quot; The Taxonomy module allows you to create, manage and apply those vocabularies.
Taxonomy is the practice of classifying content. It will come in handy for everything from menu and navigation schemes to view and display options.Many contributed modules rely on Taxonomy--generating, for example, menus based on existing tags.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="true" version="7.0" name="Testing" id="mod_testing_7.0">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Testing provides a framework for unit and functional testing.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Testing provides a framework for unit and functional testing.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="true" version="7.0" name="Tracker" id="mod_tracker_7.0">
        <dependentModules>mod_field_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_text_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_comment_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Tracker enables tracking of recent content for users.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Tracker enables tracking of recent content for users.The Tracker core module displays a site's most recently added or updated content. The Tracker module also provides user level tracking, which allows you to follow the contributions of specific authors. The Recent content page contains a reverse chronological list of new and recently updated content. The list displays the content type, the title, the author's username, how many comments that item has received, and when it was last updated. Updates include any changes to the text, either by the original author or someone else, as well as any new comments added to an item. A red &quot;new&quot; will display beside the name of each node the current user has not yet navigated to. The My recent content tab on this page limits the list to the currently logged-in user.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="true" version="7.0" name="Trigger" id="mod_trigger_7.0">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Trigger enables actions to be fired on certain system events, such as when new content is created.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Trigger enables actions to be fired on certain system events, such as when new content is created. The Trigger module provides the ability to take a particular action when a trigger occurs. Actions include functional tasks that are defined by Drupal core modules, and advanced actions that can be defined by the system administrator. Contributed modules can introduce new actions. Some examples of actions are sending an email, publishing a node, banning a user or promoting a node to the front page of a website. Triggers are defined by modules, and typically result from some characteristic change in an entity maintained by that module. Some examples of triggers are: deleting content, adding a comment, a user has logged in, or adding a term. In addition to the triggers provided by Drupal core modules, more triggers may be added by installed contributed modules.

Trigger module allows you to perform useful tasks by associating actions with specific triggers, such as e-mailing an administrator (the action) when a user account is deleted (the trigger), or automatically unpublishing a comment (the action) if the added comment (the trigger) contains certain words.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="true" version="7.0" name="Update manager" id="mod_update_manager_7.0">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Update manager checks for available updates, and can securely install or update modules and themes via a web interface.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Update manager checks for available updates, and can securely install or update modules and themes via a web interface.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="true" version="7.0" name="Toolbar" id="mod_toolbar_7.0">
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Toolbar provides a toolbar that shows the top-level administration menu items and links from other modules.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Toolbar provides a toolbar that shows the top-level administration menu items and links from other modules.The administrative toolbar gives you quick access to the most important administrative pages. The Toolbar module is enabled by default (unless you choose the &quot;Minimal&quot; profile when installing).</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0-rc1" name="ACL - Access control list" id="mod_acl_-_access_control_list_7.x-1.0-rc1">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_acl_-_access_control_list_7.x-1.0-rc1/7.x-1.0-rc1/mod_acl_-_access_control_list_7.x-1.0-rc1-7.x-1.0-rc1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>ACL -Access control list API. Has no features on its own.
</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Access control list API. Has no features on its own.The ACL module, short for Access Control Lists, is an API for other modules to create lists of users and give them access to nodes. It has no UI of its own and will not do anything by itself; install this module only if some other module tells you to.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-3.1" name="AddToAny Share/Bookmark Button" id="mod_addtoany_share/bookmark_button_7.x-3.1">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_addtoany_share/bookmark_button_7.x-3.1/7.x-3.1/mod_addtoany_share/bookmark_button_7.x-3.1-7.x-3.1.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Add to any helps readers share, bookmark, and email your articles and pages using any service, such as Facebook, Twitter, Delicious, Digg, and over 100 more using the AddToAny widget.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Add to any helps readers share, bookmark, and email your articles and pages using any service, such as Facebook, Twitter, Delicious, Digg, and over 100 more using the AddToAny widget.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-2.2" name="Backup and Migrate" id="mod_backup_and_migrate_7.x-2.2">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_backup_and_migrate_7.x-2.2/7.x-2.2/mod_backup_and_migrate_7.x-2.2-7.x-2.2.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Backup or migrate the Drupal Database quickly and without unnecessary data.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Backup and Migrate simplifies the task of backing up and restoring your Drupal database or copying your database from one Drupal site to another. It supports gzip, bzip and zip compression as well as automatic scheduled backups.Backup or migrate the Drupal Database quickly and without unnecessary data.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0-rc1" name="Chaos tool suite" id="mod_chaos_tool_suite_7.x-1.0-rc1">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_chaos_tool_suite_7.x-1.0-rc1/7.x-1.0-rc1/mod_chaos_tool_suite_7.x-1.0-rc1-7.x-1.0-rc1.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Chaos tool suite is a library of helpful tools by Merlin of Chaos.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Chaos tool suite is primarily a set of APIs and tools to improve the developer experience. It also contains a module called the Page Manager whose job is to manage pages. In particular it manages panel pages, but as it grows it will be able to manage far more than just Panels..A library of helpful tools by Merlin of Chaos.For the moment, it includes the following tools:

1)Plugins -- tools to make it easy for modules to let other modules implement plugins from .inc files.
2)Exportables -- tools to make it easier for modules to have objects that live in database or live in code, such as 'default views'.
3)AJAX responder -- tools to make it easier for the server to handle AJAX requests and tell the client what to do with them.
4)Form tools -- tools to make it easier for forms to deal with AJAX.
5)Object caching -- tool to make it easier to edit an object across multiple page requests and cache the editing work.
6)Contexts -- the notion of wrapping objects in a unified wrapper and providing an API to create and accept these contexts as input.
7)Modal dialog -- tool to make it simple to put a form in a modal dialog.
8)Dependent -- a simple form widget to make form items appear and disappear based upon the selections in another item.
9)Content -- pluggable content types used as panes in Panels and other modules like Dashboard.
10)Form wizard -- an API to make multi-step forms much easier.
11)CSS tools -- tools to cache and sanitize CSS easily to make user-input CSS safe.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.3" name="CKEditor - WYSIWYG HTML editor" id="mod_ckeditor_-_wysiwyg_html_editor_7.x-1.3">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_ckeditor_-_wysiwyg_html_editor_7.x-1.3/7.x-1.3/mod_ckeditor_-_wysiwyg_html_editor_7.x-1.3-7.x-1.3.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>CKEditor  module will allow Drupal to replace textarea fields with the CKEditor - a visual HTML editor, sometimes called WYSIWYG editor. This HTML text editor brings many of the powerful WYSIWYG editing functions of known desktop editors like Word to the web. It's very fast and doesn't require any kind of installation on the client computer.Enables the usage of CKEditor (WYSIWYG) instead of plain text fields.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>CKEditor module will allow Drupal to replace textarea fields with the CKEditor - a visual HTML editor, sometimes called WYSIWYG editor. This HTML text editor brings many of the powerful WYSIWYG editing functions of known desktop editors like Word to the web. It's very fast and doesn't require any kind of installation on the client computer.It enables the usage of CKEditor (WYSIWYG) instead of plain text fields.CKEditor is the next version of FCKeditor. The editor has been rebranded and completely rewritten. It is now much faster (the code has been optimized), loads faster (the number of files has been reduced, so the browser will perform less HTTP requests) and developers friendly.

1)End user features
2)Developer features

Features of CKEditor module:

1)Ready to use plugins and buttons for &lt;!--break--&gt;and &lt;!--pagebreak--&gt; tags
2)Support for external file browsers, like CKFinder, IMCE
3)CKEditor Link support for easily create links to Drupal internal paths
4)CKEditor SWF support for enhance functionality of Flash embedding plugin
5)Linkit support for internal linking to nodes, users, views and terms using an autocomplete field
6)Each user may have it's own configuration (choose skin, toolbar, language, default state of CKEditor, etc.)
and much more!
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.2" name="Colorbox" id="mod_colorbox_7.x-1.2">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_colorbox_7.x-1.2/7.x-1.2/mod_colorbox_7.x-1.2-7.x-1.2.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Color box is a light-weight, customizable lightbox plugin for jQuery 1.3 through 1.6.

 </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Color box is a light-weight, customizable lightbox plugin for jQuery 1.3 through 1.6. Colorbox example with the default style this module allows for integration of Colorbox into Drupal.

Images, iframed or inline content etc. can be displayed in a overlay above the current page.

Colorbox example with the default style.Colorbox is a light-weight, customizable lightbox plugin for jQuery 1.3 through 1.6. This module allows for integration of Colorbox into Drupal.Images, iframed or inline content etc. can be displayed in a overlay above the current page.A light-weight, customizable lightbox plugin for jQuery 1.3 through 1.6.

Colorbox module:
1)Excellent integration with Imagefield, Imagecache and Insert modules.
2)Integration Image module.
3)Choose between a default style and a number of other styles that are included.
4)Style the Colorbox with a custom Colorbox style in your theme.
5)Drush command to download and install the Colorbox plugin in sites/all/libraries.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0-rc1" name="Comment notify" id="mod_comment_notify_7.x-1.0-rc1">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_comment_notify_7.x-1.0-rc1/7.x-1.0-rc1/mod_comment_notify_7.x-1.0-rc1-7.x-1.0-rc1.zip</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_comment_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_text_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_token_7.x-1.0-beta5</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Comment notify follow-up e-mail notification for anonymous as well as registered users.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Comment follow-up e-mail notification for anonymous as well as registered users.Comment notify is a lightweight tool to send notification e-mails to visitors about new, published comments on pages where they have commented. Comment notify works for both registered and anonymous users.

Providing comment notifications for anonymous users is an important tool in bringing anonymous users back to your site, which helps convert anonymous users to registered users. Anonymous comment notification is a critical tool in building a blog comment community; all the major blogging platforms include this functionality.Many other notification modules do not allow notifications for anonymous users but comment notify does. On the other hand, comment notify's goal of being lightweight means it is missing lots of features. Learn more about different notification modules.)


</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-2.0-rc2" name="Rules" id="mod_rules_7.x-2.0-rc2">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_rules_7.x-2.0-rc2/7.x-2.0-rc2/mod_rules_7.x-2.0-rc2-7.x-2.0-rc2.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_token_7.x-1.0-beta5</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Rules react on events and conditionally evaluate actions.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Rules module allows site administrators to define conditionally executed actions based on occurring events (known as reactive or ECA rules). It's a replacement with more features for the trigger module in core and the successor of the Drupal 5 workflow-ng module.It allows site administrators to define conditionally executed actions based on occurring events.

Features

1)Obviously, you may use reaction rules to react upon any event with custom conditions and actions.
2)Allows functionality to be re-used via components (Drupal 6: Rule sets only).
3)Flexible scheduling system that allows scheduling any component / action.
4)Users can share their customizations by using the built-in import/export feature. For that the module also integrates with Features.
5)Modular input evaluation system - for example you can install the Token module and use it in every action.
6)The module has been developed with site performance in mind, so it makes use of caching routines to speed up rule evaluation.
7)Rules 2.x (Drupal 7 only) features improved APIs, a new admin UI, support for all entity types, parameter configuration via simple data selection (i.e. just pass node:author as argument) and much more. See this blog post for more details.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.2" name="Devel" id="mod_devel_7.x-1.2">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_devel_7.x-1.2/7.x-1.2/mod_devel_7.x-1.2-7.x-1.2.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Devel used for various blocks, pages, and functions for developers.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Devel used for various blocks, pages, and functions for developers. A suite of modules containing fun for module developers and themers . Helper functions for Drupal developers and inquisitive admins. This module can print a summary of all database queries for each page request at the bottom of each page. The summary includes how many times each query was executed on a page (shouldn't run same query multiple times), and how long each query took (short is good - use cache for complex queries).Various blocks, pages, and functions for developers.
Also a dprint_r($array) function is provided, which pretty prints arrays. Useful during development. Similarly, a ddebug_backtrace() is offerred.
much more. 

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-2.0" name="Diff" id="mod_diff_7.x-2.0">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_diff_7.x-2.0/7.x-2.0/mod_diff_7.x-2.0-7.x-2.0.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Diff show difference between node revisions.
 

</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Diff  module adds a tab for sufficiently permissioned users. The tab shows all revisions like standard Drupal but it also allows pretty viewing of all added/changed/deleted words between revisions.Show difference between node revisions.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0" name="Email Field" id="mod_email_field_7.x-1.0">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_email_field_7.x-1.0/7.x-1.0/mod_email_field_7.x-1.0-7.x-1.0.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Email field module defines an email field type.
 </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>EmailField module provides a field type for email addresses.

Features:
1)Validation of emails.
2)Turns addresses into mailto links.
3)Encryption of email addresses with.
4)Invisimail (Drupal 5 + 6).
5)SpamSpan (Drupal 6 only).
6)contact form (see Display settings).
7)provides Tokens (for D7: use Entity tokens from the Entity API).
10)exposes fields to Views.
11)can be used with Rules.
12)Panels Integration.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0" name="Currency Exchange" id="mod_currency_exchange_7.x-1.0">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_currency_exchange_7.x-1.0/7.x-1.0/mod_currency_exchange_7.x-1.0-7.x-1.0.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Currency Exchange module provides visitors to your web site with currency exchange rates. Provides feature management for Drupal.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Currency exchange module provides visitors to your web site with currency exchange rates. 

Features

1)This module provides several options that customize its look and feel:
2)An overview section on the top of the page can contain any text you want.
3)Users can enter an amount, and that amount will calculated in the target currency.
4)Provides a link to a detailed history and chart page on Yahoo Finance.
5)All currency exchange operations are logged to the watchdog (optional).
6)Provides a callable API for other modules to do currency exchange calculations.

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0-rc1" name="Nice messages" id="mod_nice_messages_7.x-1.0-rc1">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_nice_messages_7.x-1.0-rc1/7.x-1.0-rc1/mod_nice_messages_7.x-1.0-rc1-7.x-1.0-rc1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Nice messages module changes the way Drupal messages are showing up using stylable jQuery-popups provided by the small and fast jGrowl plugin.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Nice messages module changes the way Drupal messages are showing up using stylable jQuery-popups provided by the small and fast jGrowl plugin. It prevends breaking the look and feel of a website by the massive red, yellow and green boxes showing up frequently when Drupal message system is invoked. Apart from other jQuery plugin libraries like Purr and similar, the jQuery jGrowl plugin supports all browsers including older Browsers like IE6, has only a small size of only 6kb.

.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.3" name="Agenda" id="mod_agenda_7.x-1.3">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_agenda_7.x-1.3/7.x-1.3/mod_agenda_7.x-1.3-7.x-1.3.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_block_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Agenda module allows you to display a list of upcoming events from Google Calendar as a block on your website.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Agenda module allows you to display a list of upcoming events from Google Calendar as a block on your website.The events are automatically downloaded and cached from the Calendar IDs specified in the Agenda administration page. Unlimited calendars can be added, and the colours for each calendar can be specified in the CSS file.The output is fully themeable, and uses jQuery for dynamic effects such as rounded corners, and click-toggling extra information.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.4" name="FileField Sources" id="mod_filefield_sources_7.x-1.4">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_filefield_sources_7.x-1.4/7.x-1.4/mod_filefield_sources_7.x-1.4-7.x-1.4.zip</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_file_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>FileField sources provides a universal file upload field for CCK. </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>FileField Sources is an extension to the FileField module. The FileField module lets you upload files from your computer through a CCK field. The FileField Sources module expands on this ability by allowing you to select new or existing files through additional means, including:

1)Re-use files by an auto-complete textfield.
2) Attach server-side files uploaded via FTP.
3)Transfer files from a remote server (cURL required).
4)Select existing files through the IMCE file browser.

Although FileField Sources provides several built-in sources, it can be extended by any module through an API for creating new sources. Users can toggle between any of the available methods for selecting a file.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0-rc1" name="Frequently Asked Questions" id="mod_frequently_asked_questions_7.x-1.0-rc1">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_frequently_asked_questions_7.x-1.0-rc1/7.x-1.0-rc1/mod_frequently_asked_questions_7.x-1.0-rc1-7.x-1.0-rc1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Frequently asked questions manages configuration of questions for a FAQ page.
 </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Frequently asked question module manages configuration of questions for a FAQ page.The 'faq' page is automatically generated from the FAQ nodes configured. Basic Views layouts are also provided and can be customised via the Views UI (rather than via the module settings page).

Features

The layout of the FAQ page can be modified on the settings page. There are four question and answer layouts to choose from. In addition, if the 'Taxonomy' module is enabled, it is possible to put the questions into different categories when editing. Users will need the 'view faq page' permission to view the built-in 'faq' page and will need the 'administer faq' permission to configure the layout, etc.There are 3 blocks included in this module. The first shows a list of FAQ categories. The other two can show a configurable number of FAQs - one shows recent FAQs, while the other just displays random ones. </content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-2.0" name="Front Page" id="mod_front_page_7.x-2.0">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_front_page_7.x-2.0/7.x-2.0/mod_front_page_7.x-2.0-7.x-2.0.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Front page allows site admins setup custom front pages for the site.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Front Page module allows for customised home pages dependant on role. The pages can be of the following types:This module allows site admins setup custom front pages for the site.

1)Alias (only 2.x branch) - Allows for another Drupal path to be shown as the home page without redirecting the user.
2)Redirect - Allows you to redirect users to a local or remote URL.
3)Themed - Allows you to enter some static text that will be placed into the content area of a standard Drupal page.
4)Full - Allows for static content to be displayed to the screen as is. This method does not pass through Drupal's theming system.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0" name="getID3()" id="mod_getid3()_7.x-1.0">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_getid3()_7.x-1.0/7.x-1.0/mod_getid3()_7.x-1.0-7.x-1.0.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>getID3() extracts useful information from multimedia file formats</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>The getID3() Drupal module facilitates the installation and management of the getID3() PHP library, used to extract useful information from MP3s and other multimedia file formats.

This API module is used by other modules to ensure that getID3() is correctly installed. Developers who need the getID3() functionality can make this a dependency by their module, and then call the getid3_load() function to properly use the getID3() library without having to worry about whether it's installed or not..It extracts useful information from multimedia file formats.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.3" name="Global Redirect" id="mod_global_redirect_7.x-1.3">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_global_redirect_7.x-1.3/7.x-1.3/mod_global_redirect_7.x-1.3-7.x-1.3.zip</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_redirect_7.x-1.0-beta3</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>GlobalRedirect searches for an alias of the current URL and 301 redirects if found. Stops duplicate content arising when path module is enabled.
</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>GlobalRedirect is a simple module which checks the current URL for an alias and does a 301 redirect to it if it is not being used..Searches for an alias of the current URL and 301 redirects if found. Stops duplicate content arising when path module is enabled..Searches for an alias of the current URL.

Checks the current URL for a trailing slash, removes it if present and repeats check 1 with the new request. 
1)Checks if the current URL is the same as the site_frontpage and redirects to the frontpage if there is a match. 
2)Checks if the Clean URLs feature is enabled and then checks the current URL is being accessed using the clean method rather than the 'unclean' method. 
3)Checks access to the URL. If the user does not have access to the path, then no redirects are done. This helps avoid exposing private aliased node's. 
4)Make sure the case of the URL being accessed is the same as the one set by the author/administrator. For example, if you set the alias &quot;articles/cake-making&quot; to node/123, then the user can access the alias with any combination of case. 
5)Most of the above options are configurable in the settings page. In Drupal 5 you can access this after enabling the globalredirect_admin module. In Drupal 6, the settings page is bundled into the module.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.2" name="Google Analytics" id="mod_google_analytics_7.x-1.2">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_google_analytics_7.x-1.2/7.x-1.2/mod_google_analytics_7.x-1.2-7.x-1.2.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Google analytics allows your site to be tracked by Google Analytics by adding a Javascript tracking code to every page.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Adds the Google Analytics web statistics tracking system to your website.

The module allows you to add the following statistics features to your site:

1)Single/multi/cross domain tracking
2)Selectively track/exclude certain users, roles and pages
3)Monitor what type of links are tracked (downloads, outgoing and mailto)
4)Monitor what files are downloaded from your pages
5)Custom variables support with tokens
6)Custom code snippets
7)Site Search support
8)AdSense support
9)Tracking of Goals
10)Anonymize visitors IP address
11)Cache the Google Analytics code on your local server for improved page loading times
12)Access denied (403) and Page not found (404) tracking
13)DoNotTrack support (non-cached content only)
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0" name="Search Autocomplete" id="mod_search_autocomplete_7.x-1.0">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_search_autocomplete_7.x-1.0/7.x-1.0/mod_search_autocomplete_7.x-1.0-7.x-1.0.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_search_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Search autocomplete module allows you to add autocomplete functionality to the search fields of a Drupal site.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Search autocomplete module allows you to add autocomplete functionality to the search fields of a Drupal site. During the input, the field will be expanded and offer a list of suggestions before you start the search. The module integrates with search forms from the Drupal core Search.Provides aucompletion for Drupal search forms.

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.13" name="Image Resize Filter" id="mod_image_resize_filter_7.x-1.13">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_image_resize_filter_7.x-1.13/7.x-1.13/mod_image_resize_filter_7.x-1.13-7.x-1.13.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Image resize filter  is used to automatically scale images to their height and width dimensions.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Image resize filter  is used to automatically scale images to their height and width dimensions.This filter makes it easy to resize images, especially when combined with a WYSIWYG editor such as tinyMCE or CKeditor. Users never have to worry about scaling image sizes again, just insert an image and set it's height and width properties in HTML (this is done automatically by WYSIWYG editors) and the image is resized on output to match the HTML.

Features:

1)Automatically resizes both local and (optionally) remote images.
2)Optionally create a link to full size images from the resized inline versions.
3)Prevents inline &quot;hot linking&quot; of images from other sites by storing them locally.
4)Adds height and width attributes to inline images when your users are too lazy to add them.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0-rc2" name="ImageCache Profiles" id="mod_imagecache_profiles_7.x-1.0-rc2">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_imagecache_profiles_7.x-1.0-rc2/7.x-1.0-rc2/mod_imagecache_profiles_7.x-1.0-rc2-7.x-1.0-rc2.zip</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_file_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_image_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Image cache profiles utilizes image styles for user profile pictures.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>ImageCache_Profiles module allows you to set user profile pictures that are consistent throughout your site and allows avatars on the user profile pages, nodes and comments to be a different size. </content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.1" name="PayPal API" id="mod_paypal_api_7.x-1.1">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_paypal_api_7.x-1.1/7.x-1.1/mod_paypal_api_7.x-1.1-7.x-1.1.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Implements the Paypal API for Drupal sites.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Implements the Paypal API for Drupal sites.With this module you may configure content types to require payment for creating or viewing. You may further limit viewing to payment per instance, or payment to view any instance of a given type. .Implements the PayPal API for Drupal sites. 
This module does not seek to be a full-blown e-commerce system, so it will never provide a shopping cart or other e-commerce tools.Rather, it allows developers to build e-commerce systems, using this module for the payment gateway.Out of the box, you can configure the system to require payment to view or create given content. Paypal API manages a simple ledger to control user access to paid content.Payments may be configured to be made either through a Pay Now button you create through your Paypal account, or Paypal API can create them for you.

If you choose to use the Paypal API, you will need to store your Paypal account email in your Drupal web site. Use of Pay Now buttons created through your control panel do not have this requirement.Either way, the Paypal API module handles your IPN (instant payment notification) for you, and you may create custom code in your own module to handle the payment notification (through hook_paypal_api_ipn()) or else query Paypal API as necessary. See paypal_api.api.php in this package for more documentation. 
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0" name="Imagefield Crop" id="mod_imagefield_crop_7.x-1.0">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_imagefield_crop_7.x-1.0/7.x-1.0/mod_imagefield_crop_7.x-1.0-7.x-1.0.zip</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_file_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_image_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Image field crop add cropping ability to images using javascript. 

</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Image field crop add cropping ability to images using javascript. imagefield_crop provides a widget for cropping an image after upload. When the user uploads an image, the image is presented inside a cropping area. A cropping box is shown inside, and the user can resize and move it. Upon clicking 'preview' or 'submit', the image is cropped and the result is saved instead of the original image. Watch the screencast by capellic (Note: the screencast was made for the 6.x version of this module).

Features
1)Seamless, intuitive cropping, almost like using a desktop photo editing app
2)All major browsers supported
3)Dynamic preview - you see how your crop will look like, in real time!
4)Original image is saved for recropping.
5)No matter what resolution the cropping area is, the original image is used for cropping (for highest quality)
6)The sizes of the cropping area, cropping box and resulting image can be controlled by the administrator

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0" name="Star Rating" id="mod_star_rating_7.x-1.0">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_star_rating_7.x-1.0/7.x-1.0/mod_star_rating_7.x-1.0-7.x-1.0.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Star Rating is a simple module that provides star rating field and display formatter using Drupal 7's Field Type API.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Star Rating is a simple module that provides star rating field and display formatter using Drupal 7's Field Type API.It provides star rating field type and formatter Unlike Fivestar module and other voting/rating module, it supports neither end user voting nor nice AJAX interface. It is inteded for the rating only by the author of the article (node). Of course, you may be able to do this with Fivestar module and other voting/rating modules, but unlike most of them, it does not require other modules such as voting API module. It's born to be simple but good enough for those who want star rating only by authors.

For example, if you are creating a restaurant review web site and you want to add three 5 star ratings (food, price and service) with different icon type for each rating within a node, then this module would be the best match.

Features

1)Very simple and no other modules required.
2)Utilizes Drupal 7's Field API.
3)Fully supports Views module.
4)Different icon type and color can be assigned for each field and each view mode. (Total 16 icon type x 8 colors = 128 different icons)
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.1" name="Insert" id="mod_insert_7.x-1.1">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_insert_7.x-1.1/7.x-1.1/mod_insert_7.x-1.1-7.x-1.1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Insert is a utility that makes inserting images and links to files into text areas or WYSIWYGs much easier.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Insert is a utility that makes inserting images and links to files into text areas or WYSIWYGs much easier. It adds a simple JavaScript-based button to FileField and ImageField widgets. When used with ImageField and ImageCache, images may be inserted into text areas with a specific ImageCache preset.This module was previously known as FileField Insert.

Features
1)Support for all major WYSIWYG editors, including tinyMCE, CKeditor, the WYSIWYG project (the recommended approach), and plain text areas.
2)Insert images using ImageCache presets
3)Maximum width setting for inserted images (for combined use with the Image Resize Filter module)
4)Per-field insert configuration
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="i18n-7.x-1.0" name="Internationalization" id="mod_internationalization_i18n-7.x-1.0">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_internationalization_i18n-7.x-1.0/i18n-7.x-1.0/mod_internationalization_i18n-7.x-1.0-i18n-7.x-1.0.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:nil="true"/>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Internationalization extends Drupal support for multilingual features.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Internationalization is a collection of modules to extend Drupal core multilingual capabilities and be able to build real life multilingual sites. 

Features:
1)Taxonomy translation (both, per language terms and translatable terms)
2)Multilingual variables
3)Multilingual blocks (control visibility per language and translate title and content)
4)Language selection (when you switch the site language you'll see only the content for that language)</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0" name="JQuery plugins" id="mod_jquery_plugins_7.x-1.0">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_jquery_plugins_7.x-1.0/7.x-1.0/mod_jquery_plugins_7.x-1.0-7.x-1.0.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content> Jquery plugin module allows you to load miscellaneous jQuery plugins.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>jQuery plugins module allows you to load miscellaneous jQuery plugins  from any module.

The goal of this project is to reduce the overhead of developers and site maintainers in keeping their jQuery plugins up-to-date and compatible with a given version of Drupal core. It is increasingly common for multiple Drupal modules and themes to require (or optionally use) the same jQuery plugin. So it can make sense for these components to have a dependency on one tiny module which provides the plugin. There would also be overhead (in CVS maintenance, PHP code, etc.) in having a Drupal module for each plugin, so this project bundles multiple plugins in one module.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-2.2" name="jQuery Update" id="mod_jquery_update_7.x-2.2">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_jquery_update_7.x-2.2/7.x-2.2/mod_jquery_update_7.x-2.2-7.x-2.2.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Upgrades the version of jQuery in Drupal core to a newer version of jQuery.

</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Jquery update upgrades the version of jQuery in Drupal core to a newer version of jQuery.

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0" name="Login Destination" id="mod_login_destination_7.x-1.0">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_login_destination_7.x-1.0/7.x-1.0/mod_login_destination_7.x-1.0-7.x-1.0.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Login Destination module allows you to customize the destination that a user is redirected to after logging in, registering to the site , using a one-time login link or logging out .</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Login Destination allows to customize the destination that a user is redirected to after logging in, registering to the site.The Login Destination module allows you to customize the destination that a user is redirected to after logging in, registering to the site using a one-time login link or logging out.

The destination can be an internal page or an external URL. It is possible to specify certain conditions like referring pages or user roles and make the destination depend upon them. You may use PHP snippets to provide custom conditions and destinations. It is also possible to keep users on the currently visited page after logging in or out.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.2" name="LoginToboggan" id="mod_logintoboggan_7.x-1.2">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_logintoboggan_7.x-1.2/7.x-1.2/mod_logintoboggan_7.x-1.2-7.x-1.2.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>The Login Toboggan module improves the Drupal login system in an external module by offering several features.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>This module improves the Drupal login system in an external module by offering several features.

1)Allow users to login using either their username OR their e-mail address.
2)Allow users to login immediately.
3)Provide a login form on Access Denied pages for non-logged-in (anonymous) users.
4)The module provides two login block options: One uses JavaScript to display the form within the block immediately upon clicking &quot;log in&quot;. The 5)Other brings the user to a separate page, but returns the user to their original page upon login.
6)Customize the registration form with two e-mail fields to ensure accuracy.
7)Optionally redirect the user to a specific page when using the 'immediate login' feature.
8)Optionally redirect the user to a specific page upon validation of their e-mail address.
9)Optionally display a user message indicating a successful login.
10)Optionally combine both the login and registration form on one page.
11)Optionally have unvalidated users purged from the system at a pre-defined interval (please read the CAVEATS section of INSTALL.txt for 12)Important information on configuring this feature!).
13)Integrates with Rules module to do various tasks when a user validates via email validation process (see http://drupal.org/node/880904 for an example)
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0-rc4" name="Masquerade" id="mod_masquerade_7.x-1.0-rc4">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_masquerade_7.x-1.0-rc4/7.x-1.0-rc4/mod_masquerade_7.x-1.0-rc4-7.x-1.0-rc4.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Masquerade module is designed as a tool for site designers and site administrators. It allows a user with the right permissions to switch users. While masquerading, a field is set on the $user object, and a menu item appears allowing the user to switch back. Watchdog entries are made any time a user masquerades or stops masquerading.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Masquerade module is designed as a tool for site designers and site administrators. It allows a user with the right permissions to switch users. While masquerading, a field is set on the $user object, and a menu item appears allowing the user to switch back. Watchdog entries are made any time a user masquerades or stops masquerading.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0-rc1" name="Media" id="mod_media_7.x-1.0-rc1">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_media_7.x-1.0-rc1/7.x-1.0-rc1/mod_media_7.x-1.0-rc1-7.x-1.0-rc1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_chaos_tool_suite_7.x-1.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_image_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_file_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Media module provides an extensible framework for managing files and multimedia assets, regardless of whether they are hosted on your own site or a 3rd party site - it is commonly refered to as a 'file browser to the internet'</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Media module provides an extensible framework for managing files and multimedia assets, regardless of whether they are hosted on your own site or a 3rd party site - it is commonly referred to as a 'file browser to the internet'.

Media is a drop-in replacement for the Drupal core upload field with a unified User Interface where editors and administrators can upload, manage, and reuse files and multimedia assets. Any files uploaded before Media was enabled will automatically take advantage of for many of the features it comes with.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0" name="Menu Admin per Menu" id="mod_menu_admin_per_menu_7.x-1.0">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_menu_admin_per_menu_7.x-1.0/7.x-1.0/mod_menu_admin_per_menu_7.x-1.0-7.x-1.0.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_menu_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Menu admin per menu allows administrators to customize the site navigation menu.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Menu Admin Per Menu By default, Drupal allows only users with &quot;administrator menu permission&quot; to add, modify or delete menu items. If user want for instance to let certain users manage primary links or secondary links but not navigation menu, this module provides this functionality.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0-rc1" name="Menu attributes" id="mod_menu_attributes_7.x-1.0-rc1">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_menu_attributes_7.x-1.0-rc1/7.x-1.0-rc1/mod_menu_attributes_7.x-1.0-rc1-7.x-1.0-rc1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_menu_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Menu attributes module allows you to specify some additional attributes for menu items such as id, name, class, style, and rel.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Menu attributes module allows you to specify some additional attributes for menu items such as id, name, class, style, and rel.

User will be using this module when
1)user want to &quot;nofollow&quot; certain menu items to sculpt the flow of PageRank through your site
2)user want to give a menu item an ID so you can easily select it using jQuery
3)user want to add additional classes or styles to a menu item

The module currently allows you to set the following attributes for each menu item:
1)Id
2)Name
3)Target
4)Rel
5)Class
6)Style
7)Accesskey
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-2.2" name="Menu block" id="mod_menu_block_7.x-2.2">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_menu_block_7.x-2.2/7.x-2.2/mod_menu_block_7.x-2.2-7.x-2.2.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_menu_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Menu block provides configurable blocks of menu trees starting with any level of any menu.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Menu block provides configurable blocks of menu trees starting with any level of any menu.Using Menu block user can add and configure a Main menu (levels 2+) block. That block would appear once you were on one of the Main menus pages and would show the menu tree for the 2nd level (and deeper) of your Main menu and would expand as you traversed down the tree. You can also limit the depth of the menus tree (e.g. Main menu (levels 2-3)) and/or expand all the child sub-menus (e.g. Main menu (expanded levels 2+)).</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-2.0" name="Nice Menus" id="mod_nice_menus_7.x-2.0">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_nice_menus_7.x-2.0/7.x-2.0/mod_nice_menus_7.x-2.0-7.x-2.0.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Nice Menus enables drop-down/right/left expandable menus. It uses only CSS for most browsers, with minimal Javascript for IE6. (Version 2 uses the Superfish jQuery plugin for all browsers, with an option to disable JS, and falls back to CSS-only for browsers that can handle it.)</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Nice menu module enables drop-down/right/left expandable menus.

Three styles/types of menus are currently possible: 
1)Horizontal
2)Menus drop down.
3)Vertical.
4)Menus fly to the left.
5)Vertical.
6)Menus fly to the right. 

Nice Menus creates blocks that may be associated with any existing site menu which can be placed wherever normal blocks can be placed in a theme. For themers, it is also possible to theme a menu as a Nice Menu directly by using the provided theme functions so a block is not necessary. A specific theme function for the Primary Links menu is available. The theme functions also allow a developer to pass in a custom menu tree of their making (i.e. not using a Drupal menu.) There is more information on how to use theme functions in the documentation.

The module comes with a simple, generic color scheme which can be fully overridden either by adding the override CSS to the theme's normal stylesheet or by creating a Nice Menus CSS file and telling Nice Menus to use that rather than its own default one through the global theme configuration. 

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-2.2" name="ShareThis " id="mod_sharethis__7.x-2.2">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_sharethis__7.x-2.2/7.x-2.2/mod_sharethis__7.x-2.2-7.x-2.2.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Share this module is used for Integration with the ShareThis social bookmarking utility on selected node types.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Share this module is used for Integration with the ShareThis social bookmarking utility on selected node types.

Features

1)Customize your ShareThis code using the STAPI.
2))Select node types you wish to display ShareThis module on.
3)Choose to display in $teaser view or not.
4)Choose to display the ShareThis link in either the $link items, or in the $node-&gt;content itself.
5)Customize the weight of the ShareThis link if in $node placement.
6)Uses the ShareThis jQuery plugin so the ShareThis servers are queried after page rendering.
7)Place a ShareThis block anywhere on your site.
8)Views 2 integration.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0" name="Nodequeue queue" id="mod_nodequeue_queue_7.x-1.0">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_nodequeue_queue_7.x-1.0/7.x-1.0/mod_nodequeue_queue_7.x-1.0-7.x-1.0.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_nodequeue__7.x-2.0-beta1</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Node Queue queue creates a queue for each Nodequeue using Nodequeue's own smartqueue capability.
 </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Node Queue queue creates a queue for each Nodequeue using Nodequeue's own smartqueue capability.

Use case: 
User have a set of nodequeues. Within each nodequeue, User want to be able to indicate particular nodes as special within that nodequeue. This module automatically creates a smartqueue based on the other nodequeues available.Still very rough around the edges but that basic functionality is there in the initial 1.0 release: When user  create a Nodequeuequeue queue, it will create sub-queues based on your other nodequeues (not Nodequeue queues, as that would start an infinite loop).Additionally, when an item is added to the Nodequeue queue smartqueue, it will automatically be added to the original queue that inspired it. (It does not yet remove items from the smartqueue when they are removed from the inspiration queue. As my initial use case was for subqueues of just one node each, this cleanup didn't matter much, but that feature is planned.)
 </content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.1" name="Organic groups" id="mod_organic_groups_7.x-1.1">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_organic_groups_7.x-1.1/7.x-1.1/mod_organic_groups_7.x-1.1-7.x-1.1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_entity_api_7.x-1.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_list_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Organic group enable users to create and manage their own 'groups'. </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Organic group enable users to create and manage their own 'groups'. Each group can have subscribers, and maintains a group home page where subscribers communicate amongst themselves.They do so by posting the usual node types: blog, story, page, etc. A block is shown on the group home page which facilitates these posts. The block also provides summary information about the group.Groups may be selective or not. Selective groups require approval in order to become a member, or even invitation -only groups. There are lots of preferences to configure groups as you need.
 </content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-2.5" name="Page Title" id="mod_page_title_7.x-2.5">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_page_title_7.x-2.5/7.x-2.5/mod_page_title_7.x-2.5-7.x-2.5.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_token_7.x-1.0-beta5</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Page title module gives you granular control over the page title.
 </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Page title module gives you granular control over the page title. The word &quot;title&quot; is a bit overloaded. Every piece of content in Drupal has a title, and so does every page. The page title is the one found in the HTML head inside the &lt;title&gt; tag. It is also used on SERPs (Search Engine Result Pages) and can greatly enhance your websites SEO (Search Engine Optimization).User can specify patterns for how the title should be structured and, on content creation pages, specify the page title separately to the content's title.
 </content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0-rc2" name="Pathauto" id="mod_pathauto_7.x-1.0-rc2">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_pathauto_7.x-1.0-rc2/7.x-1.0-rc2/mod_pathauto_7.x-1.0-rc2-7.x-1.0-rc2.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_path_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_token_7.x-1.0-beta5</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Pathauto module automatically generates path aliases for various kinds of content (nodes, categories, users) without requiring the user to manually specify the path alias. </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Pathauto module automatically generates path aliases for various kinds of content without requiring the user to manually specify the path alias. The Pathauto module automatically generates URL/path aliases for various kinds of content (nodes, taxonomy terms, users) without requiring the user to manually specify the path alias. This allows you to have URL aliases like /category/my-node-title instead of /node/123. The aliases are based upon a &quot;pattern&quot; system that uses tokens which the administrator can change.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.2" name="Privatemsg" id="mod_privatemsg_7.x-1.2">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_privatemsg_7.x-1.2/7.x-1.2/mod_privatemsg_7.x-1.2-7.x-1.2.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Privatemsg allows your site's visitors to send private messages to each other. Perfect for community oriented sites, such as forums and social networking sites. Many additional features are available as separate modules.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Privatemsg allows your site's visitors to send private messages to each other. Perfect for community oriented sites, such as forums and social networking sites. Many additional features are available as separate modules.

Current features:
1)Send and receive private messages on a site (between multiple recipients)
2)Threaded conversations (make it easier to keep track of messages and replies)
3)Search private messages
4)Tagging and filtering (helps organise conversations)
5)User blocking
6)E-mail notifications of new messages
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-3.0" name="Quick Tabs" id="mod_quick_tabs_7.x-3.0">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_quick_tabs_7.x-3.0/7.x-3.0/mod_quick_tabs_7.x-3.0-7.x-3.0.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_chaos_tool_suite_7.x-1.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Quick Tabs module allows you to create blocks of tabbed content, specifically views, blocks, nodes* and other quicktabs.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Quick Tabs module allows you to create blocks of tabbed content, specifically views, blocks, nodes* and other quicktabs. User can create a block on your site containing multiple tabs with corresponding content. Clicking on the tabs makes the corresponding content display instantly, using jQuery. With the 6.x-2.x branch, this can be done in either ajax or non-ajax mode. if user choose ajax mode for your Quick Tabs block (and this is chosen on an individual QT basis), only the content of the active tab will be loaded on page load and the content of the other tabs will be loaded via ajax on tab click (this is good for performance if you are loading, for example, several large views). In non-ajax mode the tab content is just hidden / shown on tab-click. This latter method is an ideal way to do something like the Most Popular / Most Emailed stories tabs you see on many news websites, where it is used more as a space-saving device in your sidebar. If however, you want a QT block as the main content of your entire page, then the chances are that ajax mode will be more appropriate.Once created, the Quick Tabs blocks show up in your block listing, ready to be configured and enabled like other blocks. Multiple Quick Tabs blocks can be placed on a single page.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.7" name="reCAPTCHA" id="mod_recaptcha_7.x-1.7">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_recaptcha_7.x-1.7/7.x-1.7/mod_recaptcha_7.x-1.7-7.x-1.7.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>reCAPTCHA web service to improve the CAPTCHA system and protect email addresses. </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>reCAPTCHA web service to improve the CAPTCHA system and protect email addresses. reCAPTCHA web service to improve the CAPTCHA system and protect email addresses. reCAPTCHA helps power massive-scale online collaboration.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0" name="Scheduler" id="mod_scheduler_7.x-1.0">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_scheduler_7.x-1.0/7.x-1.0/mod_scheduler_7.x-1.0-7.x-1.0.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Scheduler module allows nodes to be published and unpublished on specified dates and time.

</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Scheduler module allows nodes to be published and unpublished on specified dates and time.Dates can be entered either as plain text or with Javascript calendar popups (JSCalendar in Drupal 5, Date Popup in Drupal 6).JSCalendar is part of the JSTools module.The Date Popup module is part of the the Date module.


</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.1" name="Search 404" id="mod_search_404_7.x-1.1">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_search_404_7.x-1.1/7.x-1.1/mod_search_404_7.x-1.1-7.x-1.1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_search_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Search 404 module performs instead of showing a standard &quot;404 Page not found&quot;, this module performs a search on the keywords in the URL.

</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Search 404 module performs a search on the keywords in the URL. It also includes search engine keywords detections as well as regular expression based term filtering from the URL.

Features
1)Supports 404 Searches via Apache Solr Search Module if it is enabled
2)Supports searching via Google CSE, if the module is present
3)Supports Search by Page module as an option
4)Supports Lucene Search when available
5)Supports Lucene Did You Mean when available
6)Supports Xapian Search when available
7)Supports Fuzzy Search module as an option
8)Support for Custom Text and Title to be displayed in search404 pages
9)Option to choose between 301 and 302 redirects
10)Option to show side blocks when a 404 error occurs
11)Option to disable auto search for performance considerations and come up with the search form populated

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0" name="Site map" id="mod_site_map_7.x-1.0">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_site_map_7.x-1.0/7.x-1.0/mod_site_map_7.x-1.0-7.x-1.0.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Site map module provides a site map that gives visitors an overview of your site. 


</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Site map module provides a site map that gives visitors an overview of your site. It can also display the RSS feeds for all blogs and categories.Drupal generates the RSS feeds automatically but few seems to be aware that they exist.

The site map can display the following items:
1)A message to be displayed above the site map
2)The latest blogs.
3)Any books.
4)Any menus that will be displayed fully expanded.
5)Any categories, i.e vocabulary, with all the terms expanded. Optionally with node counts and RSS feeds.
6)A syndication block, the &quot;more&quot; link goes to the site map.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0" name="Site verification" id="mod_site_verification_7.x-1.0">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_site_verification_7.x-1.0/7.x-1.0/mod_site_verification_7.x-1.0-7.x-1.0.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Site verification module assists with the site/domain ownership authentication/verification for search engines.
 </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Site verification module assists with the site/domain ownership authentication/verification for search engines. This module assists with the site/domain ownership authentication/verification for search engines. There are two types of verification methods supported: adding meta tags, or uploading a specific file. If you are provided with a file to upload, this module makes it easy because you can upload the file in the module's interface and the proper filename and file contents will be saved and used in the authentication process.

This module is useful for the following search engine verifications:
1)Google Webmaster Tools
2)Google Apps
3)Bing Webmaster Central (formerly Live Search)
4)Yahoo! Site Explorer
5)Yandex.ru
6)Any search engine or web service that uses META tags or file upload to verify that you are the owner of a site.

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.8" name="String Overrides" id="mod_string_overrides_7.x-1.8">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_string_overrides_7.x-1.8/7.x-1.8/mod_string_overrides_7.x-1.8-7.x-1.8.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>String Overrides provides a quick and easy way to replace any text on the site.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>String Overrides module provides a quick and easy way to replace any text on the site.

Features

1)Easily replace anything that's passed through t().
2)Locale support, allowing you to override strings in any language.
3)Ability to import/export *.po files, for easy migration from the Locale module.
4)Note that this is not a replacement to Locale as having thousands of overrides can cause more pain then benefit. Use this only if you need a few easy text changes.


</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.8" name="Superfish" id="mod_superfish_7.x-1.8">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_superfish_7.x-1.8/7.x-1.8/mod_superfish_7.x-1.8-7.x-1.8.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_menu_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Superfish integrates jQuery Superfish plugin with your Drupal menus.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Superfish integrates jQuery Superfish plugin with your Drupal menus.jQuery Superfish plugin for your Drupal menus.

Overview:
1)Supporting all the Superfish options.
2)Block-specific settings.
3)Unobtrusive JavaScript.
4)Supersubs plug-in.
5)Supposition plug-in.
6)Touchscreen compatible (for iPad, Android, etc.)
7)Accessible. (Keyboard-accessible, screen reader compatible)
8)Multi-column sub-menus. (Megamenus)
9)RTL (Right-to-left) language support.
10)Lots of built-in options for designers.

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.4" name="SWF embed" id="mod_swf_embed_7.x-1.4">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_swf_embed_7.x-1.4/7.x-1.4/mod_swf_embed_7.x-1.4-7.x-1.4.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>SWF Embed is a simple developer-centered module for working with Macromedia Flash-based content. </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>SWF Embed is a simple developer-centered module for working with Macromedia Flash-based content. It provides the necessary hooks for adding Flash content on the server-side, as well as the necessary JavaScript and jQuery for working with the Flash on the client-side.

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.5" name="Comicdrop" id="mod_comicdrop_7.x-1.5">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_comicdrop_7.x-1.5/7.x-1.5/mod_comicdrop_7.x-1.5-7.x-1.5.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_image_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Comicdrop is a single stop module designed to create and manage a set of features to support the webcomic use case.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Comicdrop is a single stop module designed to create and manage a set of features to support the webcomic use case.This includes additional forms of pagination by node type, forum integration, archive and calendar blocks and other basic configurations a non-technical end user (webcomic artist) could use in order to quickly spin up a webcomic site.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0" name="Spritesheets" id="mod_spritesheets_7.x-1.0">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_spritesheets_7.x-1.0/7.x-1.0/mod_spritesheets_7.x-1.0-7.x-1.0.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Spritesheets is a module that will optimize css background images in themes and modules on to one image asset.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Spritesheets is a module that will optimize css background images in themes and modules on to one image asset. Spritesheets is a module that will optimize css background images in themes and modules on to one image asset. User have the ability to configure which directories Spritesheets module will search, and it will parse your CSS to find images that can be included on a spritesheet. User  can then configure which images should be optimized to a spritesheet. Spritesheets can greatly reduce page load time, bandwidth, and the tax on your server by combining</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-3.0-rc1" name="Views" id="mod_views_7.x-3.0-rc1">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_views_7.x-3.0-rc1/7.x-3.0-rc1/mod_views_7.x-3.0-rc1-7.x-3.0-rc1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_chaos_tool_suite_7.x-1.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Views module provides a flexible method for Drupal site designers to control how lists and tables of content (nodes in Views 1, almost anything in Views 2) are presented. </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Views module provides a flexible method for Drupal site designers to control how lists and tables of content (nodes in Views 1, almost anything in Views 2) are presented.

When installing Views on Drupal 7, User should have the current stable version of CTools (currently rc1) and you may need to flush cache as much as twice. There are currently issues with core's cache flushing that means one cache flush isn't necessarily enough. What is Views The Views module provides a flexible method for Drupal site designers to control how lists and tables of content (nodes in Views 1, almost anything in Views 2) are presented. Traditionally, Drupal has hard-coded most of this, particularly in how taxonomy and tracker lists are formatted.This tool is essentially a smart query builder that, given enough information, can build the proper query, execute it, and display the results. It has four modes, plus a special mode, and provides an impressive amount of functionality from these modes.

Among other things, Views can be used to generate reports, create summaries, and display collections of images and other content.
You need Views if

1)User like the default front page view, but you find you want to sort it differently.
2)User  like the default taxonomy/term view, but you find you want to sort it differently; for example, alphabetically.
3)User use /tracker, but you want to restrict it to posts of a certain type.
4)User like the idea of the 'article' module, but it doesn't display articles the way you like.
5)User want a way to display a block with the 5 most recent posts of some particular type.
6)Userwant to provide 'unread forum posts'.
7)User want a monthly archive similar to the typical Movable Type/Wordpress archives that displays a link to the in the form of &quot;Month, YYYY (X)&quot; 8)where X is the number of posts that month, and displays them in a block. The links lead to a simple list of posts for that month. 

Views can do a lot more than that, but those are some of the obvious uses of Views.

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-2.4" name="Voting API" id="mod_voting_api_7.x-2.4">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_voting_api_7.x-2.4/7.x-2.4/mod_voting_api_7.x-2.4-7.x-2.4.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>VotingAPI helps developers who want to use a standardized API and schema for storing, retrieving, and tabulating votes for Drupal content.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>VotingAPI helps developers who want to use a standardized API and schema for storing, retrieving, and tabulating votes for Drupal content. VotingAPI is a framework for content voting and rating systems in Drupal. VotingAPI helps developers who want to use a standardized API and schema for storing, retrieving, and tabulating votes for Drupal content.

Among other things, it supports:
1)Rating of any content (comments, nodes, users, fish, whatever)
2)Multi-criteria voting (rate a game based on video, audio, and replayability)
3)Automatic tabulation of results (with support for different voting styles, like 'percentage' and '+1/-1')
4)Efficient caching of results (sorting and filtering doesn't require any recalculation)
5)Hooks for additional vote calculations

Note that this module does NOT directly expose any voting mechanisms to end users. It's a framework designed to make life easier for other developers, and to standardize voting data for consumption by other modules (like Views).

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-3.13" name="Webform" id="mod_webform_7.x-3.13">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_webform_7.x-3.13/7.x-3.13/mod_webform_7.x-3.13-7.x-3.13.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Webform is the module for making surveys in Drupal. </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Webform is the module for making surveys in Drupal. Webform is the module for making surveys in Drupal. After a submission, users may be sent an e-mail &quot;receipt&quot; as well as sending a notification to administrators. Results can be exported into Excel or other spreadsheet applications. Webform also provides some basic statistical review and has and extensive API for expanding its features. Some good examples could be contests, personalized contact forms, or petitions. Each of these could have a customized form for end-users to fill out. If you need to build a lot of customized, one-off forms, Webform is a more suitable solution than creating content types and using CCK or Field module. </content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-2.1" name="Wysiwyg " id="mod_wysiwyg__7.x-2.1">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_wysiwyg__7.x-2.1/7.x-2.1/mod_wysiwyg__7.x-2.1-7.x-2.1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Wysiwyg allows to use client-side editors to edit content. It simplifies the This module replaces all other editor integration modules. No other Drupal module is required.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Wysiwyg allows to use client-side editors to edit content.

It simplifies the installation and integration of the editor of your choice. This module replaces all other editor integration modules. No other Drupal module is required. Wysiwyg module is capable to support any kind of client-side editor. It can be a HTML-editor (a.k.a. WYSIWYG), a &quot;pseudo-editor&quot; (buttons to insert markup into a textarea), or even Flash-based applications. The editor library needs to be downloaded separately. Various editors are supported (see below). Wysiwyg module also provides an abstraction layer for other Drupal modules to integrate with any editor. This means that other Drupal modules can expose content-editing functionality, regardless of which editor you have installed.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.1" name="Antispam" id="mod_antispam_7.x-1.1">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_antispam_7.x-1.1/7.x-1.1/mod_antispam_7.x-1.1-7.x-1.1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Antispam provides spam protection to your drupal site using external antispam service like Akismet. </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Antispam provides spam protection to your drupal site using external antispam service like Akismet. AntiSpam module is the successor of the Akismet module, and it provides spam protection to your drupal site using external antispam service like Akismet. AntiSpam module is fully compatible with Drupal 6.x (Akismet module for Drupal 6.x release had many compatibility issues and was not usable as it was), and it expanded the support of the external antispam service with TypePad AntiSpam and Defensio service as well as Akismet service. Now you can choose one of the antispam service you wish to use.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.1" name="Mollom" id="mod_mollom_7.x-1.1">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_mollom_7.x-1.1/7.x-1.1/mod_mollom_7.x-1.1-7.x-1.1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Mollom is an &quot;intelligent&quot; content moderation web service.
 </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Mollom is an &quot;intelligent&quot; content moderation web service.Mollom handles incoming posts intelligently, in much the same way a human moderator decides what posts are acceptable.Mollom is in a unique position to determine if a post is potentially spam; not only based on the posted content, but also on the past activity and reputation of the poster. In short, Mollom handles incoming posts intelligently, in much the same way a human moderator decides what posts are acceptable. Therefore, Mollom enables you to allow anonymous users to post comments and other content on your site.

How it works:
Mollom may block a post outright if it is from a known spammer. If Mollom is unsure how to classify a post, it may require the completion of a CAPTCHA to accept the post. Posts that do not match a &quot;spammy&quot; text pattern and do not originate from known spammers are accepted without the need to complete a CAPTCHA. Essentially, Mollom acts as a proactive content moderator that is on the job 24 hours a day, 7 days a week.
A stand-alone CAPTCHA solution, which neither considers user behavior nor point of origin, can never achieve this level of informed protection, and generally requires users to solve a CAPTCHA on every post. Using Mollom's text analysis, users must only solve CAPTCHAs when Mollom is unsure about a post.The Mollom module allows other modules to integrate their forms with Mollom. Forms exposed by Drupal core, including the user registration and comment forms, are supported by default. Mollom is actively developed and maintained by Dries Buytaert, the founder and project lead of Drupal, and Benjamin Schrauwen. Mollom is currently used by more than 30,000 sites, including Sony, Adobe, LinuxJournal, Warner Bros Records, Netlog, NBC, and others. As of September, 2010, Mollom currently protects over 30,000 websites with an average efficiency rate of 99.93% - which means that only 7 in 10,000 spam messages are not routinely caught by Mollom's filters. Since Mollom began operating, it has prevented almost 300 million spam posts from littering the web.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-2.1-beta1" name="AddThis" id="mod_addthis_7.x-2.1-beta1">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_addthis_7.x-2.1-beta1/7.x-2.1-beta1/mod_addthis_7.x-2.1-beta1-7.x-2.1-beta1.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>AddThis creates AddThis button as a block, to be used in themes and to node links.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>AddThis creates AddThis button as a block, to be used in themes and to node links. AddThis is the #1 bookmarking and sharing button on the Internet. AddThis has become the standard button for bookmarking and sharing. The AddThis button spreads your content across the Web by making it easier for your visitors to bookmark and share it with other people, againand againand again. This simple yet powerful button is very easy to install and provides valuable Analytics about the bookmarking and sharing activity of your users. AddThis helps your visitors create a buzz for your site and increase its popularity and ranking. (source: addthis.com).


</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.x-dev" name="AdSense" id="mod_adsense_7.x-1.x-dev">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_adsense_7.x-1.x-dev/7.x-1.x-dev/mod_adsense_7.x-1.x-dev-7.x-1.x-dev.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Adsense displays Google AdSense ads on your site to earn revenue.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Adsense displays Google AdSense ads on your site to earn revenue.This module provides web content providers with the means to earn revenue from visitors by displaying ads from Google AdSense advertising service on their sites.

User usage:
1)AdSense for Search and Drupal are incompatible as both use the 'q' query for different purposes. Using this module, you can display the search results in your site.
2)Protects you from displaying more ads in a page than the maximum allowed by Google.
3)The module provides easy-to-use ad blocks.
4)User can easily disable the ads for certain roles.
5)Provides simple controls for troubleshooting the ads before going live with the site.
6)If Google changes some minor details in the script in , your script can be updated site-wide just by upgrading the module.
7)If user want to do add revenue sharing, there's really no other option.


</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-2.0-beta1" name="Advanced Forum" id="mod_advanced_forum_7.x-2.0-beta1">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_advanced_forum_7.x-2.0-beta1/7.x-2.0-beta1/mod_advanced_forum_7.x-2.0-beta1-7.x-2.0-beta1.zip</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_forum_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_taxonomy_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_options_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_comment_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_options_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_chaos_tool_suite_7.x-1.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_views_7.x-3.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Advanced Forum builds on and enhances Drupal's core forum module. </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Advanced Forum builds on and enhances Drupal's core forum module. When used in combination with other Drupal contributed modules, many of which are automatically used by Advanced Forum, you can achieve much of what stand alone software provides. Because it uses the core forum module, it uses the node and comment system built into Drupal and is completely integrated, not a bridge. While it doesn't have all of the features of stand alone forum applications, being completely integrated into your site provides advantages that they don't.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0" name="Advanced help" id="mod_advanced_help_7.x-1.0">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_advanced_help_7.x-1.0/7.x-1.0/mod_advanced_help_7.x-1.0-7.x-1.0.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Advanced help module allows module developers to store their help outside the module system, in pure .html files. The files can be easily translated simply by copying them into the right translations directory. </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Advanced help module allows module developers to store their help outside the module system, in pure .html files. The files can be easily translated simply by copying them into the right translations directory. The entire system can appear in a popup or not as the module prefers (and by taking away access to view the popups, a site can force the popups to not exist). The system ties into Drupal's search system and is fully indexed, so the entire contents can be searched for keywords. the help files can be placed in a hierarchy as well, allowing for top down navigation of the help. By itself, this module doesn't do much; it requires another module to support it, but it does come with a nice little sample of text from Wikipedia to demonstrate the system.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-2.0-alpha1" name="Author Pane" id="mod_author_pane_7.x-2.0-alpha1">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_author_pane_7.x-2.0-alpha1/7.x-2.0-alpha1/mod_author_pane_7.x-2.0-alpha1-7.x-2.0-alpha1.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Author Pane is a block of information about a given user, like those typically found on a forum post, but can be used in other places as well. </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Author Pane is a block of information about a given user, like those typically found on a forum post, but can be used in other places as well. From core, it collects the user picture, name, join date, online status, contact link, and profile information. In addition, any module or theme can feed it more information via the preprocess system. All of this information is then gathered and displayed using a template file.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.x-dev" name="Custom Pagers" id="mod_custom_pagers_7.x-1.x-dev">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_custom_pagers_7.x-1.x-dev/7.x-1.x-dev/mod_custom_pagers_7.x-1.x-dev-7.x-1.x-dev.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Custom Pagers allows administrators to define context-sensitive previous/next pagers for any node type. </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Custom Pagers allows administrators to define context-sensitive previous/next pagers for any node type. The list of nodes to be cycled through is generated by a user-selectable view, and each pager can be displayed above or below the node body or in a sidebar block. This makes it possible to duplicate the paging functions of forum.module and book.module, as well as more complex stuff like comic strip navigation. Requires token.module and views.module.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.x-dev" name="Boost" id="mod_boost_7.x-1.x-dev">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_boost_7.x-1.x-dev/7.x-1.x-dev/mod_boost_7.x-1.x-dev-7.x-1.x-dev.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Boost provides static page caching for Drupal enabling a very significant performance and scalability boost for sites that receive mostly anonymous traffic.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Boost module  provides static page caching for Drupal enabling a very significant performance and scalability boost for sites that receive mostly anonymous traffic.

Boost is very easy to install and has been throughly tested on Shared, VPS and Dedicated hosting. Apache is fully supported, with Nginx, Lighttpd and IIS 7 semi-supported. Boost will cache &amp; gzip compress html, xml, ajax, css, &amp; javascript. Boosts cache expiration logic is very advanced; it's fairly simple to have different cache lifetimes for different parts of your site. The built in crawler makes sure expired content is quickly regenerated for fast page loading. For shared hosting this is your best option in terms of improving performance.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-3.0-alpha1" name="Calendar" id="mod_calendar_7.x-3.0-alpha1">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_calendar_7.x-3.0-alpha1/7.x-3.0-alpha1/mod_calendar_7.x-3.0-alpha1-7.x-3.0-alpha1.zip</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_views_7.x-3.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_chaos_tool_suite_7.x-1.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_date_7.x-2.0-alpha4</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Calendar module will display any Views date field in calendar formats, including CCK date fields, node created or updated dates, etc. Switch between year, month, and day views. Back and next navigation is provided for all views. </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Calendar module will display any views date field in calendar formats, including CCK date fields, node created or updated dates, etc. Switch between year, month, and day views. Back and next navigation is provided for all views.Lots of the Calendar functionality comes from the Date module, so any time you update the Calendar module you should be sure you also update to the latest version of the Date module at the same time.Date iCal, a project that will contain code and features needed to either import or export dates using iCal feeds.

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0-alpha3" name="CAPTCHA" id="mod_captcha_7.x-1.0-alpha3">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_captcha_7.x-1.0-alpha3/7.x-1.0-alpha3/mod_captcha_7.x-1.0-alpha3-7.x-1.0-alpha3.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>CAPTCHA is a challenge-response test most often placed within web forms to determine whether the user is human.
</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>CAPTCHA is a challenge-response test most often placed within web forms to determine whether the user is human. The purpose of CAPTCHA is to block form submissions by spambots, which are automated scripts that post spam content everywhere they can. The CAPTCHA module provides this feature to virtually any user facing web form on a Drupal site. </content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.x-dev" name="Computed Field" id="mod_computed_field_7.x-1.x-dev">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_computed_field_7.x-1.x-dev/7.x-1.x-dev/mod_computed_field_7.x-1.x-dev-7.x-1.x-dev.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Computed Field is a very powerful CCK field module that lets you add a custom &quot;computed fields&quot; to your content types.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Computed Field is a very powerful CCK field module that lets you add a custom &quot;computed fields&quot; to your content types. Computed fields are populated with values that you define via PHP code. User may draw on anything available to Drupal, including other fields, the current user, database tables, you name it. (Feeling the power yet? :) ) User can also choose whether to store your computed field values in the database with other content fields, or have them &quot;calculated&quot; on the fly during node views. (Although you should note that Views use requires database stored values.) This field is literally the Swiss Army knife of CCK fields. So start cooking up your PHP based values!

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-2.x-dev" name="Content Construction Kit (CCK)" id="mod_content_construction_kit_(cck)_7.x-2.x-dev">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_content_construction_kit_(cck)_7.x-2.x-dev/7.x-2.x-dev/mod_content_construction_kit_(cck)_7.x-2.x-dev-7.x-2.x-dev.zip</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_ui_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Content Construction Kit allows you to add custom fields to nodes using a web browser.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Content Construction Kit allows you to add custom fields to nodes using a web browser. Drupal 7 and Fields in Core.Most of CCK has moved to core in the Drupal 7 version. Please note that this is not the place to get support for D7 Fields! We are getting a number of support requests, bug reports, and even feature requests for D7 fields. Fields are in core in D7, you must file issues there, not here.

The D7 version of the contrib CCK package currently contains:

D6 -&gt; D7 data migration code, see Migrating D6 Content Construction Kit (CCK) to D7 Fields for an explanation of how to upgrade your data.
some miscellaneous helpers to do things that core will not do, like maintain the PHP code snippets some fields may have been using to define allowed values (partially working)

The following features are now handled by separate, dedicated projects:

1)nodereference and userreference : References project - co-maintainer needed.
2)content_permissions: Field permissions module. See this issue for progress on the D7 version..
3)fieldgroup : Field group module - with much more awesomeness than in D6 !
4)content_copy: Either use Bundle copy or the Features module which supports exporting and importing content types and fields in 'feature' modules. 

Integration with other modules:

1)Views - all Views field integration is handled by Views in D7.
2)Panels - all Panels field integration is handled by Panels in D7.
3)Token - see the D7 version of the Token module.
4)Devel - the Devel module will handle field generation code in D7.

Everything else is in Drupal 7 core. CCK Resources

CCK is a very powerful system with many different contributed modules to extend its functionality. Install the Advanced Help module for additional help, and use the Views module to display CCK information in a variety of ways.

Here are a few other comprehensive documentation and tutorial resources to help get you started:

1)Text: The CCK Handbook on Drupal.org.
2)Text: CCK Module basics tutorial.
3)Video: Adding Fields With CCK video.
4)Video: CCK &amp; Views Tutorial (for Drupal 5).
5)DVD: Learning CCK in-depth training by Lullabot.
6)Book: Using Drupal O'Reilly covers CCK with lots of examples.
7)Video: Karen Stevenson's CCK Presentation at the Do It With Drupal Seminar (paid access) .</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0-alpha1" name="Custom breadcrumbs" id="mod_custom_breadcrumbs_7.x-1.0-alpha1">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_custom_breadcrumbs_7.x-1.0-alpha1/7.x-1.0-alpha1/mod_custom_breadcrumbs_7.x-1.0-alpha1-7.x-1.0-alpha1.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Custom breadcrumbs allows administrators to define custom breadcrumb trails for node types.

</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Custom breadcrum allows administrators to define custom breadcrumb trails for node types.This allows CCK-style node types to have &quot;Home &gt; User Blog &gt; 2005 &gt; January&quot; style breadcrumbs on the node view page itself, synchronizing cleanly with custom views or pathauto aliases. Breadcrumb visibility can be customized via a php snippet.

No new features are planned for these versions, but they are still supported and bug reports are encouraged. In addition to breadcrumb visibility, this version provides an option that permits php code snippets to be used to form the breadcrumb titles and paths. Multiple languages are also supported.


</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-2.0-alpha4" name="Date" id="mod_date_7.x-2.0-alpha4">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_date_7.x-2.0-alpha4/7.x-2.0-alpha4/mod_date_7.x-2.0-alpha4-7.x-2.0-alpha4.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Date package contains both a flexible date/time field type Date field and a Date API that other modules can use. </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Date package contains both a flexible date/time field type Date field and a Date API that other modules can use. The Drupal Handbook pages are at Date/Calendar Documentation. The latest code includes two new modules, Date Repeat Field, a module to create date fields that use the Date Repeat API, and Date All Day, a module to manage handling of All Day values, including adding an All day checkbox to the widget. Both of those were formerly included in the basic Date module but have been pulled out to streamline the code and make it possible to disable them. They also serve as examples of how other modules can intervene to alter date processing.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0-beta1" name="DHTML Menu" id="mod_dhtml_menu_7.x-1.0-beta1">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_dhtml_menu_7.x-1.0-beta1/7.x-1.0-beta1/mod_dhtml_menu_7.x-1.0-beta1-7.x-1.0-beta1.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>DHTML Menu uses Javascript to reduce the number of page loads when using nested menus; this is particularly useful with Drupal's administration system.

</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>DHTML Menu uses Javascript to reduce the number of page loads when using nested menus; this is particularly useful with Drupal's administration system.Ordinarily in Drupal, in order to see the sub-items in a menu, you need to click the link of this item and wait for a full page load. After enabling DHTML Menu, clicking a menu link once will expand it to reveal its sub-items without reloading the page. A double-click on the item will load the page normally. Additionally, a cookie stores which menus are open and which are closed, so that the state of the menus remain consistent as you navigate around the site.

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0-beta3" name="Media Embedded" id="mod_media_embedded_7.x-1.0-beta3">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_media_embedded_7.x-1.0-beta3/7.x-1.0-beta3/mod_media_embedded_7.x-1.0-beta3-7.x-1.0-beta3.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_media_7.x-1.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Media Embedded module parses links in text fields and adds them to a predefined media field. Module does also a formatter for replacing the parsed links inside a text field.
 </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Media Embedded module parses links in text fields and adds them to a predefined media field. Module does also a formatter for replacing the parsed links inside a text field.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0-rc1" name="Entity API" id="mod_entity_api_7.x-1.0-rc1">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_entity_api_7.x-1.0-rc1/7.x-1.0-rc1/mod_entity_api_7.x-1.0-rc1-7.x-1.0-rc1.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Entity API module extends the entity API of Drupal core in order to provide a unified way to deal with entities and their properties. Additionally, it provides an entity CRUD controller, which helps simplifying the creation of new entity types.

</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Entity API module extends the entity API of Drupal core in order to provide a unified way to deal with entities and their properties. Additionally, it provides an entity CRUD controller, which helps simplifying the creation of new entity types.

Features:

This is an API module, so it doesn't provide any end-user features. However, users may enable the entity tokens module, which provides token replacements for all entity properties that have no tokens and are known to the entity API.

Overview:

1)The module provides API functions allowing modules to create, save, delete, view or to determine access for any entity, i.e. entity_create(), entity_save(), entity_delete(), entity_view() and entity_access().

2)The entity API introduces a unique place for metadata about entity relationships and entity properties: hook_entity_property_info(). This information about entity properties contains the data type and callbacks for how to get and set the data of a property. Modules may rely on this information in order to support any entity property, e.g. Rules and the Search API build upon that.

3)Furthermore the module provides data wrappers that make use of the available information to provide a simple and unified access to entities and their properties. For usage examples have a look at the README or the provided tests.

4)Beside that, the module helps you defining a new entity type. For that, it provides an entity controller, which implements full CRUD functionality for your entities. Optionally, entities may be created based on classes derived from the provided Entity class.

5)The entity API cares about creating fieldable entities as well as exportable entities, however it does not yet support revisions. Additionally it supports implementing bundle entities, i.e. bundle objects (like node types) for fieldable entities implemented as (exportable) entities, for which the appropriate field API callbacks get automatically invoked.

6)For entity types implemented based upon the provided CRUD API the API is providing additional module integration too, i.e. Rules events are provided for all CRUD-related hooks, some basic entity property information for hook_entity_property_info() is provided and exportable entities are automatically integrated with the Features module.

7)These module integrations are implemented in separate controller classes, which may be separately overridden or enabled/deactivated.
Optionally, the entity API also helps providing an administrative interface for managing entities, e.g. the UI for managing profile types of Profile 2 is built with that.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0-beta4" name="Features" id="mod_features_7.x-1.0-beta4">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_features_7.x-1.0-beta4/7.x-1.0-beta4/mod_features_7.x-1.0-beta4-7.x-1.0-beta4.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Features module enables the capture and management of features in Drupal. A feature is a collection of Drupal entities which taken together satisfy a certain use-case.

</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Features module enables the capture and management of features in Drupal. A feature is a collection of Drupal entities which taken together satisfy a certain use-case.Features provides a UI and API for taking different site building components from modules with exportables and bundling them together in a single feature module. A feature module is like any other Drupal module except that it declares its components (e.g. views, contexts, CCK fields, etc.) in its .info file so that it can be checked, updated, or reverted programmatically.

Examples of features might be:

1)A blog.
2)A pressroom.
3)An image gallery.
4)An e-commerce t-shirt store.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-2.0-alpha4" name="Feeds" id="mod_feeds_7.x-2.0-alpha4">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_feeds_7.x-2.0-alpha4/7.x-2.0-alpha4/mod_feeds_7.x-2.0-alpha4-7.x-2.0-alpha4.zip</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_chaos_tool_suite_7.x-1.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_job_scheduler_7.x-2.0-alpha2</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Feeds Import or aggregate data as nodes, users, taxonomy terms or simple database records.
</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Feeds Import or aggregate data as nodes, users, taxonomy terms or simple database records.

Features :
1)One-off imports and periodic aggregation of content.
2)Import or aggregate RSS/Atom feeds.
3)Import or aggregate CSV files.
4)Import or aggregate OPML files.
5)PubSubHubbub support.
6)Create nodes, users, taxonomy terms or simple database records from import.
7)Extensible to import any other kind of content.
8)Granular mapping of input elements to Drupal content elements.
9)Exportable configurations.
10)Batched import for large files.

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0-alpha1" name="FileField Paths" id="mod_filefield_paths_7.x-1.0-alpha1">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_filefield_paths_7.x-1.0-alpha1/7.x-1.0-alpha1/mod_filefield_paths_7.x-1.0-alpha1-7.x-1.0-alpha1.zip</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_token_7.x-1.0-beta5</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>File (Field) Paths module extends the default functionality of Drupal's core Upload module, the FileField module and many other File Upload modules by adding the ability to use node tokens in destination paths and filenames.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>File (Field) Paths module extends the default functionality of Drupal's core Upload module, the FileField module and many other File Upload modules by adding the ability to use node tokens in destination paths and filenames. In simple terms, File (Field) Paths allows you to automatically sort and rename your uploaded files using token based replacement patterns to maintain a nice clean filesystem.

 
Features:

1)Configurable file paths now use node tokens instead of user tokens.
2)Configurable filenames.
3)Support for:
3a)Drupal core Upload module.
3b)FileField module.
3c)ImageField module.
3d)ImageField Crop module.
3e)Image module.
3f)Comment Upload module.
3g)[D6] Audio module.
3h)[D6] Video module.
4)File path and filename cleanup options:
5)Filter out words and punctuation by taking advantage of the Pathauto module.
5a)Convert unicode characters into US-ASCII with the Transliteration module.
5b)Automatically updates unprocessed file paths in the node body, teaser and CCK text fields on save.
6)Retroactive updates - rename and/or move previously uploaded files (Use with caution)
7)[D6] Active updating - actively rename and/or move previously uploaded files (Use with caution)

 </content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-2.0-beta6" name="Flag" id="mod_flag_7.x-2.0-beta6">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_flag_7.x-2.0-beta6/7.x-2.0-beta6/mod_flag_7.x-2.0-beta6-7.x-2.0-beta6.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Flag is a flexible flagging system that is completely customizable by the administrator. 
</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Flag is a flexible flagging system that is completely customizable by the administrator. Using this module, the site administrator can provide any number of flags for nodes, comments, or users. Some possibilities include bookmarks, marking important, friends, or flag as offensive. With extensive views integration, you can create custom lists of popular content or keep tabs on important content.

Flags may be per-user, meaning that each user can mark an item individually, or global, meaning that the item is either marked or it is not marked, and any user who changes that changes it for everyone.

In this way, additional flags (similar to published and sticky) can be put on nodes, or other items, and dealt with by the system however the administration likes.
Features

Create unlimited arbitrary flags or bookmarks to flag content
Extensive Views integration to make lists of popular flagged content
Full support for Tokens in all messages and labels
Execute Actions when content is flagged past a certain threshold (Actions is now included in Drupal 6 core with no additional modules, requires 2.x version in Drupal 5)
Full Rules module integration
JavaScript based toggling of flags
Limit flag display by content type and roles
Optionally show each flag as a checkbox on the node form

Each flag provides data to the Views module, and provides a default view to list 'my bookmarks'. The default views are basic, but are easily tailored to whatever the system administrator would like them to do.

The module will come installed with a simple bookmark and two sample views for 'My bookmarks' both as a stand-alone page at &quot;bookmarks&quot;, and a page for each user as a tab under their profile at user/x/bookmarks.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-3.0-alpha5" name="Hierarchical Select" id="mod_hierarchical_select_7.x-3.0-alpha5">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_hierarchical_select_7.x-3.0-alpha5/7.x-3.0-alpha5/mod_hierarchical_select_7.x-3.0-alpha5-7.x-3.0-alpha5.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Hierarchical Select module defines the &quot;hierarchical_select&quot; form element, which is a greatly enhanced way for letting the user select items in a hierarchy.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Hierarchical Select module defines the &quot;hierarchical_select&quot; form element, which is a greatly enhanced way for letting the user select items in a hierarchy. Hierarchical Select has the ability to save the entire lineage of a selection or only the &quot;deepest&quot; selection. You can configure it to force the user to make a selection as deep as possible in the tree, or allow the user to select an item anywhere in the tree. Levels can be labeled, you can configure limit the number of items that can be selected, configure a title for the dropbox, choose a site-wide animation delay, and so on. You can even create new items and levels through Hierarchical Select!

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-2.4" name="Video" id="mod_video_7.x-2.4">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_video_7.x-2.4/7.x-2.4/mod_video_7.x-2.4-7.x-2.4.zip</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_file_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_image_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Video module allows users to submit videos to a Drupal site.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Video module allows users to submit videos to a Drupal site. Video module 7.x-2.x provide video field while 6.x-3-x and 6.x-4-x provides a CCK video upload field to upload videos with ease. The 5.x module and 6.x-2 version is not CCK-based and supports additional playback options in a single node.Video module allows you to upload video in any format, play video in any format, transcode video to H246, Theora, VP8 using Zencoder , FFMPEG , automatically creates video thumbnails, stream videos from cloud, HTML5 videos with mobile device playback compatibility, Very reliable API for converting videos and auto thumbnail, embed video to node body using WYSIWYG module (D7 only) and many more.




</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.x-dev" name="ImageAPI" id="mod_imageapi_7.x-1.x-dev">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_imageapi_7.x-1.x-dev/7.x-1.x-dev/mod_imageapi_7.x-1.x-dev-7.x-1.x-dev.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>ImageAPI is meant to be used in place of the API provided by image.inc. You probably do not need to install this module unless another module are you using requires it. It provides no new features to your Drupal site. It only provides an API other modules can leverage. Currently GD2 and ImageMagick support are distributed with ImageAPI.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>ImageAPI is meant to be used in place of the API provided by image.inc. You probably do not need to install this module unless another module are you using requires it. It provides no new features to your Drupal site. It only provides an API other modules can leverage. Currently GD2 and ImageMagick support are distributed with ImageAPI.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0-alpha2" name="ImageMagick" id="mod_imagemagick_7.x-1.0-alpha2">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_imagemagick_7.x-1.0-alpha2/7.x-1.0-alpha2/mod_imagemagick_7.x-1.0-alpha2-7.x-1.0-alpha2.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>ImageMagick allows to use ImageMagick as image toolkit for Image API in Drupal 7 core.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>ImageMagick allows to use ImageMagick as image toolkit for Image API in Drupal 7 core.ImageMagick needs to be installed on your server and the convert binary needs to be accessible and executable from PHP. The PHP configuration must allow invocation of proc_open() (which is security-wise identical to exec()).


</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-2.6" name="jCarousel" id="mod_jcarousel_7.x-2.6">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_jcarousel_7.x-2.6/7.x-2.6/mod_jcarousel_7.x-2.6-7.x-2.6.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>jCarousel module allows developers and themers to make use of the jCarousel jQuery plugin. It includes a developer API that other modules can use, as well as Views integration in the 2.0 version so that you can turn any list of content or images into a carousel.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>jCarousel module allows developers and themers to make use of the jCarousel jQuery plugin. It includes a developer API that other modules can use, as well as Views integration in the 2.0 version so that you can turn any list of content or images into a carousel.

Features:
1)Built-in Views support.
2)AJAX-loading of additional items as needed.
3)Carousel pager/navigation to jump between multiple pages.
4)Circular wrapping of items.
5)API for direct usage of jCarousel without Views.

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-2.0-alpha2" name="Job Scheduler" id="mod_job_scheduler_7.x-2.0-alpha2">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_job_scheduler_7.x-2.0-alpha2/7.x-2.0-alpha2/mod_job_scheduler_7.x-2.0-alpha2-7.x-2.0-alpha2.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Job Scheduler is a simple API for scheduling tasks once at a predetermined time or periodically at a fixed interval.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Job Scheduler is a simple API for scheduling tasks once at a predetermined time or periodically at a fixed interval.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0-beta1" name="Language icons" id="mod_language_icons_7.x-1.0-beta1">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_language_icons_7.x-1.0-beta1/7.x-1.0-beta1/mod_language_icons_7.x-1.0-beta1-7.x-1.0-beta1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_locale_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Language icons module provides icons for language links, both for the Language switcher block and (optionally) for node links. It is a spin-off from Internationalization (i18n) package.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Language icons module provides icons for language links, both for the Language switcher block and  for node links. As basic multilingual support is now built into Drupal 6 core, it doesn't depend anymore on any other contributed module. This module will work as simple add-in for Drupal 6. However, for a fully enabled multilingual site, the Internationalization package is recommended. The default icons provided are png images with a fixed height of 12 pixels and a variable width per the official dimension of the respective flag. However this module can handle other image types and sizes too. 
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.x-dev" name="Lightbox2" id="mod_lightbox2_7.x-1.x-dev">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_lightbox2_7.x-1.x-dev/7.x-1.x-dev/mod_lightbox2_7.x-1.x-dev-7.x-1.x-dev.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Lightbox2 module is a simple, unobtrusive script used to overlay images on the current page. It's a snap to setup and works on most modern browsers.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Lightbox2 module is to overlay images on the current page. The module places images above your current page, not within. This frees you from the constraints of the layout, particularly column widths. It keeps users on the same page. Clicking to view an image and then having to click the back button to return to your site is bad for continuity (and no fun!). 

Features:

The version 2 module has several benefits over the plain Lightbox module. Note, not all of these features are available when the &quot;Lightbox2 Lite&quot; option is enabled.

1)Image Sets: group related images and navigate through them with ease - ideal for your image galleries.
2)Slideshow Capability.
3)HTML Content Support: ability to show websites or other HTML content in a lightbox.
4)Video Content Support.
5)Visual Effects: fancy pre-loader and transition when you click on the image.
6)Keyboard Shortcuts: useful keyboard shortcuts for switching between images, toggling play / pause, etc.
7)Zoom Capability: larger images are reduced in size so they fit snugly inside the browser window. A zoom in button can then be clicked on to see it in its original size, while a zoom out button is provided to return you to the scaled down version.
8)Choice of Layouts.
9)Skin and Animation Configuration.
10)Right-to-Left Language Support.
11)Automatic Image Detection: configurable automatic re-formatting of image node thumbnails, previews, etc, so there is no need to add 'rel=&quot;lightbox&quot;' to each image node link on your site. Image, Inline, Flickr, Acidfree Albums, Image Assist, Embedded Media Field and CCK Imagefield modules are all supported.
12)Page Exclusion Capability: exclude certain pages on your site from having the lightbox2 functionality.
13)Login Support: ability to modify all user/login links so the login form appears in a lightbox.
14)Gallery 2 Support: support for Gallery 2 images via the Gallery module (beta). See here for information on how to customise your Gallery2 theme to work with lightbox.

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0" name="Link" id="mod_link_7.x-1.0">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_link_7.x-1.0/7.x-1.0/mod_link_7.x-1.0-7.x-1.0.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Link module provides a useful custom content field, which can be added to content types for validating and storing internal or external links and URLs supporting additional title, tokens, target and css class attribution and static title values</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Link provides a useful custom content field, which can be added to content types for validating and storing internal or external links  The link module can be count to the top 50 modules in Drupal installations and provides a standard custom content field for links. With this module links can be added easily to any content types and profiles and include advanced validating and different ways of storing internal or external links and URLs. It also supports additional link text title, site wide tokens for titles and title attributes, target attributes, css class attribution, static repeating values, input conversion, and many more.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0-beta2" name="Localization update" id="mod_localization_update_7.x-1.0-beta2">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_localization_update_7.x-1.0-beta2/7.x-1.0-beta2/mod_localization_update_7.x-1.0-beta2-7.x-1.0-beta2.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_locale_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Localization update automatically download and update your translations fetching them from other Localization server.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Localization update automatically download and update your translations fetching them from other Localization server.

Integrating with git checkouts

This module is based on concepts very similar to Drupal core's update module. Modules and themes with their corresponding drupal.org projects are identified and translations are downloaded for the appropriate versions. If you use git checkouts instead of package tarballs or zip files, use Git deploy module, so projects and versions are identified properly. (For legacy CVS checkouts, the CVS deploy module will work). 
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0-beta1" name="Signup Rules Integration" id="mod_signup_rules_integration_7.x-1.0-beta1">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_signup_rules_integration_7.x-1.0-beta1/7.x-1.0-beta1/mod_signup_rules_integration_7.x-1.0-beta1-7.x-1.0-beta1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_logintoboggan_7.x-1.2</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Signup Rules provides Rules integration for Signup module
 </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Signup Rules provides Rules integration for Signup module.Signup Rules provides Rules integration for Signup module administrators can use this module to automatically modify users, nodes, and signups when certain site or Signup related events occur. Signup Rules can also be used to replace and enhance actions that are native to Signup module, like sending e-mails to users who have signed up for content.
 


</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0-beta6" name="Media Gallery" id="mod_media_gallery_7.x-1.0-beta6">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_media_gallery_7.x-1.0-beta6/7.x-1.0-beta6/mod_media_gallery_7.x-1.0-beta6-7.x-1.0-beta6.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_list_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_options_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_number_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_media_7.x-1.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_taxonomy_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Media Gallery module uses the Media module to provide a rich media gallery.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Media Gallery module uses the Media module to provide a rich media gallery .It currently supports images and youtube videos well. Other file types may or may not work as well, but the facility is there to add them. This module was developed by the engineering team at Acquia

Features:
1)Add media from URL, upload or existing files
2)Multi-file upload
3)Set rows and columns and dynamically size images to fit space
4)Lightbox support
5)CC license settings
6)Title, description and tags on images
7)Drag and drop re-ordering
8)Gallery collections to group related galleries together
9)Creates gallery blocks
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0-beta1" name="Media Gallery picker" id="mod_media_gallery_picker_7.x-1.0-beta1">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_media_gallery_picker_7.x-1.0-beta1/7.x-1.0-beta1/mod_media_gallery_picker_7.x-1.0-beta1-7.x-1.0-beta1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_media_gallery_7.x-1.0-beta6</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_list_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_options_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_number_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_media_7.x-1.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_taxonomy_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Media Gallery picker module creates a filter and a wysiwyg plugin to select galleries in content.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Media Gallery picker module creates a filter and a wysiwyg plugin to select galleries in content.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.x-dev" name="Menu per Role" id="mod_menu_per_role_7.x-1.x-dev">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_menu_per_role_7.x-1.x-dev/7.x-1.x-dev/mod_menu_per_role_7.x-1.x-dev-7.x-1.x-dev.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_menu_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Menu Per Role module allows you to restrict access to menu items1 based on user roles. </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Menu Per Role module allows you to restrict access to menu items1 based on user roles. It depends on the Drupal core menu.modulejust activate both modules and edit a menu item as usual. There will be a new fieldset that allows you to restrict access by role. The fieldset also appears in the node edit form.

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0-alpha1" name="Messaging" id="mod_messaging_7.x-1.0-alpha1">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_messaging_7.x-1.0-alpha1/7.x-1.0-alpha1/mod_messaging_7.x-1.0-alpha1-7.x-1.0-alpha1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Messaging Framework to allow message sending in a channel independent way. It will provide a common API for message composition and sending while allowing plug-ins for multiple messaging methods.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Messaging Framework to allow message sending in a channel independent way. It will provide a common API for message composition and sending while allowing plug-ins for multiple messaging methods.When using this framework, you won't send e-mails to users anymore. You will send them 'messages' and they will decide how they want to get them delivered, that may be by mail, IM, SMS, depending on user's preferences...</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-2.0-beta1" name="Nodequeue " id="mod_nodequeue__7.x-2.0-beta1">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_nodequeue__7.x-2.0-beta1/7.x-2.0-beta1/mod_nodequeue__7.x-2.0-beta1-7.x-2.0-beta1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Nodequeue module allows users to collect nodes in an arbitrarily ordered list. The order in the list can be used for a any purpose</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Nodequeue module allows users to collect nodes in an arbitrarily ordered list. The order in the list can be used for a any purpose, such as:

1)A block listing teasers for the five top news stories on a site.
2)A users favorite music albums.
3)A group of favorite from which one is randomly displayed.

Nodequeue provides a simple drag-and-drop interface to manually order any queue. Additionally, it allows nodes to be added and removed from queues without needing edit permissions to the node. Nodes can be added to queues either from a queue management tab or by links on the node teaser.

Smartqueue API:

Nodequeue provides a robust API that allows other modules to define smartqueues, which are associated with external data. For example, the included taxonomy smartqueue creates subqueues for a given queue for every term in the chosen vocabulary. Nodes are then only eligible for subqueues whose term matches the nodes terms. This makes it very easy to have queues for each category without cluttering the management page.

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0-alpha1" name="Notifications" id="mod_notifications_7.x-1.0-alpha1">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_notifications_7.x-1.0-alpha1/7.x-1.0-alpha1/mod_notifications_7.x-1.0-alpha1-7.x-1.0-alpha1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_menu_block_7.x-2.2</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_trigger_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Notifications is a complete Subscriptions/Notifications Framework aiming at extendability and scalability. It allows any number of plug-ins defining new event types or subscription types or a different user interface.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Notifications is a complete Subscriptions/Notifications Framework aiming at extendability and scalability. It allows any number of plug-ins defining new event types or subscription types or a different user interface.

Features:

1)Immediate or digested notifications, allowing multiple digest formats for deferred notifications. Digests are configurable and themeable.
2)By using the Messaging Framework, notifications are not limited to email. Other methods like SMS or XMPP can be used.
3)Pluggable subscription and event types. Currently included: Content subscriptions (thread or node, author, content type), Taxonomy.
4)Event and message queueing, fully scalable and configurable. Uses token module for message composition and text replacement, thus it supports pluggable tokens.
5)Pluggable and fully configurable user interface. 
6)A UI module is provided but it can be disabled and replaced by a custom UI module.
7)Configurable per content type. User can have different types of subscriptions and a different UI for each content type.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-3.0-alpha3" name="Panels" id="mod_panels_7.x-3.0-alpha3">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_panels_7.x-3.0-alpha3/7.x-3.0-alpha3/mod_panels_7.x-3.0-alpha3-7.x-3.0-alpha3.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_chaos_tool_suite_7.x-1.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Panels module allows a site administrator to create customized layouts for multiple uses. </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Panels module allows a site administrator to create customized layouts for multiple uses. At its core it is a drag and drop content manager that lets you visually design a layout and place content within that layout. Integration with other systems allows you to create nodes that use this, landing pages that use this, and even override system pages such as taxonomy and the node page so that you can customize the layout of your site with very fine grained permissions.


</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0-beta3" name="redirect" id="mod_redirect_7.x-1.0-beta3">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_redirect_7.x-1.0-beta3/7.x-1.0-beta3/mod_redirect_7.x-1.0-beta3-7.x-1.0-beta3.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_pathauto_7.x-1.0-rc2</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Redirect module work in progress for integration and collaboration between redirection-type modules.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Redirect module work in progress for integration and collaboration between redirection-type modules.

1)Path redirect
2)Global redirect (Merged in basic functionalty: #905914: Re-enable global redirections)

Features:

1)Common API for loading, saving, and deleting redirects.
2)Case-insensitive redirect matching with a hook to allow other modules to narrow-down the candidate redirects.
3)Redirect counter and last used timestamp, with automatic cleanup of inactive redirects.
4)Integration with Drupal's page cache to optimize redirects and performance.
5)Complete individual redirect access API.
6)Views API integration.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0-alpha2" name="Printer, e-mail and PDF versions" id="mod_printer,_e-mail_and_pdf_versions_7.x-1.0-alpha2">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_printer,_e-mail_and_pdf_versions_7.x-1.0-alpha2/7.x-1.0-alpha2/mod_printer,_e-mail_and_pdf_versions_7.x-1.0-alpha2-7.x-1.0-alpha2.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Printer, e-mail and PDF versions module allows you to generate the following printer-friendly versions of any node: Printer-friendly version (webpage format),PDF version ,Send by-email.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Printer, e-mail and PDF versions module allows you to generate the following printer-friendly versions of any node.

PDF version (at www.example.com/printpdf/nid)
Send by-email (at www.example.com/printmail/nid)

where nid is the node id of content to render.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-2.0-beta3" name="References" id="mod_references_7.x-2.0-beta3">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_references_7.x-2.0-beta3/7.x-2.0-beta3/mod_references_7.x-2.0-beta3-7.x-2.0-beta3.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_options_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>References defines common base features for the various reference field types.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>References module defines common base features for the various reference field types.

As the past couple months showed, the current maintainers are not up to the task. This module accepts new maintainers.
References will most probably be deprecated in the near future in favor of Entity Reference, which should probably be considered first on fresh D7 projects. Another, more radical, alternative would be the Relation module.

This project provides D7 versions of the 'Node reference' and 'User reference' field types, that were part of the CCK package in D6, at functional parity with the D6 counterparts. See http://drupal.org/node/533222 for details.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0-alpha3" name="Google Analytics Statistics" id="mod_google_analytics_statistics_7.x-1.0-alpha3">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_google_analytics_statistics_7.x-1.0-alpha3/7.x-1.0-alpha3/mod_google_analytics_statistics_7.x-1.0-alpha3-7.x-1.0-alpha3.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Google Analytics Statistics allows your site to be tracked by Google Analytics by adding a Javascript tracking code to every page.
 </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Google Analytics Statistics allows your site to be tracked by Google Analytics by adding a Javascript tracking code to every page. The module allows you to add the following statistics features to your site:

Features:
1)Single/multi/cross domain tracking.
2)Selectively track/exclude certain users, roles and pages.
3)Monitor what type of links are tracked (downloads, outgoing and mailto).
4)Monitor what files are downloaded from your pages.
5)Custom variables support with tokens.
6)Custom code snippets.
7)Site Search support.
8)AdSense support.
9)Tracking of Goals.
10)Anonymize visitors IP address.
11)Cache the Google Analytics code on your local server for improved page loading times.
12)Access denied (403) and Page not found (404) tracking.
13)DoNotTrack support (non-cached content only).
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.x-dev" name="Secure Pages" id="mod_secure_pages_7.x-1.x-dev">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_secure_pages_7.x-1.x-dev/7.x-1.x-dev/mod_secure_pages_7.x-1.x-dev-7.x-1.x-dev.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Secure pages small process which will redirect the required pages to a SSL version of the page.
</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Secure pages small process which will redirect the required pages to a SSL version of the page.This module makes sure that the user is running on a secure page when they create or edit content, view user details, or administer the site.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-3.0-beta1" name="SEO Checklist" id="mod_seo_checklist_7.x-3.0-beta1">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_seo_checklist_7.x-3.0-beta1/7.x-3.0-beta1/mod_seo_checklist_7.x-3.0-beta1-7.x-3.0-beta1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>SEO Checklist module provides a checklist of recommended Drupal modules and good Drupal SEO (Search Engine Optimization) best practices. </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>SEO Checklist module provides a checklist of recommended Drupal modules and good Drupal SEO (Search Engine Optimization) best practices. Maximize the presence of your Drupal website in the major search engines like Google, Yahoo, Bing, etc. This module will:

provide a checklist that helps you keep track of what needs to be done
look to see what modules you already have installed and check them off for you automatically (thanks, EclipseGC!)
provide a list of things that you haven't done so that you can do them.
time/date stamp each item as you complete it so that you have a report that you can give your boss/client to show them how awesome you are that you've done all the SEO stuff
make you look like an SEO genius!

With this module, all you have to do is use the checklist and you'll know exactly what SEO stuff was done. It's more than just a list of stuff to do - it's a powerful organization tool, as well.

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-2.1" name="Service links" id="mod_service_links_7.x-2.1">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_service_links_7.x-2.1/7.x-2.1/mod_service_links_7.x-2.1-7.x-2.1.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Service Links allow the users to share the website's content on various social networks, bookmarking websites, social blogs and similiar, and help programmers to have a small framework that provide easily more services.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Service Links allow the users to share a web page in various social networks like bookmarking services, social blogs and similiar, providing an easy way to extend their number. Built on Drupal for Drupal doesn't include commercial advertising codes and don't require third part libraries.

The services included are various: del.icio.us, Digg/Digg button, Facebook/Facebook Share/Facebook Like, Furl, Google Bookmark/Google Plus One, IceRocket, LinkedIn/Linkedin button counter, MySpace, Newsvine, Reddit, StumbleUpon, Technorati, Twitter/Twitter widget, Yahoo Bookmark, and many more, they are split for language in different packages: basque, dutch, farsi, german, hungarian, italian, russian, spanish, swedish.

Other services are availables as an extra module fully customizable with some click.

Features:

1)Show links as text, image or both;
2)display for content types or taxonomy;
3)display in teaser, full page or both;
4)display links for user roles;
5)provide links on: node content, node link, block;
6)provide blocks for node and not-node pages;
7)sortable services through a drag'n drop table;
8)custom icons may be specified in a different folder;
9)browser bookmarking (work with Firefox, IE, Opera, Chrome);
10)support for short links (enhanced with Shorten Urls);
11)support for widgets (also known like dynamic buttons): Digg Button, Facebook Share, Facebook Like, Linkedin button counter, Google Plus One, Twitter Button;
12)title tag used for build the link, can be override with a custom string including tokens (look to Token project);
13)support for icon sprites (through Service Links Sprites plugin);
14)support the page visibility as every block does;
15)provide two powerful APIs for print the whole set of selected services or a custom subset (look the documentation page) with the ability to override the default settings.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0-beta1" name="SMTP Authentication Support" id="mod_smtp_authentication_support_7.x-1.0-beta1">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_smtp_authentication_support_7.x-1.0-beta1/7.x-1.0-beta1/mod_smtp_authentication_support_7.x-1.0-beta1-7.x-1.0-beta1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>SMTP Authentication Support module allows Drupal to bypass the PHP mail() function and send email directly to an SMTP server. The module supports SMTP authentication and can even connect to servers using SSL if supported by PHP.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>SMTP Authentication Support module allows Drupal to bypass the PHP mail() function and send email directly to an SMTP server. The module supports SMTP authentication and can even connect to servers using SSL if supported by PHP.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.1-beta1" name="SpamSpan" id="mod_spamspan_7.x-1.1-beta1">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_spamspan_7.x-1.1-beta1/7.x-1.1-beta1/mod_spamspan_7.x-1.1-beta1-7.x-1.1-beta1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_filter_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>SpamSpan module obfuscates email addresses to help prevent spambots from collecting them.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>SpamSpan module obfuscates email addresses to help prevent spambots from collecting them.

It implements the technique at the SpamSpan website (a German version is also available). The problem with most email address obfuscators is that they rely upon JavaScript being enabled on the client side. This makes the technique inaccessible to people with screen readers. SpamSpan however will produce clickable links if JavaScript is enabled, and will show the email address as example [at] example [dot] com if the browser does not support JavaScript or if JavaScript is disabled.

This technique is unlikely to be absolutely foolproof. It is possible in theory for a determined spambot to harvest addresses from your site no matter how you disguise them. But research suggests that the by far the great majority of spambots do not bother to attempt to collect addresses which have been hidden using JavaScript. Indeed, most spambots cannot currently read JavaScript at all.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-2.0-beta3" name="Strongarm" id="mod_strongarm_7.x-2.0-beta3">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_strongarm_7.x-2.0-beta3/7.x-2.0-beta3/mod_strongarm_7.x-2.0-beta3-7.x-2.0-beta3.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_chaos_tool_suite_7.x-1.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Strongarm gives site builders a way to override the default variable values that Drupal core and contributed modules ship with. It is not an end user tool, but a developer and site builder tool which provides an API and a limited UI. 

Enforces variable values defined by modules that need settings set to operate properly.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Strongarm gives site builders a way to override the default variable values that Drupal core and contributed modules ship with. It is not an end user tool, but a developer and site builder tool which provides an API and a limited UI.

An example of such a variable is site_frontpage. In Drupal this defaults to node, which ensures that the front page gets content as soon as some exists, but for many Drupal sites this setting is simply wrong. Strongarm gives the site builder a place in the equation - an opportunity to set the site_frontpage to something that makes sense for their site.

Strongarm leverages ctools to provide exportables of Drupal variables. This branch also allows Strongarm to be used with the Features module. More information about this work is available on this blog post.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0-beta2" name="User IP Log" id="mod_user_ip_log_7.x-1.0-beta2">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_user_ip_log_7.x-1.0-beta2/7.x-1.0-beta2/mod_user_ip_log_7.x-1.0-beta2-7.x-1.0-beta2.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_views_7.x-3.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>User IP Log is a simple module that logs the IP address of users on login event to table</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>User IP Log is a simple module that logs the IP address of users on login event to table.

Features:
1)Views Integration.
2)Added default page view User IP Log listing the recently logged users, IP and timestamp with username and uid filter.
3)Module uses Drupal ip_address() which is adjusted for reverse proxy.
4)Provides data for other modules to use for analytical and authentication purpose.
5)Could be extended to generate any custom reports using Views Bonus Pack, Views Group By or Views Charts.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0-beta5" name="Token" id="mod_token_7.x-1.0-beta5">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_token_7.x-1.0-beta5/7.x-1.0-beta5/mod_token_7.x-1.0-beta5-7.x-1.0-beta5.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Tokens provides a shared API for replacement of textual placeholders with actual data.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Tokens provides a shared API for replacement of textual placeholders with actual data.Tokens are small bits of text that can be placed into larger documents via simple placeholders, like %site-name or [user]. The Token module provides a central API for modules to use these tokens, and expose their own token values.

Note that Token module doesn't provide any visible functions to the user on its own, it just provides token handling services for other modules.

For Drupal 6, the Token module provides a &quot;Token Actions&quot; module which can be enabled separately. This provides several &quot;actions&quot; for the Drupal core Actions/Trigger modules to use that take advantage of the Token replacement functionality.

Modules that use the Token module and provide tokens via the API include Organic Groups, Pathauto, Comment Notify, and Commerce. Also check out the full list of modules that use or provide tokens or the list of open issues tagged with 'token'.

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-3.0" name="Transliteration" id="mod_transliteration_7.x-3.0">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_transliteration_7.x-3.0/7.x-3.0/mod_transliteration_7.x-3.0-7.x-3.0.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Translitertion provides one-way string transliteration (romanization) and cleans file names during upload by replacing unwanted characters.Converts non-latin text to US-ASCII and sanitizes file names.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Translitertion provides one-way string transliteration (romanization) and cleans file names during upload by replacing unwanted characters.Converts non-latin text to US-ASCII and sanitizes file names. It takes Unicode text and tries to represent it in US-ASCII characters (universally displayable, unaccented characters) by attempting to transliterate the pronunciation expressed by the text in some other writing system to Roman letters.According to Unidecode, from which most of the transliteration data has been derived, &quot;Russian and Greek seem to work passably. But it work quite bad on Japanese and Thai.&quot;

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.x-dev" name="Avatar Selection" id="mod_avatar_selection_7.x-1.x-dev">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_avatar_selection_7.x-1.x-dev/7.x-1.x-dev/mod_avatar_selection_7.x-1.x-dev-7.x-1.x-dev.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Avatar Selection manages configuration of a default list of avatar icons that a user can use instead of uploading a picture.

</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Avatar Selection manages configuration of a default list of avatar icons that a user can use instead of uploading a picture.When a user edits their account details they can choose to upload an image or photo of themselves, also known as an avatar.The Avatar Selection module allows the user to pick an avatar image from a list already loaded by an administrative user. It is also possible to disable the uploading of pictures by users and only allow them to select an avatar icon from this list.No images are supplied with this module. It is recommended that all images you use are roughly of the same size.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-3.0-beta2" name="Views Bulk Operations (VBO)" id="mod_views_bulk_operations_(vbo)_7.x-3.0-beta2">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_views_bulk_operations_(vbo)_7.x-3.0-beta2/7.x-3.0-beta2/mod_views_bulk_operations_(vbo)_7.x-3.0-beta2-7.x-3.0-beta2.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_entity_api_7.x-1.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_views_7.x-3.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_chaos_tool_suite_7.x-1.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>View Bulk Operation [VBO] provides a way of selecting multiple rows and applying operations to them.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>View Bulk Operation module augments views by allowing bulk operations to be executed on the displayed rows. It does so by showing a checkbox in front of each node, and adding a select box containing operations that can be applied. Drupal Core or Rules actions can be used.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-3.0" name="Views Slideshow" id="mod_views_slideshow_7.x-3.0">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_views_slideshow_7.x-3.0/7.x-3.0/mod_views_slideshow_7.x-3.0-7.x-3.0.zip</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_views_7.x-3.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_chaos_tool_suite_7.x-1.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>View slide show provides a view style that displays rows as a jQuery slideshow. This is an API and requires Views Slideshow Cycle or another module that supports the API.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Views Slideshow can be used to create a slideshow of any content (not just images) that can appear in a View. Powered by jQuery, it is heavily customizable: you may choose slideshow settings for each View you create.

Potential uses:

1)News item slideshow (such as the title, image and teaser of the last 5 news articles submitted)
2)The Last X number of X submitted (images, videos, blog entries, forum posts, comments, testimonials, etc.).
3)Rotate any image, based on any filters you can apply in views.
4)Hottest new products for any ecommerce drupal site.
5)Rotate contact links, share links, etc.
6)Heck, you could rotate entire nodes, categories, image galleries, etc. I wouldn't suggest it, but you have that power.
7)Its also a great space saver. Places where you had multiple images or multiple items such as RSS feeds or category listings can now be presented in a slideshow.

The possibilities are really endless, as the more ways you can think of to categorize and add to views, the more you can rotate.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-2.0-beta3" name="XML sitemap" id="mod_xml_sitemap_7.x-2.0-beta3">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_xml_sitemap_7.x-2.0-beta3/7.x-2.0-beta3/mod_xml_sitemap_7.x-2.0-beta3-7.x-2.0-beta3.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>XML sitemap module creates a sitemap that conforms to the sitemaps.org specification. </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>XML sitemap module creates a sitemap that conforms to the sitemaps.org specification. This helps search engines to more intelligently crawl a website and keep their results up to date. The sitemap created by the module can be automatically submitted to Ask, Google, Bing (formerly Windows Live Search), and Yahoo! search engines. The module also comes with several submodules that can add sitemap links for content, menu items, taxonomy terms, and user profiles.

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0-beta2" name="Taxonomy Manager" id="mod_taxonomy_manager_7.x-1.0-beta2">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_taxonomy_manager_7.x-1.0-beta2/7.x-1.0-beta2/mod_taxonomy_manager_7.x-1.0-beta2-7.x-1.0-beta2.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_taxonomy_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_options_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Taxonomy Manager is a tool for administrating taxonomy terms.
 </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Taxonomy Manager is a tool for administrating taxonomy terms.This module provides a powerful interface for managing taxonomies. A vocabulary gets displayed in a dynamic tree view, where parent terms can be expanded to list their nested child terms or can be collapsed.

The Taxonomy Manager has following operations and key features:

1)Dynamic treeview
2)Mass deleting
3)Mass adding of new terms
4)Moving of terms in hierarchies
5)Merging of terms (using the Term merge module in 7.x)
6)Fast weight changing with up and down arrows (and AJAX saving)
7)AJAX powered term editing form
8)Simple search interface
9)CSV Export of terms
10)i18n support for multilingual vocabularies (per language terms)
11)Double Tree interface for moving terms in hierarchies, adding new translations and switching terms between different vocabularies

For using the Taxonomy Manager you should have JavaScript and automatically load of images enabled in your browser.

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.x-dev" name="Taxonomy subterms " id="mod_taxonomy_subterms__7.x-1.x-dev">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_taxonomy_subterms__7.x-1.x-dev/7.x-1.x-dev/mod_taxonomy_subterms__7.x-1.x-dev-7.x-1.x-dev.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_taxonomy_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_options_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage_7.0</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Taxonomy Subterms displays subterms in terms page.

</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Taxonomy Subterms displays subterms in terms page.Taxonomy Subterms is a simple module to force display child taxonomy terms on the parent taxonomy page of nodes belonging to the current term or/and the children of the current term.Taxonomy subterms makes use of the exact same page callback of the default taxonomy terms page (or the one you put in place).The module just add the depth param with an 'all' value to the original arguments and pass them to the &quot;normal&quot; page callback.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-2.0-alpha1" name="Fivestar" id="mod_fivestar_7.x-2.0-alpha1">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_fivestar_7.x-2.0-alpha1/7.x-2.0-alpha1/mod_fivestar_7.x-2.0-alpha1-7.x-2.0-alpha1.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_voting_api_7.x-2.4</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Fivestar enables fivestar ratings on content, users, etc.

</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Fivestar enables fivestar ratings on content, users, etc.The Fivestar voting module adds a clean, attractive voting widget to nodes in Drupal 5, node and comments in Drupal 6, and any entity in Drupal 7.

Features:
1)jQuery rollover effects and AJAX no-reload voting.
2)Configurable star sets.
3)Graceful degradation to an HTML rating form when JavaScript is turned off.
4)Support for anonymous voters.
5)Spam protection to keep users from filling your DB with bogus votes.
6)Easy-to-use integration with Views module for lists sorted by rating, or filtered by min/max ratings.
7)A Fivestar CCK field for use in custom node types.
8)An easy-to-use Form API element type for use in other modules.
9)Compatible with all versions of jQuery (1.0 - 1.4.4).
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-3.0-rc2" name="Ubercart" id="mod_ubercart_7.x-3.0-rc2">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_ubercart_7.x-3.0-rc2/7.x-3.0-rc2/mod_ubercart_7.x-3.0-rc2-7.x-3.0-rc2.tar.gz</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_field_sql_storage_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_file_7.0</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_rules_7.x-2.0-rc2</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_views_7.x-3.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_chaos_tool_suite_7.x-1.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <dependentModules>mod_entity_api_7.x-1.0-rc1</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Ubercart out of the box is a great solution for stores that sell physical goods, digital product downloads, and site memberships.</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Ubercart out of the box is a great solution for stores that sell physical goods, digital product downloads, and site memberships.

Features:
1)Configurable product catalog includes catalog pages and a block to display product categories.
2)Flexible product creation system with product classes.
3)Multiple product image support out of the box.
4)Flexible product attributes system.
5)Basic product stock level tracking and notification.
6)Product features to add file downloads, role promotions, and more to products.
7)Single page checkout.
8)Automatic account generation (anonymous checkout).
9)Customer and administrator checkout notifications.
10)Simple order processing (with workflow for automated order processing).
11)Simple order creation and editing.
12)Integrated payment system that acts as a bridge between acceptable payment methods (check, credit card, purchase order, etc.) and payment gateways (CyberSource, Authorize.net, PayPal, etc.).
13)Shipping quotes and fulfillment, including integration with UPS, FedEx, USPS.
14)Sales, product, and customer reports.
15)Activity logging.

Ubercart is PayPal certified and integrates PayPal Website Payments Standard, Website Payments Pro, and Express Checkout. For more information, you can read the Ubercart PayPal information page.</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.1" name="variable" id="mod_variable_7.x-1.1">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_variable_7.x-1.1/7.x-1.1/mod_variable_7.x-1.1-7.x-1.1.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Variable module provides a registry for meta-data about Drupal variables and some extended Variable API and administration interface.
</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Variable module provides a registry for meta-data about Drupal variables and some extended Variable API and administration interface.Variable module provides a registry for meta-data about Drupal variables and some extended Variable API and administration interface.This is an API module so it must be installed only when other modules require it.

</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.0" name="shopmenu" id="mod_shopmenu_7.0">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_shopmenu_7.0/7.0/mod_shopmenu_7.0-7.0.zip</contentURL>
        <dependentModules>mod_ubercart_7.x-3.0-rc2</dependentModules>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Shopmenu provides shopping cart menu and contains ubercart module altered forms.

the &quot;menu&quot; hook (shop_menu). For each merchant from whom I'm using their datafeed, I make code like this in the shop_menu function: function shop_menu($may_cache) {   $items = array();   if ($may_cache) { .... ...</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Shopmenu provides shopping cart menu and contains ubercart module altered forms.

the &quot;menu&quot; hook (shop_menu). For each merchant from whom I'm using their datafeed, I make code like this in the shop_menu function: function shop_menu($may_cache) {   $items = array();   if ($may_cache) { .... ...</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.0-beta11.zip" name="apachesolr" id="mod_apachesolr_7.x-1.0-beta11.zip">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_apachesolr_7.x-1.0-beta11.zip/7.x-1.0-beta11.zip/mod_apachesolr_7.x-1.0-beta11.zip-7.x-1.0-beta11.zip.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Apachesolr module is a framework used for searching with Solr.
 </content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Apachesolr module is a framework used for searching with Solr. This module integrates Drupal with the Apache Solr search platform. Solr search can be used as a replacement for core content search and boasts both extra features and better performance. If you're looking for Apache Solr integration, this is possibly the best option available. Drupal 7

Drupal 7 version of the module is almost ready to go to a RC status. Faceted search is supported if you use the facet API module. Facets will be available for you ranging from content author to taxonomy to arbitrary fields.

This version also includes :

1)Search Pages (Multiple search pages with optionally customized search results)
2)Multiple Environment (support for Multiple Solr Servers)
3)Range Query type, that in combination with facet API and Facet Api Slider a very rich faceting experience delivers to the end user.
4)Supports Custom Entity indexing through hooks. Examples such as Apachesolr Commerce,Apachesolr User indexing and Apachesolr Term can give you a headstart in developing your own indexing code for your entity.
</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
    <module required="false" core="false" version="7.x-1.x-dev" name="workflow" id="mod_workflow_7.x-1.x-dev">
        <contentURL>/modules/tech-phpdru7/files/mod_workflow_7.x-1.x-dev/7.x-1.x-dev/mod_workflow_7.x-1.x-dev-7.x-1.x-dev.zip</contentURL>
        <documents>
            <document documentType="HELP_TEXT">
                <content>Workflow module allows the creation and assignment of arbitrary workflows to node types.
 

</content>
            </document>
            <document documentType="DESCRIPTION">
                <content>Workflow module allows the creation and assignment of arbitrary workflows to node types.The workflow module allows the creation and assignment of arbitrary workflows to Drupal node types. Workflows are made up of workflow states. For example, a workflow with the states Draft, Review, and Published could be assigned to the Story node type.Transitions between workflow states can have actions assigned to them. In our example, we could assign an action so that when the story moves from the Draft state to the Review state an email is sent out. Another action could be assigned to the transition from Review to Published so that the node's status is set to Published (and becomes visible on your website).</content>
            </document>
        </documents>
    </module>
</modules>
